<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>Iterating</title>
    <link href="https://iterating.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://iterating.com" />
    <updated>2025-11-21T14:35:28-05:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>AL8X</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://iterating.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Rank</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/rank/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/rank/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-21T14:35:28-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Did you know that we used to score people's intelligence? I&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Did you know that we used to score people's intelligence?</p>
<p>I mean, we still do for "geniuses" and what not. But I'm talking about going the other way. The low way.</p>
<p>And these ranks had titles like moron, imbecile, and idiot.</p>
<p>Guess which one was dumbest?</p>
<p>Idiot.</p>
<p>An imbecile is a little smarter than an idiot.</p>
<p>And a moron is King of the Stupid.</p>
<p>So, calling someone a moron isn't as bad as it sounds.</p>
<p>You're actually paying them a compliment.</p>
<p>If they're an imbecile or an idiot.</p>
<p>Class dismissed.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Sip the Juice</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/sip-the-juice/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/sip-the-juice/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-20T17:38:06-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    My brain is starting to unfog. This writing every day thing&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>My brain is starting to unfog.</p>
<p>This writing every day thing is helping me rewire.</p>
<p>Unclogging the conduction wire.</p>
<p>Letting more juice flow.</p>
<p>Not to say that I wasn't flowing before, but I wasn't flowing before.</p>
<p>Time is so interesting. </p>
<p>Living in a bad way felt numb. Like I wasn't in my skin. Just an observer.</p>
<p>My eyes didn't feel like my own.</p>
<p>It felt like forever. </p>
<p>But it's slowly and largely faded.</p>
<p>So staggeringly thankful.</p>
<p>I don't know if I'm just used to a new normal, a new avatar, but I am starting to understand.</p>
<p>I am just happy to be here.</p>
<p>An honor to be nominated.</p>
<p>Writing to myself.</p>
<p>To my loved ones.</p>
<p>And to strangers (how'd you get in here?).</p>
<p>The thing I'm focusing on now is energy. </p>
<p>The inner fuel tank.</p>
<p>I get about as terrible a gas mileage as my body-on-frame SUVs.</p>
<p>But I love 'em.</p>
<p>I'm not saying I want to be a Tesla or some hybrid, just want some more juice when I stomp.</p>
<p>Here's the thing I'm learning, though:</p>
<p>There was a time when I had to use my juice on just keeping myself above ground.</p>
<p>So I conserved it. Hoarded it. Let it stock up, even as it diminished.</p>
<p>But it is only by using it that the capacity regrows.</p>
<p>Muscle memory applying to all sorts of circuitry.</p>
<p>How much fuel do I got left?</p>
<p>I got enough to go around.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Diamond Hands and Crystal Balls</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/diamond-hands-and-crystal-balls/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/diamond-hands-and-crystal-balls/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-19T13:57:02-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    I see these gurus everywhere. They were shilling crypto a few&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I see these gurus everywhere.</p>
<p>They were shilling crypto a few years ago.</p>
<p>Then, they switched to NFTs.</p>
<p>Shouting "generational wealth!" </p>
<p>Which seems like a weird thing to shout when you're talking about jpegs.</p>
<p>Now, they're all in on AI, AGI, SI, etc.</p>
<p>Although it's starting to see some cracks, there, too.</p>
<p>If you're a guru, you got to keep hawking what's hot and jump to the next big thing.</p>
<p>And what is that?</p>
<p>I'm betting quantum.</p>
<p>You'll see it everywhere.</p>
<p>Computing, mechanics, physics.</p>
<p>We are living in such a strange time.</p>
<p>The things that happen at the quantum level, should you look into it, is stranger than any fiction, but it is as close to "fact" as anything is determined to be so today.</p>
<p>I'm no guru.</p>
<p>Just an old(ish) man.</p>
<p>But I can see things, even if they are a little blurrier than they were before.</p>
<p>Generational wealth!!!</p>
<p>WOOOO!!!</p>
<p>Spooky.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Salted</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/salted/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/salted/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-18T12:52:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    For over a year, I couldn't eat kimchi. This might not&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>For over a year, I couldn't eat kimchi.</p>
<p>This might not matter to you, but to a Korean adult, taking away their kimchi is just cruel.</p>
<p>It's not like I didn't have it around.</p>
<p>My family devours it.</p>
<p>I just went through some ess. And a part of said ess messed up my chew and taste buds.</p>
<p>And for a long time, it was just meat shakes.</p>
<p>Literal meat shakes.</p>
<p>During this time, I made a deal.</p>
<p>Ok, God, if the terms are I get to live, but I have to give up kimchi, I'll do it.</p>
<p>It wasn't easy, but I agreed.</p>
<p>Since that year, within the last year or so, I've been given the gift of taste back. I'm not sure if it's what I've always had or if it differs, but I'm thankful that kimchi tastes <em>GOOOOOOD</em>.</p>
<p>For every day of my life, for nearly every meal of my life, I've had kimchi.</p>
<p>Except for a stretch of just a little over a year, when kimchi just didn't sound good. I couldn't eat it if I wanted.</p>
<p>All of that to say, the things we take for granted, the things we consider essential, may or may not be so.</p>
<p>I did fine without the kimchi, I mean I lived, but it wasn't as essential as I thought.</p>
<p>It was just a food.</p>
<p>So I ask, what is truly essential? What <em>must</em> be?</p>
<p>What are you believing you <em>have</em> to have in your life, that just ain't true?</p>
<p>And what is truly sacred?</p>
<p>Truly holy?</p>
<p>I used to think kimchi was. I mean I still love it. But I went over a year without it.</p>
<p>It's just a jar of fermentation, like all of us. </p>
<p>I lost a lot during that season, but nothing I couldn't live without, although I would have been wrong about that if you'd asked me before it all happened.</p>
<p>The things I considered essential then are no longer so.</p>
<p>A nice to have. Not a must have. Never was a must have. I just thought that it was.</p>
<p>There are very, very, very few <em>must</em> haves.</p>
<p>I'm spending more and more time thinking about that.</p>
<p>But right now, I <em>get</em> to eat kimchi.</p>
<p>What a privilege.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>But</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/but/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/but/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-17T13:03:12-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    When I was growing up, there was a theory. That a&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>When I was growing up, there was a theory.</p>
<p>That a guy needed his butt whooped to truly be a man.</p>
<p>His arse need kicked.</p>
<p>It was just a rite of passage.</p>
<p>And you could mostly tell, from their actions and/or attitude, whether said kickage had taken place in their lives.</p>
<p>It, to me, is a measure of character. Of respect.</p>
<p>There's a lack of respect these days. Particularly self-respect. Self-pride is off the charts. But self-respect is in a recession at best.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>That person needs their whoopin'!</p>
</blockquote>
<p>I suppose I still say that today.</p>
<p>As a man of peace, this is more a fleeting thought in a glimmer of flame.</p>
<p>I don't really say it.</p>
<p>I'm a pacifist, man. </p>
<p>Truly.</p>
<p>Peace. Love. All that ess.</p>
<p>Next time, though, you see someone acting a fool, remember my wisdom.</p>
<p>It really eliminates 99% of your outrage.</p>
<p>Should you have any. </p>
<p>As a man of peace (have I said that yet?), I have a little (out)rage.</p>
<p>Yang to my yin, as they say (no one says that). </p>
<p>Have I told you I'm going for absurd?</p>
<p>Nailed it.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Even</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/even/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/even/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-16T16:42:35-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    We talk about odds. Like you have a 1 in a&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>We talk about odds.</p>
<p>Like you have a 1 in a 1000 chance to do this.</p>
<p>Or you have a 1% chance to succeed in that.</p>
<p>But the reality is, for most people, we only care about the results.</p>
<p>For example, if you had a 99% likelihood to pass a test, but you fail it, is there any solace in knowing you had such a high probability of passing? No, the only result you care about is your own.</p>
<p>So to me, I think most things are 50/50.</p>
<p>They happen or they don't.</p>
<p>Data is important.</p>
<p>But I don't care about the odds as it pertains to me.</p>
<p>It's always binary.</p>
<p>0.</p>
<p>1.</p>
<p>Heads.</p>
<p>Tails. </p>
<p>Win.</p>
<p>Lose.</p>
<p>Opportunity.</p>
<p>Cost.</p>
<p>Live.</p>
<p>Die.</p>
<p>To long shots and sure things.</p>
<p>Same same.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Rounding Error</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/rounding-error/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/rounding-error/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-15T13:23:59-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    We have stopped printing the penny. In this case, I am&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>We have stopped printing the penny.</p>
<p>In this case, I am using the patriotic "We" as I don't actually run the mint.</p>
<p>But listen, I'm on a roll here.</p>
<p>Did you know it cost four cents to print a penny?</p>
<p>Oof.</p>
<p>Ooooof.</p>
<p>It hurts my brain.</p>
<p>I don't know how much it costs to print a nickel, but if I were a nickel, I'd be sweating.</p>
<p>USA! USA! USA!</p>
<p>If pennies are from heaven, here's hoping you made it back home.</p>
<p>To pinching dimes.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Thanks</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/thanks/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/thanks/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-14T18:35:32-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    I wish it didn't take a scare once in a while&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I wish it didn't take a scare once in a while to remember how lucky and blessed you are.</p>
<p>I wish it didn't, but sometimes it does.</p>
<p>A jolt back into reality.</p>
<p>A wake-up call.</p>
<p>A near miss.</p>
<p>The more susceptible you are to danger, the more you realize how much plain ol' luck has to do with it.</p>
<p><em>Just wasn't my day to go.</em></p>
<p>Dodged a bullet.</p>
<p>You could credit skill, but I ain't Neo.</p>
<p>Better to be lucky than great, sure.</p>
<p>But not better than good.</p>
<p>Good still beats luck.</p>
<p>I hope.</p>
<p>It's just sometimes, lucky survives, and good don't.</p>
<p>To the unlucky good. Just wasn't your day. </p>
<p>Time to go.</p>
<p>Good luck.</p>
<p>Signed,</p>
<p>One lucky mf.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Wisdom</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/wisdom/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/wisdom/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-13T13:19:17-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    As I've said before, I'm currently in an absurd phase. I'm&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>As I've said before, I'm currently in an absurd phase.</p>
<p>I'm going for absurd.</p>
<p>As an underachieving, overachieving Asian going for absurd, there is always motivation in insults.</p>
<p>So here's an absurd motivational insult to put in your pocket while you pursue the meaning of life:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Don't be wisdumb, be wissmart!</p>
</blockquote>
<p>...</p>
<p>I'll see myself out.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>The Way of Other Ways</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/the-way-of-other-ways/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/the-way-of-other-ways/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-12T17:08:39-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    As a self-proclaimed martial artist of little to no renown, I&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>As a self-proclaimed martial artist of little to no renown, I seek the Way.</p>
<p>How do I define the Way?</p>
<p>When Bruce Lee first taught in America, the old Chinese grandmasters had a problem with it.</p>
<p>For lots of reasons, but for two main ones:</p>
<p>1) He taught others besides (but including) Chinese people.</p>
<p>2) He taught more than one way.</p>
<p>Bruce came to the conclusion that you study and practice all arts, adding what is useful and discarding what is not. In martial and other arts.</p>
<p>But old folks (especially Chinese grandmasters) are stuck in their ways.</p>
<p>In their Way.</p>
<p>There are no other Ways.</p>
<p>Just one.</p>
<p>Of course, this is just old people trying to protect older ideas.</p>
<p>In an era where nothing is sacred (always the present), they wanted to keep something so (always the past).</p>
<p>Change is scary.</p>
<p>Change is unknown.</p>
<p>Change is future.</p>
<p>But the thing about chasing other Ways is that you aren't disrespecting, you are being the most respectful. </p>
<p>How do you know the strengths of your beliefs if they are never tested?</p>
<p>If you don't seek other Ways?</p>
<p>Belief must be tested.</p>
<p>After all you have gone through, after all you are going through, and after all you will go through, what will you still believe?</p>
<p>What has stayed the same?</p>
<p>What has changed?</p>
<p>What should change?</p>
<p>Seek and try other Ways.</p>
<p>As many as you can.</p>
<p>Test it against your status quo.</p>
<p>Keep what works.</p>
<p>Discard the rest.</p>
<p>Treasure what works.</p>
<p>Throw away what does not.</p>
<p><em>Throw away what does not!</em></p>
<p>THROW AWAY WHAT DOES NOT!</p>
<p>Most of us know what to keep.</p>
<p>It's knowing what to throw away that you keep hanging onto, that's the killer.</p>
<p>There are other Ways.</p>
<p>This is mine.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
