<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>Iterating</title>
    <link href="https://iterating.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://iterating.com" />
    <updated>2025-11-14T18:44:41-05:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>AL8X</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://iterating.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Thanks</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/thanks/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/thanks/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-14T18:35:32-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    I wish it didn't take a scare once in a while&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I wish it didn't take a scare once in a while to remember how lucky and blessed you are.</p>
<p>I wish it didn't, but sometimes it does.</p>
<p>A jolt back into reality.</p>
<p>A wake-up call.</p>
<p>A near miss.</p>
<p>The more susceptible you are to danger, the more you realize how much plain ol' luck has to do with it.</p>
<p><em>Just wasn't my day to go.</em></p>
<p>Dodged a bullet.</p>
<p>You could credit skill, but I ain't Neo.</p>
<p>Better to be lucky than great.</p>
<p>But not better than good.</p>
<p>Good still beats luck.</p>
<p>It's just sometimes, luck survives, and good don't.</p>
<p>To the unlucky good. Just wasn't your day. </p>
<p>Time to go.</p>
<p>May you rise, once more.</p>
<p>Good luck.</p>
<p>Signed,</p>
<p>One lucky mf.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Wisdom</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/wisdom/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/wisdom/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-13T13:19:17-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    As I've said before, I'm currently in an absurd phase. I'm&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>As I've said before, I'm currently in an absurd phase.</p>
<p>I'm going for absurd.</p>
<p>As an underachieving, overachieving Asian going for absurd, there is always motivation in insults.</p>
<p>So here's an absurd motivational insult to put in your pocket while you pursue the meaning of life:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Don't be wisdumb, be wissmart!</p>
</blockquote>
<p>...</p>
<p>I'll see myself out.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>The Way of Other Ways</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/the-way-of-other-ways/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/the-way-of-other-ways/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-12T17:08:39-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    As a self-proclaimed martial artist of little to no renown, I&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>As a self-proclaimed martial artist of little to no renown, I seek the Way.</p>
<p>How do I define the Way?</p>
<p>When Bruce Lee first taught in America, the old Chinese grandmasters had a problem with it.</p>
<p>For lots of reasons, but for two main ones:</p>
<p>1) He taught others besides (but including) Chinese people.</p>
<p>2) He taught more than one way.</p>
<p>Bruce came to the conclusion that you study and practice all arts, adding what is useful and discarding what is not. In martial and other arts.</p>
<p>But old folks (especially Chinese grandmasters) are stuck in their ways.</p>
<p>In their Way.</p>
<p>There are no other Ways.</p>
<p>Just one.</p>
<p>Of course, this is just old people trying to protect older ideas.</p>
<p>In an era where nothing is sacred (always the present), they wanted to keep something so (always the past).</p>
<p>Change is scary.</p>
<p>Change is unknown.</p>
<p>Change is future.</p>
<p>But the thing about chasing other Ways is that you aren't disrespecting, you are being the most respectful. </p>
<p>How do you know the strengths of your beliefs if they are never tested?</p>
<p>If you don't seek other Ways?</p>
<p>Belief must be tested.</p>
<p>After all you have gone through, after all you are going through, and after all you will go through, what will you still believe?</p>
<p>What has stayed the same?</p>
<p>What has changed?</p>
<p>What should change?</p>
<p>Seek and try other Ways.</p>
<p>As many as you can.</p>
<p>Test it against your status quo.</p>
<p>Keep what works.</p>
<p>Discard the rest.</p>
<p>Treasure what works.</p>
<p>Throw away what does not.</p>
<p><em>Throw away what does not!</em></p>
<p>THROW AWAY WHAT DOES NOT!</p>
<p>Most of us know what to keep.</p>
<p>It's knowing what to throw away that you keep hanging onto, that's the killer.</p>
<p>There are other Ways.</p>
<p>This is mine.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Ivory and Gold</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/ivory-and-gold/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/ivory-and-gold/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-11T13:04:12-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Today is a very special day. I won't say why because&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Today is a very special day.</p>
<p>I won't say why because some things are just for me.</p>
<p>I always thought I would end up alone on some mountain top in rural Korea.</p>
<p>Contemplating and striking the air and wooden things.</p>
<p>You know, monk type ess.</p>
<p>And I suppose there is a universe where I am doing just that.</p>
<p>But not this one.</p>
<p>In this one, I have to nurture and love ivory and two precious mixtures of ivory and gold.</p>
<p>Yes, they all drive me crazy, but I suppose everything I have ever loved does.</p>
<p>So alas, my mountain top is digital.</p>
<p>My alone is in brief pockets of time. </p>
<p>I am the <em>richest man in the world</em>.</p>
<p>A hermit with a fortune.</p>
<p>Just like I dreamed.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Treasure Chaser</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/treasure-chaser/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/treasure-chaser/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-10T12:09:45-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Are your memories treasure? Or are your visions of the future&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Are your memories treasure?</p>
<p>Or are your visions of the future the treasure?</p>
<p>What about the present?</p>
<p>Is right now considered a treasure?</p>
<p>They all seem pretty valuable.</p>
<p>Treasure hunters are an interesting group.</p>
<p>Chasing futures where they hope to find the valued past right now or somewhat soonish.</p>
<p>Someone's past, found in someone else's present, for yet another someone else's future.</p>
<p>Actually finding the treasure comes with all sorts of drama (like all big moments).</p>
<p>You may not even be able to keep it.</p>
<p>The law, ya know.</p>
<p>Ahh, but the chase is yours.</p>
<p>They can't take that away, right?</p>
<p>Right?</p>
<p>Did they take that away?</p>
<p>How big is your fortune?</p>
<p>Is it vaulted in your heart?</p>
<p>Is it in the cloud in your brain?</p>
<p>Or can you touch it with your lips?</p>
<p>Are you the treasure?</p>
<p>Yours or anyone else's?</p>
<p>Somewhere between remembering and imagining is present day.</p>
<p>Vault, earth, cloud.</p>
<p>I'd say carpe diem or some ess, but I hear they cancelled Latin.</p>
<p><em>Sic Transit Gloria.</em></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Timelines</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/timelines/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/timelines/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-09T23:06:45-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    I almost forgot to write again. Some days just fly by.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I almost forgot to write again.</p>
<p>Some days just fly by.</p>
<p>Most days do.</p>
<p>As you get older, the seconds, minutes, hours, and days just seem a bit shorter.</p>
<p>Even the microwave timer I set for a few comfortable minutes seems to take me by surprise.</p>
<p><em>Already? I thought I had more time.</em></p>
<p>Kids never want the day to end.</p>
<p>They can spend an eternity in a day and still want it to last a little longer.</p>
<p>My little ones are how I measure time now.</p>
<p>I don't <em>feel</em> old.</p>
<p>I just act it.</p>
<p>Always have.</p>
<p>But when I see how big they're getting, well, do the math.</p>
<p>This is a very wonderful season. In the year. Of my life.</p>
<p>If you don't know by now, I believe time is the truest and most precious currency. </p>
<p>And attention is how we pay.</p>
<p>Are you paying attention to how you spend your time?</p>
<p>Tick tock. </p>
<p>Ever wonder why they call the app that?</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Guano</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/guano/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/guano/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-08T17:48:08-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Ever hear the idea that insanity is doing the same thing&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Ever hear the idea that insanity is doing the same thing over and over and expecting a different result?</p>
<p>This is a <em>mostly</em> true statement.</p>
<p>But there are always exceptions to every rule. Exceptions so few that they prove the rule.</p>
<p>For example, do you know how they split really big rocks?</p>
<p>One person grabs a big hammer.</p>
<p>Said person smashes said hammer on big rock. </p>
<p>It does nothing.</p>
<p>They smash it again in the same spot.</p>
<p>Over and over again.</p>
<p>Expecting it to crack.</p>
<p>It doesn't.</p>
<p>Not right away.</p>
<p>They just keep smacking the rock.</p>
<p>Same spot.</p>
<p>Over and over.</p>
<p>The key is patience. And knowing where and how to strike.</p>
<p>They just keep smashing away.</p>
<p>Then you know what happens?</p>
<p>After a long time, and a lot of reps, the rock just suddenly splits.</p>
<p>A bat ess crazy person probably discovered this.</p>
<p>So, for your consideration:</p>
<p>What are you doing, over and over, expecting a different result?</p>
<p>And are you splitting a rock or swinging at a shadow?</p>
<p>Three feet from gold or digging your own grave?</p>
<p>Find good hammer.</p>
<p>Find good rock. </p>
<p>Find right spot to smash.</p>
<p>Smash rock in right spot.</p>
<p>Over and over.</p>
<p>Nothing happens.</p>
<p>Keep going.</p>
<p>Rock splits.</p>
<p>Good work.</p>
<p>Good rock.</p>
<p>Good human.</p>
<p>Next rock...</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Once Upon A Time</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/once-upon-a-time/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/once-upon-a-time/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-07T00:37:54-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    I'm just happy to be here. I know sometimes it's not&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I'm just happy to be here.</p>
<p>I know sometimes it's not clear.</p>
<p>That's the old curmudgeon in me.</p>
<p>But I've always been this way.</p>
<p>Right now, all of this, every single ridiculous post, is me reeling from the reality of how a man who plays the long game almost passes, but survives.</p>
<p>Lives to fight another day.</p>
<p>A most fortunate man.</p>
<p>How do you keep thinking and planning the future when you're just enjoying, and grateful for, today?</p>
<p>I tell those closest to me that I'm in my absurd phase.</p>
<p>I'm going for absurd.</p>
<p>It seems like a fun way to play it.</p>
<p>All of this, after all, is the stuff of fairy tales.</p>
<p>Magic and wonder.</p>
<p>I sit in awe of it all.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>But if I'm not the same, the next question is, "Who in the world am I?" Ah! That's the great puzzle!</p>
</blockquote>
<p>And they lived happily ever after.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>The End</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/the-end/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/the-end/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-06T14:34:50-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    You ever stick to something, just because you wanted to see&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>You ever stick to something, just because you wanted to see how it ends?</p>
<p>Be it a book, a game, a movie, a tv show, a job?</p>
<p>Why do we do that?</p>
<p>Some sort of closure is needed. </p>
<p>Even if you know it'll disappoint.</p>
<p>I'd like to think that wisdom is in knowing what to finish and what to just stop.</p>
<p>What is worth finishing?</p>
<p>What is worth stopping?</p>
<p>Oh, and don't worry.</p>
<p>I am still going to write here.</p>
<p>Just getting started.</p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>The Answer</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/the-answer/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/the-answer/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-06T14:23:02-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    You know what your problem is? I think that's a fine&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>You know what your problem is?</p>
<p>I think that's a fine way to start a sentence.</p>
<p>But you better come correct with the follow-up.</p>
<p>Well, do you?</p>
<p>Hmm?</p>
<p>Hmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm?</p>
<p>Yeah, heck if I know.</p>
<p>No gurus here.</p>
<p>Figure it out.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
