<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>Iterating</title>
    <link href="https://iterating.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://iterating.com" />
    <updated>2025-12-24T00:02:00-05:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>杻백</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://iterating.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Sacralize</title>
        <author>
            <name>杻백</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/sacralize/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/sacralize/</id>

        <updated>2025-12-24T00:02:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Years ago, I remember Joe Rogan sharing a story on his&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Years ago, I remember Joe Rogan sharing a story on his show.</p>
<p>This was way back before he became <em>the</em> dude in podcasting.</p>
<p>I don't listen to many podcasts anymore, but back then he would just go on and on about whatever the heck with his co-host.</p>
<p>And this one day, he's on a roll.</p>
<p>Talking about how we take so much for granted.</p>
<p>And he set it up this way.</p>
<p>Which is how I think I can best define what I mean by "sacralize" aka my new favorite word.</p>
<p>He said, imagine living underground for your entire life. You only know caves and tunnels and passages and nothing else. Everyone lives this way.</p>
<p>And one day, you hear about this ultimate attraction.</p>
<p>It's at the end of a tunnel that leads up. Impossibly up.</p>
<p>And if you have enough money, you can pay to go there.</p>
<p>And the few people who have gone rave about it forever.</p>
<p>They just can't believe it's there.</p>
<p>So you save up, wait for your window (because it's only open during certain hours), and you go.</p>
<p>You pay the enormous admission fee and see for yourself.</p>
<p>And you climb up this ladder for seemingly forever in this narrow tunnel which leads to a little room with a hole in the ceiling.</p>
<p>And through the opening you can see it.</p>
<p>The above world.</p>
<p>The outside world.</p>
<p>The night's sky.</p>
<p>And more importantly, the unlimited (give or take) amount of stars in the sky.</p>
<p>And you sit and stare in awe.</p>
<p>Forever changed.</p>
<p>You'll spend the rest of your life underground talking about what you saw.</p>
<p>Most will never believe you.</p>
<p>And I suppose that's what I mean by sacralizing.</p>
<p>We don't sacralize the night's starry skies because it is just so routine for us.</p>
<p>But if we lived underground, and had to pay to see the stars, we would sacralize it.</p>
<p>Because it deserves it.</p>
<p>And I remember Rogan telling this story and just thinking how right he was.</p>
<p>How we would make it a holy pilgrimage to see the night's lights.</p>
<p>If it just wasn't available almost every single night of our lives.</p>
<p>And that's the trick of sacralization.</p>
<p>You make it sacred even though, and especially because, it is so routine.</p>
<p>Yes, it is just what happens on a clear evening.</p>
<p>Stars just show themselves.</p>
<p>But it is also something sacred.</p>
<p>Both can be true.</p>
<p>Both are true.</p>
<p>And so, 'tis the season to remember such things.</p>
<p>How beautiful things are that you see everyday.</p>
<p>It doesn't make them less important, I argue it does the exact opposite.</p>
<p>The beautiful and important things you see everyday are more beautiful and more important because you see them everyday.</p>
<p>Not less.</p>
<p>I've learned the best things in life are free.</p>
<p>But you have to earn them to keep them.</p>
<p>Understand?</p>
<p>So next time, maybe every time from here on out, you look up and see a million stars, you experience it as if you had to spend your life's savings earned living underground to see it.</p>
<p>And the realization that hey, <em>hey</em>, this is just given to me.</p>
<p>And do that, do that same thing, when you look down, and from side to side while you're at it.</p>
<p>And I think, <em>I think</em>, that's the secret recipe to all of this.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Diamonds or Coals</title>
        <author>
            <name>杻백</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/diamonds-or-coals/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/diamonds-or-coals/</id>

        <updated>2025-12-23T12:19:03-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Now's not the time to be writing on this thing. It's&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Now's not the time to be writing on this thing.</p>
<p>It's a time to celebrate.</p>
<p>To dance and sway a little.</p>
<p>To find a mistletoe.</p>
<p>To help Santa be Santa. Shhhh.</p>
<p>To believe in magic.</p>
<p>Have you been good?</p>
<p>What you get?</p>
<p>I'm notoriously hard to buy a gift for. Not because of any real reason. I just don't want many things people can buy me.</p>
<p>The gifts I want I already have. So if people ask what I want, it would be gifts for my gifts. So that's what people do. Buy gifts for them.</p>
<p>I don't say this piously. I enjoy watching their joy. It's wonderful.</p>
<p>Much better than if I got a new shirt or gift card.</p>
<p>I do like metal pens, though. Just saying.</p>
<p>Merry almost Christmas.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Snowflake Opposite</title>
        <author>
            <name>杻백</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/snowflake-opposite/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/snowflake-opposite/</id>

        <updated>2025-12-22T13:04:08-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Welp, it's about that time to put a bow on 2025.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Welp, it's about that time to put a bow on 2025.</p>
<p>It's not here yet, 2026 I mean, but you can see it from here.</p>
<p>Depending on your field, either a lot gets done this week or nothing does.</p>
<p>I think for most it's nothing.</p>
<p>Some might be scrambling for end of year deadlines, hosting family and friends, or last minute gifts (or gift cards), but that's about it.</p>
<p>It's a chill time, literally for some. Figuratively for most.</p>
<p>This year has been something. One for the record books.</p>
<p>Like him or not, the US President has stuffed a decade of events into one year.</p>
<p>But buckle up, buttercup.</p>
<p>I think we're looking at another 30 years in the next handful.</p>
<p>This might not make much sense right now, but it will.</p>
<p>...</p>
<p>There are two easy ways to waste time:</p>
<p>One is to spend it on useless things. Worthless things. Under the Pareto principles, this works out to about 80% of your time spent on a whole bunch of nothing. Or at least, proportionately nothing.</p>
<p>The other is to try to hold onto it too badly. Trying to capture it and put it into your pocket. You try to get it just right and end up missing the whole darn thing because you were too focused on holding onto it. Because you wanted to savor it.</p>
<p>So I'm looking forward to 2026.</p>
<p>I can't believe I'm almost there.</p>
<p>It's a special year as far as years go, for me.</p>
<p>But I ain't counting chickens (or crows), yet.</p>
<p>I am enjoying this last week or so of 2025.</p>
<p>Putting my chair back, reclining, and just taking it all in.</p>
<p>My cup runneth over of Coke Zero.</p>
<p>Ahhhh.</p>
<p>Carbonation.</p>
<p>What a life.</p>
<p>What a run.</p>
<p>What a world.</p>
<p>Thank You for letting me play.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>What Happens If I Press This Button?</title>
        <author>
            <name>杻백</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/what-happens-if-i-press-this-button/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/what-happens-if-i-press-this-button/</id>

        <updated>2025-12-21T12:57:36-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    As an autodidactic amateur coder, I draw parallels and contrasts to&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>As an autodidactic amateur coder, I draw parallels and contrasts to things I know to the things I want to know.</p>
<p>And it's clear that when you build something, sometimes things break.</p>
<p>You make big updates, but something along the line was ignored, accidentally erased, or just downright incompatible, making the whole thing not work.</p>
<p>It happens so frequently that after every change my goal is to try and break it, use it until I find a point of failure (which I usually can).</p>
<p>So there's this delicate balance.</p>
<p>Of making improvements but keeping it running optimally.</p>
<p>Of adding new features but not over clunking the experience.</p>
<p>Of changing things but not crashing it all down.</p>
<p>This is where that word, iterating, becomes so key.</p>
<p>You tinker. You add. You see if it still works. See if you like the changes. Then tinker again.</p>
<p>In theory, there's a time when you stop tinkering, when you move on to another project or priority. But it's nice to think you can come back, revisit, at any time. This is what's different about code. You can always go back.</p>
<p>Change the past.</p>
<p>You can even make backups. You should make backups.</p>
<p>I suppose you can do this in real life, but not in a time machine sense.</p>
<p>So here's hoping all your updates are upgrades.</p>
<p>And that you never break.</p>
<p>We both know that's not going to happen forever.</p>
<p>But that's part of the fun.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>All Dawgs</title>
        <author>
            <name>杻백</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/all-dawgs/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/all-dawgs/</id>

        <updated>2025-12-20T11:48:44-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    What's on the other side of the edge of the universe?&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>What's on the other side of the edge of the universe?</p>
<p>I mean, it can't go on forever can it?</p>
<p>What's on the other side?</p>
<p>One step over the edge.</p>
<p>Nothing?</p>
<p>Everything?</p>
<p>Another universe?</p>
<p>Is it like a video game, where you can see there's something beyond it, but you cannot go in, because the game won't let you?</p>
<p>They didn't code for that.</p>
<p>Is it just pure darkness, or nothingness, or void?</p>
<p>Or is it something cooler, more majestic, more awesome, than we can imagine?</p>
<p>All things being equal, I always wonder why people choose to believe in there being nothing there.</p>
<p>I mean, if you have the choice, and I think you do, why not choose to believe there's something incredible on the other side of infinity?</p>
<p>Why not have faith that there's something larger than all of us combined, than all of this combined, and that that thing is actually rooting for us, believing in us, loving us, when we sometimes aren't worth doing so?</p>
<p>That's the part that hurts me (such as I can hurt), it's the what happened to you to make you stop (or never start) believing?</p>
<p>It reminds me of a story.</p>
<p>About a pair of twins.</p>
<p>Who grew up in a terrible home.</p>
<p>Hurt by their world, their parents, by everyone.</p>
<p>And one grew up just like they were raised. While the other grew up to be a loving person and live a good life.</p>
<p>And when you asked them, after all these years, why they did what they did, they answered the same way:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>How was I supposed to turn out with the way I was raised?</p>
</blockquote>
<p>I'm probably getting it all wrong, but I hope you get the idea.</p>
<p>One learns how to be from their upbringing, another learns how <em>not</em> to be.</p>
<p>A playbook versus a cautionary tale.</p>
<p>And believe me, I've seen many things that should have turned my faith, I get it.</p>
<p>But I feel like not having faith is also somehow not having faith in yourself.</p>
<p>Somehow, it feels like not believing is like saying, "I don't believe in myself, anymore."</p>
<p>Do you get me?</p>
<p>And so, if I were the sort to pour out a little liquor, I'd do so right now.</p>
<p>On the curb.</p>
<p>For those who never had faith, or lost it along their way.</p>
<p>And I hope you join me in pouring one out, rather than be the one we pour for.</p>
<p>Because I think believing there's something on the other side of forever is just so much easier, it makes so much more sense, than believing there's nothing.</p>
<p>I just do.</p>
<p>And after everything I've gone through, everything I have won and lost, everything I have done and not done, how could I believe in anything else?</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>How the Best Get Bigger</title>
        <author>
            <name>杻백</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/how-the-best-get-bigger/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/how-the-best-get-bigger/</id>

        <updated>2025-12-19T13:18:12-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    You know, there's this idea that we are all born with&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>You know, there's this idea that we are all born with limitless potential.</p>
<p>Or at least a maximum potential.</p>
<p>And that things that happen to you over time slowly (or quickly) chop away at it.</p>
<p>Nothing increases your potential (it was always there), but lots of things, everything, can knock it down.</p>
<p>And I wrestle with this a bit.</p>
<p>I mean, I think I agree.</p>
<p>But it's sort of a downer, right?</p>
<p>You wonder how many good souls have been smashed by their lives.</p>
<p>How many beautiful things turned ugly simply by being born, raised, and lived in a certain place, in a certain time, around a certain person.</p>
<p>It's the whole nature versus nurture thing.</p>
<p>Some of us are born animals, but a lot of us stay wild. Or are turned it. I'm not sure which. Probably both.</p>
<p>Or even worse, they became domesticated.</p>
<p>Woof.</p>
<p>And so, I now look at the vast potential of youth. And think: How do I best preserve their infinite/maximum potential?</p>
<p>As a man who believes I'd rather my loved ones be safe than sorry, I wrestle with the balance of how fun it is to take risks and challenge yourself versus keeping them out of danger (which is also somewhat dangerous).</p>
<p>How do I teach failure is ok, necessary even, when it hurts their tender hearts?</p>
<p>How do I not chop away?</p>
<p>Must I chop away?</p>
<p>How do I keep them perfect?</p>
<p>Can I keep them perfect?</p>
<p>I can see now, I was chopped away at.</p>
<p>We all are.</p>
<p>Over time. Over decades.</p>
<p>Over and over.</p>
<p>I was a big block of jagged rock.</p>
<p>I'd like to think I'm more chiseled now.</p>
<p>Smoother (but rougher).</p>
<p>A curated sculpture.</p>
<p>Work of art or some bull.</p>
<p>I sure am something, alright.</p>
<p>But I was more beautiful as a child.</p>
<p>Who cannot say that?</p>
<p>I'm sorry if you cannot say that.</p>
<p>My job then, is to learn what chops down, and what doesn't.</p>
<p>I think I know.</p>
<p>But like all things, I have to go back.</p>
<p>In the 90s, one of my heroes was Lee Haney, a bodybuilding icon. And I remember watching him train. And he was a funny dude for a big mamma jamma and he'd always repeat this line, even while hoisting comically large amounts of iron, as to how to best get bigger:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>"Stimulate, don't annihilate, amateur!"</p>
</blockquote>
<p>He'd call whoever he was training with, and you, an amateur.</p>
<p>Which I always appreciated.</p>
<p>As the guy who wore the Mr. Olympia title and defended it for a decade, I suppose everyone else was.</p>
<p>But I think that's it, Lee.</p>
<p>I think that's the key.</p>
<p>To turning pro or keeping things at optimum levels.</p>
<p>Avoid the annihilating chops.</p>
<p>Seek the stimulating ones.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Pow Pow</title>
        <author>
            <name>杻백</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/pow-pow/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/pow-pow/</id>

        <updated>2025-12-18T14:05:18-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    You ever write something and then just erase it? I wrote&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>You ever write something and then just erase it?</p>
<p>I wrote paragraphs here and just didn't like it.</p>
<p>I suppose everyone does that but I usually don't.</p>
<p>I just write and tinker and keep writing.</p>
<p>It probably shows.</p>
<p>This whole writing thing is a part of me, part of who I am, and it is one of the things I thought I had lost, but I'm finding again.</p>
<p>So many things have changed for me in the past few years, so I am happy to say I am able to write again.</p>
<p>Writing feels like such a selfish thing. And with my time at a premium, it felt like a waste of valuable minutes when I could be, should be, focusing on other things.</p>
<p>But like with <span style="text-decoration: line-through;">really, really few, almost never really,</span>many things, I was wrong.</p>
<p>I've learned that a little bit of typing time is a wonderful thing.</p>
<p>It amplifies the rest of my day.</p>
<p>Maybe by turning gears, removing cobwebs, warming me up. Who knows.</p>
<p>I'm starting to think, "Oh, I should write about that."</p>
<p>So thanks for that, digital notebook made by a fruit, for letting me do just that. Too many thats.</p>
<p>There's memories in my muscles. My fingers. And tapping them repetitively on little squares have helped me in more ways than I could have imagined.</p>
<p>A return to first principles.</p>
<p>Start from the foundation.</p>
<p>One tap at a time.</p>
<p>1.</p>
<p>2.</p>
<p>3.</p>
<p>Unlocking levels long forgotten.</p>
<p>Unlocking levels yet to attain.</p>
<p>I'm rereading books and learning how much I had missed the first few times around. Seeing the whole world through these new, old, lenses.</p>
<p>And how much <em>perspective</em> has to do with everyone and everything.</p>
<p>I don't know what I'm getting at.</p>
<p>I'm just glad I get to write.</p>
<p>[Finger guns!]</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Watch My Six</title>
        <author>
            <name>杻백</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/watch-my-six/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/watch-my-six/</id>

        <updated>2025-12-17T11:58:54-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    "You got my back?" "Hell yeah." Back in the day, this&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <blockquote>
<p>"You got my back?"</p>
<p>"Hell yeah."</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Back in the day, this is all that mattered when determining your truest friends.</p>
<p>It's how you measured them.</p>
<p>That when it went down, and it always eventually would, some people would stay and others would run.</p>
<p>And it wasn't always who you thought it would be.</p>
<p>Both ways.</p>
<p>I've had friends run the second (before) it got hot.</p>
<p>And I've had bare acquaintances defend my honor without a second thought.</p>
<p>It's just who they were.</p>
<p>There till the end.</p>
<p>These people quickly switched places.</p>
<p>If only in my heart.</p>
<p>I used to work at a place where they would repeat certain phrases. Mantras. Things they thought wise. Witty.</p>
<p>One of them was, "If someone tells you who they are, believe them."</p>
<p>Which I always thought was the dumbest thing I had ever heard in my life.</p>
<p>People lie all the time.</p>
<p>Tell you how great they are and all that feces.</p>
<p>But you see, I was wrong.</p>
<p>For the saying is based on people telling you who they are through their <em>actions</em>, not their words.</p>
<p>You hope that actions and words mean the same thing, and ideally they do, but your experience should show you how this just isn't so.</p>
<p>Look around you.</p>
<p>Who's the nice person pretending to be a jerk?</p>
<p>And who's the jerk pretending to be a nice person?</p>
<p>Now, I'll be the first one to tell you that if you watch your back too much, you'll take an uppercut to the jaw when you turn around.</p>
<p>Keep your head on a swivel.</p>
<p>This is why it's important to have people around you that you can absolutely trust.</p>
<p>Such a list is a short one, though.</p>
<p>Always has been.</p>
<p>Always will be.</p>
<p>Trust is earned over time, lost in a second.</p>
<p>But a shortcut to gaining a person's trust is to have their back.</p>
<p>Use this information for pure purposes only.</p>
<p>Good looking out.</p>
<p></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Got A Sec?</title>
        <author>
            <name>杻백</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/got-a-sec/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/got-a-sec/</id>

        <updated>2025-12-16T13:05:35-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    You ever talk to someone, and they are coming to you&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>You ever talk to someone, and they are coming to you for advice, and you realize, pretty quickly, that they are only there to hear your affirmation?</p>
<p>Meaning, if you disagree, and give honest feedback, they are put off?</p>
<p><em>No, no, no. You don't see. You aren't agreeing with me. [Face twitches]. Not six minute abs! Seven!</em></p>
<p>So the feedback becomes a fight.</p>
<p>I have an easy solution for that.</p>
<p>But a slightly harder solution is to realize that a lot of folks (when they say they want feedback and your "honest" opinion) are just really saying, "You agree with me, right?"</p>
<p>Right?</p>
<p>Of course, they have evolved. And some now exist solely to anger you.</p>
<p>They expect disagreement.</p>
<p>Hoping you care enough to disagree.</p>
<p>And they love it.</p>
<p>In fact, one of the most effective ways to gather a following is to anger people.</p>
<p>They want you to disagree.</p>
<p>Because engagement, wrestling the pig, gets the hog paid.</p>
<p>So now, not only do we have jabronis looking only for agreement, we got other jabronis looking for a scrap, if only behind a "smart" phone.</p>
<p>So, contrary to popular opinion, I just choose not to engage.</p>
<p>I choose not to run!</p>
<p>Did you know that if your social media feeds are full of ragebait, it's because they know you love it?</p>
<p>While you sit there angry, stewing, scrolling to more anger, you are being absolutely fed what you respond to.</p>
<p>Now, if it's going the other way, the Kumbaya way, well you're probably only getting the affirmation you have been secretly seeking (like when you talk to ai).</p>
<p>You want my advice?</p>
<p>I have the answer.</p>
<p>And it's just so simple a solution, it's elegant.</p>
<p>[Phone rings]</p>
<p>[Phone displays "Suspected Spam"]</p>
<p>I gotta take this.</p>
<p>"What? The prince of where? Prince Whozit? Well, I always got time for royalty!"</p>
<p>[Points to phone, mouths to you, "Prince Whozit!"]</p>
<p>[You leave the room, as confused as ever. The author beams.]</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>True Wuv</title>
        <author>
            <name>杻백</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/true-wuv/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/true-wuv/</id>

        <updated>2025-12-15T12:29:44-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    I don't know what to say today. Somedays it be that&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I don't know what to say today.</p>
<p>Somedays it be that way.</p>
<p>I will say I love <em>The Princess Bride</em>, aka <em>The Revenge Tale of Inigo Montoya</em>.</p>
<p>Seems like a good day to say that.</p>
<p>In a movie full of quotable lines, the ones I like to say the most (even, especially, today) are those morsels of art cooked up by Andre the Giant.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Why are you wearing a mask? Were you burned by acid or something like that?</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Maybe it's because I grew up watching the old MSG network in NYC, and every couple of months they'd air a World Wrestling Federation house show live from Madison Square Garden.</p>
<p>And, if I was lucky, it'd get to see Andre.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>My way is not very sportsmanlike.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Seeing the Giant as a nice guy (for a Brute Squad member) was a nice surprise for a kid watching him beat up Hulk Hogan.</p>
<p>I didn't appreciate this movie as a love story as a kid. I was fixated on Inigo enacting his vengeance. Having fun storming the castle. To me, it was all about the action.</p>
<p>But it is.</p>
<p>It is a love story.</p>
<p>And, as we say in our home, every story is a love story.</p>
<p>You could call this one a story about true love.</p>
<p>You could call it a story of a son's love for his father.</p>
<p>You could call it a story about a grandfather's love for his grandson.</p>
<p>And you'd be right.</p>
<p>The way this movie ends is not, as we see, how the real deal goes sometimes.</p>
<p>But I'm going to keep this one light.</p>
<p>Out of respect for the fallen and those that remain.</p>
<p>In memory of the gentle sportsman, the awfully misunderstood Vizzini (the character, not the actor!), and the guy that directed them.</p>
<p><em>Memento</em> <em>vivere</em>, friends.</p>
<p></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
