<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>Iterating</title>
    <link href="https://iterating.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://iterating.com" />
    <updated>2025-12-19T13:25:43-05:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>AL8X</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://iterating.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Statues of Golden Marble</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/statues-of-marble/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/statues-of-marble/</id>

        <updated>2025-12-19T13:18:12-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    You know, there's this idea that we are all born with&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>You know, there's this idea that we are all born with limitless potential.</p>
<p>Or at least a maximum potential.</p>
<p>And that things that happen to you over time slowly (or quickly) chop away at it.</p>
<p>Nothing increases your potential (it was always there), but lots of things can knock it down.</p>
<p>And I wrestle with this a bit.</p>
<p>I mean, I think I agree.</p>
<p>But it's sort of a downer, right?</p>
<p>You wonder how many good souls have been smashed by their lives.</p>
<p>How many beautiful things turned ugly simply by being born, raised, and lived in a certain place, in a certain time, around a certain person.</p>
<p>It's the whole nature versus nurture thing.</p>
<p>Some of us are born animals, but a lot of us stay wild. Or are turned it. I'm not sure which. Probably both.</p>
<p>Or even worse, they became domesticated.</p>
<p>And so, I now look at the vast potential of youth. And think: How do I best preserve their infinite/maximum potential? </p>
<p>As a man who believes I'd rather my loved ones be safe than sorry, I wrestle with the balance of how fun it is to take risks and challenge yourself versus keeping them out of danger (which is also somewhat dangerous).</p>
<p>How do I teach failure is ok, necessary even, when it hurts their tender heart?</p>
<p>How do I not chop away?</p>
<p>Must I chop away?</p>
<p>How do I keep them perfect?</p>
<p>Can I keep them perfect?</p>
<p>I can see now, I was chopped away at. Over time. Over decades.</p>
<p>I was a big block of rock.</p>
<p>I'd like to think I'm more chiseled now. A sculpture.</p>
<p>Work of art or some ess.</p>
<p>But I was more beautiful as a child.</p>
<p>Who cannot say that?</p>
<p>I'm sorry if you cannot say that.</p>
<p>My job then, is to learn what chops down, and what doesn't.</p>
<p>I think I know.</p>
<p>But like all things, I have to go back.</p>
<p>In the 90s, one of my heroes was Lee Haney, a bodybuilding icon. And I remember watching him train. And he was a funny dude for a big mamma jamma and he'd always repeat this line, even while hoisting comically large amounts of iron, as to how how to get bigger:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>"Stimulate, don't annihilate, amateur!"</p>
</blockquote>
<p>And I think that's it.</p>
<p>I think that's the key.</p>
<p>To turning pro.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Pow Pow</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/pow-pow/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/pow-pow/</id>

        <updated>2025-12-18T14:05:18-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    You ever write something and then just erase it? I wrote&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>You ever write something and then just erase it?</p>
<p>I wrote paragraphs here and just didn't like it.</p>
<p>I suppose everyone does that but I usually don't.</p>
<p>I just write and tinker and keep writing. </p>
<p>It probably shows.</p>
<p>This whole writing thing is a part of me, part of who I am, and it is one of the things I thought I had lost, but I'm finding again.</p>
<p>So many things have changed for me in the past few years, so I am happy to say I am able to write again.</p>
<p>Writing feels like such a selfish thing. And with my time at a premium, it felt like a waste of valuable minutes when I could be, should be, focusing on other things.</p>
<p>But like with <span style="text-decoration: line-through;">really, really few, almost never really,</span>many things, I was wrong.</p>
<p>I've learned that a little bit of typing time is a wonderful thing.</p>
<p>It amplifies the rest of my day.</p>
<p>Maybe by turning gears, removing cobwebs, warming me up. Who knows.</p>
<p>I'm starting to think, "Oh, I should write about that."</p>
<p>So thanks for that, digital notebook made by a fruit, for letting me do just that. Too many thats.</p>
<p>There's memories in my muscles. My fingers. And tapping them repetitively on little squares have helped me in more ways than I could have imagined.</p>
<p>A return to first principles.</p>
<p>Start from the foundation.</p>
<p>One tap at a time.</p>
<p>1.</p>
<p>2.</p>
<p>3.</p>
<p>Unlocking levels long forgotten. </p>
<p>Unlocking levels yet to attain.</p>
<p>I'm rereading books and learning how much I had missed the first few times around. Seeing the whole world through these new, old, lenses.</p>
<p>And how much <em>perspective</em> has to do with everyone and everything.</p>
<p>I don't know what I'm getting at.</p>
<p>I'm just glad I get to write.</p>
<p>[Finger guns!]</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Watch My Six</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/watch-my-six/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/watch-my-six/</id>

        <updated>2025-12-17T11:58:54-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    "You got my back?" "Hell yeah." Back in the day, this&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <blockquote>
<p>"You got my back?"</p>
<p>"Hell yeah."</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Back in the day, this is all that mattered when determining your truest friends.</p>
<p>It's how you measured them.</p>
<p>That when it went down, and it always eventually would, some people would stay and others would run.</p>
<p>And it wasn't always who you thought it would be.</p>
<p>Both ways.</p>
<p>I've had friends run the second (before) it got hot.</p>
<p>And I've had bare acquaintances defend my honor without a second thought.</p>
<p>It's just who they were.</p>
<p>There till the end.</p>
<p>These people quickly switched places.</p>
<p>If only in my heart.</p>
<p>I used to work at a place where they would repeat certain phrases. Mantras. Things they thought wise. Witty.</p>
<p>One of them was, "If someone tells you who they are, believe them."</p>
<p>Which I always thought was the dumbest thing I had ever heard in my life.</p>
<p>People lie all the time.</p>
<p>Tell you how great they are and all that feces.</p>
<p>But you see, I was wrong.</p>
<p>For the saying is based on people telling you who they are through their <em>actions</em>, not their words.</p>
<p>You hope that actions and words mean the same thing, and ideally they do, but your experience should show you how this just isn't so.</p>
<p>Look around you.</p>
<p>Who's the nice person pretending to be a jerk?</p>
<p>And who's the jerk pretending to be a nice person?</p>
<p>Now, I'll be the first one to tell you that if you watch your back too much, you'll take an uppercut to the jaw when you turn around.</p>
<p>Keep your head on a swivel. </p>
<p>This is why it's important to have people around you that you can absolutely trust.</p>
<p>Such a list is a short one, though.</p>
<p>Always has been.</p>
<p>Always will be.</p>
<p>Trust is earned over time, lost in a second.</p>
<p>But a shortcut to gaining a person's trust is to have their back.</p>
<p>Use this information for pure purposes only.</p>
<p>Good looking out.</p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Got A Sec?</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/got-a-sec/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/got-a-sec/</id>

        <updated>2025-12-16T13:05:35-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    You ever talk to someone, and they are coming to you&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>You ever talk to someone, and they are coming to you for advice, and you realize, pretty quickly, that they are only there to hear your affirmation?</p>
<p>Meaning, if you disagree, and give honest feedback, they are put off?</p>
<p><em>No, no, no. You don't see. You aren't agreeing with me. [Face twitches]. Not six minute abs! Seven!</em></p>
<p>So the feedback becomes a fight.</p>
<p>I have an easy solution for that.</p>
<p>But a slightly harder solution is to realize that a lot of folks (when they say they want feedback and your "honest" opinion) are just really saying, "You agree with me, right?"</p>
<p>Right?</p>
<p>Of course, they have evolved. And some now exist solely to anger you.</p>
<p>They expect disagreement.</p>
<p>Hoping you care enough to disagree.</p>
<p>And they love it.</p>
<p>In fact, one of the most effective ways to gather a following is to anger people.</p>
<p>They want you to disagree. </p>
<p>Because engagement, wrestling the pig, gets the hog paid.</p>
<p>So now, not only do we have jabronis looking only for agreement, we got other jabronis looking for a scrap, if only behind a "smart" phone.</p>
<p>So, contrary to popular opinion, I just choose not to engage.</p>
<p>I choose not to run!</p>
<p>Did you know that if your social media feeds are full of ragebait, it's because they know you love it?</p>
<p>While you sit there angry, stewing, scrolling to more anger, you are being absolutely fed what you respond to.</p>
<p>Now, if it's going the other way, the Kumbaya way, well you're probably only getting the affirmation you have been secretly seeking (like when you talk to ai).</p>
<p>You want my advice?</p>
<p>I have the answer.</p>
<p>And it's just so simple a solution, it's elegant.</p>
<p>[Phone rings]</p>
<p>[Phone displays "Suspected Spam"]</p>
<p>I gotta take this.</p>
<p>"What? The prince of where? Prince Whozit? Well, I always got time for royalty!"</p>
<p>[Points to phone, mouths to you, "Prince Whozit!"]</p>
<p>[You leave the room, as confused as ever. The author beams.]</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>True Wuv</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/true-wuv/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/true-wuv/</id>

        <updated>2025-12-15T12:29:44-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    I don't know what to say today. Somedays it be that&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I don't know what to say today.</p>
<p>Somedays it be that way.</p>
<p>I will say I love <em>The Princess Bride</em>, aka <em>The Revenge Tale of Inigo Montoya</em>.</p>
<p>Seems like a good day to say that.</p>
<p>In a movie full of quotable lines, the ones I like to say the most (even, especially, today) are those morsels of art cooked up by Andre the Giant.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Why are you wearing a mask? Were you burned by acid or something like that?</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Maybe it's because I grew up watching the old MSG network in NYC, and every couple of months they'd air a World Wrestling Federation house show live from Madison Square Garden.</p>
<p>And, if I was lucky, it'd get to see Andre.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>My way is not very sportsmanlike.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Seeing the Giant as a nice guy (for a Brute Squad member) was a nice surprise for a kid watching him beat up Hulk Hogan.</p>
<p>I didn't appreciate this movie as a love story as a kid. I was fixated on Inigo enacting his vengeance. Having fun storming the castle. To me, it was all about the action.</p>
<p>But it is.</p>
<p>It is a love story.</p>
<p>And, as we say in our home, every story is a love story.</p>
<p>You could call this one a story about true love.</p>
<p>You could call it a story of a son's love for his father.</p>
<p>You could call it a story about a grandfather's love for his grandson.</p>
<p>And you'd be right.</p>
<p>The way this movie ends is not, as we see, how the real deal goes sometimes.</p>
<p>But I'm going to keep this one light.</p>
<p>Out of respect for the fallen and those that remain.</p>
<p>In memory of the gentle sportsman, the awfully misunderstood Vizzini (the character, not the actor!), and the guy that directed them.</p>
<p><em>Memento</em> <em>vivere</em>, friends.</p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Sidearming Steaks</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/sidearming-steaks/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/sidearming-steaks/</id>

        <updated>2025-12-14T18:12:31-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    I got this theory. About pro football. I call it "The&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I got this theory.</p>
<p>About pro football.</p>
<p>I call it "The curse of the decent quarterback."</p>
<p>And it goes a little something like this:</p>
<p>Teams that find a decent quarterback are cursed to play them for a decade, to middling success at best.</p>
<p>A good enough quarterback, I argue, only gives good enough results, not a ring. But they're too good to let go. So you keep them. And you never win it all.</p>
<p>That's my theory.</p>
<p>So what would I do if I were running a pro team?</p>
<p>Glad you asked.</p>
<p>I'd do weird ess like draft a QB every year, even if I think we've got a winner already.</p>
<p>Just stack 'em.</p>
<p>Have the best backup in the league. And the best 3rd string. Always.</p>
<p>Even draft 1st round QBs in consecutive years. Maybe three in a row. Get them rookie contracts on the cheap.</p>
<p>Heck, I might draft a QB in every round one year.</p>
<p>Or, <em>better yet</em>, forget drafting QBs at all.</p>
<p><em>Never</em> waste a single draft pick on a QB.</p>
<p>Instead, sign those quarterbacks considered "busts" by their first teams, even second or third. Just round them all up. Treat free agency, waiver wire, and trades as your draft. And just pile 'em up.</p>
<p>Why not?</p>
<p>With that understood, then I'd focus on the offensive line. Then all defense. And lastly, the skill players.</p>
<p>I won't insult any QB by naming them, I think you know what I mean if you watched for any length of time. It's such an important position in today's game that you must get the decision right. And then when you do, protect it at all costs. Even if you have to keep competition flowing by bringing in their heir apparents yearly.</p>
<p>Have the QB feel like he's got to earn the starting role every game, because he does.</p>
<p>I'm not a one trick pony, though. </p>
<p>I got other ideas. </p>
<p>Like how we should make draft combine participants run the 40 yard dash in full gear. Helmets and pads and all.</p>
<p>To get a truer gauge of game speed.</p>
<p>You like that shee, right?</p>
<p>Of course, this is all just from the mind of a old(ish) flag football cornerback who just so happened to have a Rico Dynamite cannon for an arm.</p>
<p>But from my armchair, it's as clear as a Preston, Idaho winter sky.</p>
<p>Now, where's Jon Gruden when I need him?</p>
<blockquote>
<p>"Coach, I got this theory..."</p>
</blockquote>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Wont</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/wont/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/wont/</id>

        <updated>2025-12-13T00:26:27-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Writing while tired is a silly, dangerous, thing. So I won't.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Writing while tired is a silly, dangerous, thing.</p>
<p>So I won't.</p>
<p>But let me just say, it's pretty cool to write tired.</p>
<p>You just ramble and ramble and hope maybe something worth something will tumble out.</p>
<p>Of course, that's how I write every day.</p>
<p>I don't like hosting, but we're hosting this weekend. So I'm writing early.</p>
<p>Just in case.</p>
<p>This writing every day thing has become important to me. </p>
<p>Even though this is my second writing, it counts as the next day, technically.</p>
<p>So the streak continues.</p>
<p>Hermit don't like hosting. Hermit only like to do what he like to do. Hermit curmudgeon. Hermit need sleep.</p>
<p>Goodnight.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Raining &#x27;Bows</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/raining-bows/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/raining-bows/</id>

        <updated>2025-12-12T15:57:54-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    I'm still working through this idea that the secret to life&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I'm still working through this idea that the secret to life is noticing, feeling, living the magic of everyday moments.</p>
<p>Of making the routine feel elevated.</p>
<p>Of seeing heaven in a favorite song.</p>
<p>I think that's the whole point of this [<em>waves hands around chaotically</em>] thing.</p>
<p>You know?</p>
<p>We get 30,000 sunsets (give or take). </p>
<p>30,000 golden hours right before.</p>
<p>Each one magical.</p>
<p>Each one sacred.</p>
<p>If you want them to be.</p>
<p>I took for granted growing up in the city.</p>
<p>I never looked <em>up</em>.</p>
<p>And now, when I see skyscrapers, I stare in awe like a tourist.</p>
<p>How they block out the skyline because they <em>are</em> the skyline.</p>
<p>How creatures just like us made them.</p>
<p>From the ground up.</p>
<p>I'll leave it to you whether skyscrapers are a good thing or a bad thing.</p>
<p>But they are a pretty amazing display of what humans can do.</p>
<p>I feel that way about redwood trees, too. Except we didn't make those.</p>
<p>I heard a long time ago that we lose just as much as we gain by learning how a rainbow is made.</p>
<p>And I suppose most think it's easier to be awed when you're young, naive, or just foolish.</p>
<p>But it's true (about the rainbow).</p>
<p>Sometimes boiling it down to textbook "science" takes a bit of the beauty away. Takes away the "that which cannot be said." Takes away the magic. Because you know how the trick is done.</p>
<p>Rainbows are magnificent.</p>
<p>So are small humans that have half your genes (Lord help us) and half your love's (thank God).</p>
<p>And so is Robin Williams (especially in his dramatic roles).</p>
<p>And countless other things we experience routinely.</p>
<p>We just get used to it all.</p>
<p>So here's to never getting used to it.</p>
<p>To keeping it forever fresh.</p>
<p>Groundhog day is life for most. </p>
<p>Over and over.</p>
<p>Same same same.</p>
<p>Is that a blessing or a curse?</p>
<p>Is nothing sacred?</p>
<p>Or is everything?</p>
<p>I made my choice.</p>
<p>What you doing?</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Double rainbow!!!</p>
</blockquote>
<p>These are what we stay alive for.</p>
<p>Aye aye, Captain.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Space Lord Mother Mother</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/space-lord-mother-mother/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/space-lord-mother-mother/</id>

        <updated>2025-12-11T11:35:23-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Psst. Hey you. Yeah, I'm talking to you. Get over here.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Psst.</p>
<p>Hey you.</p>
<p>Yeah, I'm talking to you.</p>
<p>Get over here.</p>
<p>Listen.</p>
<p>Listen.</p>
<p>There's some stuff that happened this year that has probably blown your mind.</p>
<p>But guess what?</p>
<p>Next year will be just as weird.</p>
<p>Maybe weirder.</p>
<p>Just like every year coming and every year since.</p>
<p>Sure, maybe its got on a new outfit or shade of makeup.</p>
<p>But it's all the same.</p>
<p>Unless aliens come from a rock rocket.</p>
<p>That would be different.</p>
<p>I joked with my wife: "What if they (the aliens) put in their starfaring flight to Earth, their dumbest, most disposable representative(s) they could find?" </p>
<p>Their planet's idiot(s).</p>
<p>Just because they didn't want to lose anyone important.</p>
<p>Not for something as trivial as a flight to our solar system.</p>
<p>And these fools from the sky come down to say hello.</p>
<p>And we humans and our world leaders race to greet them. With records of gold detailing our efforts. Maybe some even on the ground. On their knees.</p>
<p>And these aliens are like, "Woah. Cool."</p>
<p>While we deify them.</p>
<p>Or kill them.</p>
<p>50/50.</p>
<p>Same same.</p>
<p>What would be better: Aliens sending their very best or their very worst?</p>
<p>In my tale, they send their dumbest.</p>
<p>And hilarity ensues.</p>
<p>Or tragedy.</p>
<p>Which will get funnier over time.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Imp Patient</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/imp-patient/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/imp-patient/</id>

        <updated>2025-12-10T11:48:54-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    For a guy who almost died who still plays the long&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>For a guy who almost died who still plays the long game (I think), I'm understandably sort of impatient.</p>
<p>I mean, I can delay gratification, delegate, lead, and all that bull mess, but what I mean is that window of time after the deal is done where you are waiting for everything to wrap up and close.</p>
<p>The shipping time.</p>
<p>The transfer time.</p>
<p>The results of your efforts time.</p>
<p>The when you can call it complete time.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Put a bow on it!</p>
</blockquote>
<p>But it's always been that way. </p>
<p>Studying for the bar exam sooooked. Taking the bar sucked. </p>
<p>But waiting six months(!) for the results?</p>
<p>Worst of all <em>by far</em>.</p>
<p>Why? I think it's the <em>out of my control </em>part. The <em>what if</em> part. The <strong><em>not knowing</em></strong> part.</p>
<p>Give me a bunch of things I can do to prepare and get it done, a mountain of them (please don't), and it'll get done. But once it's fate is in someone else's hands, I suppose that drives me a <em>little</em> crazy.</p>
<p>What's taking so long?</p>
<p>Do they need something else?</p>
<p>Was I unclear?</p>
<p>There's a snow storm in the rust belt. Is that why its delayed?</p>
<p>This is a part of young me (Yung Mi?) that I carry today in my back pocket.</p>
<p>And while I've done enough to discipline that boy over the years, he still shows his face every once in awhile.</p>
<p>And the holidays with all its over-promising and under-delivering, well it's enough to make an old man shake his fist in the sky and throw punches at the sun.</p>
<p>No old men here, though.</p>
<p>Just hurry up already.</p>
<p>[Shakes fist at screen.]</p>
<p>Yung Mi yaaa, what are you going to do when you grow up?</p>
<p>Coffee's for closers, you know.</p>
<p>Just crank up <em>Enter Sandman</em> and brew me a cup.</p>
<p>I'm just getting warmed up.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
