<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>Iterating</title>
    <link href="https://iterating.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://iterating.com" />
    <updated>2026-01-20T14:00:51-05:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>𖤂</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://iterating.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Alpha Omega</title>
        <author>
            <name>𖤂</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/alpha-omega/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/alpha-omega/</id>

        <updated>2026-01-20T13:52:54-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    I believe in every day sacralization. To make every day, every&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I believe in every day sacralization. </p>
<p>To make every day, every moment, something beyond sacred.</p>
<p>Beyond holy.</p>
<p>This is, of course, easier said than done.</p>
<p>But it's good to have nice goals.</p>
<p>Another goal I'm narrowing down on is this idea of an Apex Opus.</p>
<p>It's my play on magnum opus, but even more unique.</p>
<p>The pinnacle work.</p>
<p>Your highest success.</p>
<p>And while I see it as an integral part of raising a family and leading your tribe, I also wonder if it could be something more distilled, more concrete, even if non-analog.</p>
<p>Magnum opuses are works of art or books.</p>
<p>What about apex opuses?</p>
<p>I'm not sure yet.</p>
<p>A word (or more), a drawing, a human being (or three), a creation of some form that you made or transformed with your own bare mind and hands.</p>
<p>As I believe that we will all be remembered most for a snapshot in time (hopefully in the Best of Times), I also believe that we will be honored for our best work.</p>
<p>At least, ideally.</p>
<p>If you're a crook, folks tend to remember you at your worst. For your worst actions. For your worst work.</p>
<p>But let's try to avoid that.</p>
<p>Let's go the other way.</p>
<p>A 180.</p>
<p>And try to be remembered at our best.</p>
<p>At our highest.</p>
<p>At our grandest.</p>
<p>At our apex.</p>
<p>Now, for most of you, I have really good news.</p>
<p>You haven't hit your peak yet.</p>
<p>But I have some less good news.</p>
<p>You have to start working on your apex opus.</p>
<p>Wait, that sounds like excellent news.</p>
<p>It doesn't have to become well-known, if the only person who benefits is you, I call that a win.</p>
<p>But start to think about it.</p>
<p>Who are you?</p>
<p>What are you about?</p>
<p>And what will you be at your highest point?</p>
<p>Show your work.</p>
<p>And what you show will be proof you were here.</p>
<p>And that you made something of yourself.</p>
<p>And if no one else will applaud, well, you can count on at least one pair of hands.</p>
<p>Not me, though. </p>
<p>Probably your umma.</p>
<p>I'm like Tony Danza ova here.</p>
<p>AO.</p>
<p>OA.</p>
<p>Al out.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Apex Opus</title>
        <author>
            <name>𖤂</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/apex-opus/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/apex-opus/</id>

        <updated>2026-01-19T16:22:32-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Today is like a second Sunday. It feels like that to&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Today is like a second Sunday.</p>
<p>It feels like that to me.</p>
<p>And so, I don't want to write too much, because I already did.</p>
<p>But here's something interesting.</p>
<p>In a good life, I think that having a <em>magnum opus</em> is essential.</p>
<p>Having a great work.</p>
<p>Having made something of tremendous value.</p>
<p>If only for yourself. And your loved ones.</p>
<p>An impact.</p>
<p>But even more important is having an <em>apex opus</em>.</p>
<p>Your highest work.</p>
<p>Your grandmasterpiece.</p>
<p>Your verse.</p>
<p>As in, what will be the headline on your obituary?</p>
<p>And I mean that in a good way.</p>
<p>In the best way.</p>
<p>I am iterating on this big idea.</p>
<p>To dreams.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Don of Kings </title>
        <author>
            <name>𖤂</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/don-of-kings/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/don-of-kings/</id>

        <updated>2026-01-18T17:50:21-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    I interrupt this musings column with the following: Why hasn't anyone&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I interrupt this musings column with the following:</p>
<p>Why hasn't anyone told me about chess boxing?</p>
<p>You know, the hybrid sport that alternates rounds of boxing and chess?</p>
<p>Aka the Sport of the Future?</p>
<p><em>60 Minutes</em> did a feature on it a couple of months ago.</p>
<p>It's huge in Russia (I think). Has been for years (I think).</p>
<p>And I'm just hearing about it now.</p>
<p>Brains and brawn.</p>
<p>Hooks and rooks (stole that from the <em>60M</em> segment, but it's pretty good!).</p>
<p>Perfect for a nerd who can fight (sorta).</p>
<p>Or a fighter who can nerd out (sorta).</p>
<p>Aka, <em>my people</em>.</p>
<p>You can have your pickles and balls.</p>
<p>Feast on 'em.</p>
<p>I found my old man sport.</p>
<p>♟🥊</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Tango and Cash</title>
        <author>
            <name>𖤂</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/tango-and-cash/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/tango-and-cash/</id>

        <updated>2026-01-18T11:32:38-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    The dance to life is a delicate one. And by that&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>The dance to life is a delicate one.</p>
<p>And by that I mean spectrums.</p>
<p>A large part of leading a family is to know the balance between protecting them and also letting them learn lessons the hard way (for themselves).</p>
<p>And the trick is, I think, to protect them from the hardest or perhaps I should say harshest lessons.</p>
<p>And what's the harshest?</p>
<p>I'm not sure.</p>
<p>Maybe it is <em>true</em> heartbreak?</p>
<p>Or worse yet, staying in love with the wrong person?</p>
<p>Is it addiction?</p>
<p>Illness?</p>
<p>I think we have all learned enough to know that precaution has its own dangers.</p>
<p>There is danger in being safe.</p>
<p>And safety in being dangerous.</p>
<p>And thus, everything is a sliding scale.</p>
<p>And I search for that perfect balance.</p>
<p>Failure isn't bad. It took me a long time to learn that.</p>
<p>Failure is necessarily implied to make accomplishment feel earned.</p>
<p>If you are guaranteed a win, you will take it for granted.</p>
<p>Who wants to hit 1.000?</p>
<p>You think you do, but you really don't.</p>
<p>But stacking failure on top of another on top of another, that's when things get rough.</p>
<p>So that's one, to protect those you lead from the spiral failures.</p>
<p>Sidenote: Work on not being right. Or at least, not feeling some sort of weird mix of vindication ("I told you so") and validation when you caution and warn and then it happens. You can almost see it coming. They can't. You cannot rewind, but memory is a great teacher, and you hope they remember how often you seem to know what you're talking about. Even and especially before it happens.</p>
<p>I don't rely on people changing. </p>
<p>I change.</p>
<p>Either my angle or my position.</p>
<p>Some mistakes are unforgivable.</p>
<p>At least by me.</p>
<p>Protect your loved ones from those.</p>
<p>And so that's the dance.</p>
<p>It seems delicate, but upon reflection there's a lot of room on the dance floor.</p>
<p>There's a lot of space to play.</p>
<p>But all the fun's at the edges.</p>
<p>And thus, we dance.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>New You. Save?</title>
        <author>
            <name>𖤂</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/new-you-save/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/new-you-save/</id>

        <updated>2026-01-17T17:12:22-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    I don't play video games anymore (my game is writing), but&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I don't play video games anymore (my game is writing), but I still love them.</p>
<p>One of my favorite parts of video games is in its character creation.</p>
<p>Whether sports or RPG, it better have create mode down and deep.</p>
<p>I'd spend hours getting the details right.</p>
<p>Starting from their name, their look, their attributes.</p>
<p>Nerds understand.</p>
<p>I had to get it <em>juuuuuuuust</em> right.</p>
<p>Goldilocks right.</p>
<p>And this was usually before you even started playing the game!</p>
<p>And it makes me wonder, why we don't do that for the video game called Life.</p>
<p>I mean, who spends hours (let alone years) on our own character creation?</p>
<p>At least with that lens?</p>
<p>I've joked before that we all need real life character sheets (not CVs or resumes), but I think I'm onto something.</p>
<p>We need to spend more time on character creation, on who we want to be, than we do.</p>
<p>So that's what I'll leave you with today.</p>
<p>Go into "new game" or "continue game" (as appropriate) and see if you can create or edit your character.</p>
<p>And while you can spend hours finding the right eyebrows, I'd encourage you to spend some time on your mental attributes and skills. </p>
<p>Want to boost wisdom? Perhaps you look into stoicism.</p>
<p>Want to save money? The world is your oyster (make more than you spend).</p>
<p>Want to boost charisma? Well, look no further, champ.</p>
<p>[Smiling. Eyes wide open. Not blinking. Direct eye contact. Blink first, dammit.]</p>
<p>I'm just saying, most of us grown-ups stop with the character creation part of our own stories. We leave it all for the digital world.</p>
<p>And that's just silly.</p>
<p>I'm beginning to understand now that the old grandmasters didn't start out as young grandmasters. </p>
<p>They grew into it.</p>
<p>And that's sort of what I would like to do.</p>
<p>Grow into an old grandmaster character.</p>
<p>Although there is not much use for old grandmasters, as I knew it, so I think I'll edit it to being a more kinder, gentler, more useful old grand<em>mentor</em>.</p>
<p>A mentor of mentors.</p>
<p>Now, I just need to find the right shade of shimmery silver hair to compliment my glowing golden skin. </p>
<p>Be back in a few hours.</p>
<p>Create your character.</p>
<p>Create your life.</p>
<p>Create a new game.</p>
<p>Save.</p>
<p>[Returns a few hours later, full of shimmer and glow. Surprised to see you still sitting there. Doesn't sell it. Pretends to not see you. Gathers a few things. Leaves room. Turns off light. <em>I...I should probably head</em>, you say to yourself, as you sit blissfully in the dark, thinking about the right elbow accessory to equip that screams YOU when you get home.]</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>The Donger Need Food</title>
        <author>
            <name>𖤂</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/the-donger-need-food/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/the-donger-need-food/</id>

        <updated>2026-01-16T11:46:25-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Is it better to write with an empty stomach or a&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Is it better to write with an empty stomach or a full one?</p>
<p>I am wrestling with this right now.</p>
<p>The topic: Optimal belly input for optimal writing output.</p>
<p>It's probably like most things, the answer is probably somewhere in between.</p>
<p>After a light meal. As you nibble on a nice snack.</p>
<p>Or a few hours digesting a feast.</p>
<p>Right now, I got a meatloaf meal in my belly.</p>
<p>Meat.</p>
<p>Loaf.</p>
<p>Poetic.</p>
<p>A rare non-kimchi meal.</p>
<p>But it's been known to happen.</p>
<p>And boy, am I full, but I'm not sure I can write to my best ability.</p>
<p>The Donger need nap.</p>
<p>The Donger need write.</p>
<p>Of course, there is no perfect time to write or anything else.</p>
<p>Only windows of opportunity.</p>
<p>So this is mine.</p>
<p>I sits.</p>
<p>I writes.</p>
<p>I do not consider this a chore.</p>
<p>Which surprises me.</p>
<p>Having to do this thing every day.</p>
<p>But I am increasingly treating this as almost like another meal.</p>
<p>I have to eat.</p>
<p>I have to write.</p>
<p>Or, better put:</p>
<p>I get to eat.</p>
<p>I get to write.</p>
<p>A privilege.</p>
<p>Because that is what it is.</p>
<p>Now, I'm not always bringing the heat.</p>
<p>Somedays, I'm throwing change-ups and sliders.</p>
<p>This is probably my eephus.</p>
<p>But I'm smiling. </p>
<p>Belly full.</p>
<p>Floating a few inches off the ground.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Strike Three!</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Got 'em.</p>
<p>PS: If you ever call me "The Donger" that's a nut punch right there. Maybe two.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>All Others Pay</title>
        <author>
            <name>𖤂</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/all-others-pay/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/all-others-pay/</id>

        <updated>2026-01-15T14:51:56-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Everyone knocks lawyers until they need one. And sometimes even then.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Everyone knocks lawyers until they need one.</p>
<p>And sometimes even then.</p>
<p>But that's true with lots of things. </p>
<p>Haters gonna hate.</p>
<p>Like this rise of "decentralized" things.</p>
<p>No middle men.</p>
<p>No oversight!</p>
<p>No permission!!</p>
<p>PURE FREEDOM!!!</p>
<p>Except, when they lose everything, they want a recourse.</p>
<p>They want justice!</p>
<p>And they are confused that no one can help them.</p>
<p>Why?</p>
<p>Because they didn't bake in the fact that no oversight comes with big downsides. Pure freedom rarely leads to order. Free justice is self-enforced. Often meaning you have no ability to right many wrongs.</p>
<p>One of the legal tenets of truly owning something is that your ownership right is recognized and defended by a <em>mature</em> body and system of law.</p>
<p>Someone wrongs you, you have the ability to fight back with the law.</p>
<p>And I'm seeing so many stories involving crypto scams where the only lesson is a cautionary one.</p>
<p>Hogs slaughtered.</p>
<p>And many are like, "Why isn't anyone helping me?"</p>
<p>Well, this is part of what they signed up for.</p>
<p>No one can help.</p>
<p>All of this is still new, relatively speaking, and more regulation and rules are kinda the antithesis of this movement.</p>
<p>So how do you own things in this decentralized future?</p>
<p>In many ways, it's caveman era stuff.</p>
<p>Protect your own.</p>
<p>Survive.</p>
<p>Brutal.</p>
<p>Me?</p>
<p>I like having a system of accountability.</p>
<p>I like ownership rights.</p>
<p>I don't necessarily trust all authority, but I do trust some, especially those that have my back.</p>
<p>More than I trust someone who says they can get rich quick and they can show me how to do it too.</p>
<p>More than I trust some of these folks who treat this as a religion or as a way to save the world.</p>
<p>It's not either, man. It's just money or something like it.</p>
<p>I knew something was off with this whole decentralized thing when they said the best way to technologically secure and future-proof your stuff was to write it all down on paper. Not on your computer!</p>
<p>Never your computer!</p>
<p>Paper!</p>
<p>Or hammer it on metal!</p>
<p>Or these little devices that do not connect to the internet, promise!</p>
<p>Trust!</p>
<p>Trust no one, they say, except you have to trust those selling you this stuff.</p>
<p>You have to trust them.</p>
<p>"You can trust us in a trust-no-one world."</p>
<p>Trust us so you don't have to trust anyone (else).</p>
<p>And so the irony of a trustless world is you still have to trust those who are hocking its wares and thumping its bible.</p>
<p>You have to trust their trustless stuff.</p>
<p>And that's the hard part.</p>
<p>"Trust no one, except all of us. We are telling the truth. And we wouldn't ever think of stealing your stuff."</p>
<p>Sounds familiar.</p>
<p>But what do I know?</p>
<p>DTA.</p>
<p>Don't trust anybody.</p>
<p>Even me.</p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Luck Factory</title>
        <author>
            <name>𖤂</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/luck-factory/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/luck-factory/</id>

        <updated>2026-01-14T12:02:03-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    How do you define luck? Success by chance rather than by&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>How do you define luck?</p>
<p>Success by chance rather than by specific action.</p>
<p>Have you ever met someone who was unlucky?</p>
<p>Someone who just couldn't seem to catch a break?</p>
<p>Stacking Ls like school chairs.</p>
<p>Eeyores.</p>
<p>And what about the other way?</p>
<p>You ever meet someone who just seemed to have a good luck charm in their taped fist?</p>
<p>My wife says I could fall in poop (her version is different) and still come out smelling like roses.</p>
<p>Which is a wonderful analogy (except the first part).</p>
<p>And yes, I do seem to fail upwards.</p>
<p>Always have.</p>
<p>I've always considered myself blessed.</p>
<p>Even when I almost died.</p>
<p><em>Especially</em> when I almost died.</p>
<p>Because I have lived a good life.</p>
<p>Not an easy life, but a good one.</p>
<p>And I just felt and feel so lucky about it all.</p>
<p>In almost all metrics, I have overachieved.</p>
<p>Which is strange because anyone who knows me knows I'm an underachiever.</p>
<p>And if you know anything about me, it should be that.</p>
<p>I'm an overachieving underachiever.</p>
<p>Who is still walking the earth.</p>
<p>Hot dog.</p>
<p>Hot <em>dawg</em>.</p>
<p>Makes me wanna do an old man dance.</p>
<p>Excuse me.</p>
<p>[Dancing using mostly fists, shimmying shoulders, and some foot movement but not as much as you'd expect.]</p>
<p>Thank you.</p>
<p>Where was I? </p>
<p>Oh yes.</p>
<p>I've always believed you can manufacture luck.</p>
<p>I've had a lot of luck in my life, so I suppose it's easy for me to believe it.</p>
<p>But I also view many failures as lucky.</p>
<p>Which I don't think unlucky folk do.</p>
<p>I see many of my Ls as standing for Luck. </p>
<p>Lucky losses.</p>
<p>Over time, these Ls have turned into Ws.</p>
<p>And I either saw it right away, as it happened, or decades after.</p>
<p>And so I'm wondering now, if luck is more about perspective, about reframing, than about what actually happened.</p>
<p>Interpretation of events rather than events themselves.</p>
<p>Unlucky because you got hurt or lucky you didn't get more hurt?</p>
<p>Unlucky because you almost died or lucky you survived?</p>
<p>I am a lucky stoic.</p>
<p>Been that way, be that way, believe that way.</p>
<p>To out-kicking your coverage, instructive fumbles, and the infinite grace of God.</p>
<p>And to everything it makes possible, even the im.</p>
<p>🍀</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Bystander</title>
        <author>
            <name>𖤂</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/bystander/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/bystander/</id>

        <updated>2026-01-13T14:21:21-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    I'm hitting that mid-January funk. Except instead of a new gym&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I'm hitting that mid-January funk.</p>
<p>Except instead of a new gym membership wearout, it's this musings column.</p>
<p>Perhaps a little bit of the enthusiasm and luster has been lost since restarting this whole writing thing in October of '25.</p>
<p>A smidge.</p>
<p>A sprinkle.</p>
<p>Writing everyday is perhaps too much. Or too frequent. Or both.</p>
<p>It's in these days where I have nothing to say that all the growth comes from.</p>
<p>The hard reps.</p>
<p>I use hard in a very narrow sense.</p>
<p>This sheet easy.</p>
<p>What can I pluck out of thin air and make something out of nothing?</p>
<p>One of the basic tenets of martial arts is rhythm. </p>
<p>When you see two people trained to fight, it's almost like they're dancing.</p>
<p>One, two. One, two, three. One moves forward, the other back.</p>
<p>There's an order there. </p>
<p>That's why some wise folk say fighting a newbie or an untrained person can be very difficult. </p>
<p>Rookies tend to be spastic. Unpredictable. Muscly. Tight. And just chaotic.</p>
<p>You know what I mean?</p>
<p>Crazy.</p>
<p>And so, when you get really high up in this type of training, you learn a very advanced technique.</p>
<p>After you have all the moves down, you're ready to start all over.</p>
<p>Once you <em>have</em> rhythm, you must <em>break</em> it.</p>
<p>Re-introducing chaos into the order of advanced combat.</p>
<p>You spend years first mastering order to only then keep it spicy through mixing in chaos.</p>
<p>One, two, one, one, one, two, three, four, one, high kick!</p>
<p>Bad form, bad form, bad form, perfect execution!</p>
<p>I always found that funny.</p>
<p>At the height of controlled technique, liquid flow, of true mastery, is the most noob of tactics.</p>
<p>Life is like that.</p>
<p>In so many ways.</p>
<p>An apex leads you right back to the beginning.</p>
<p>Flailing, flailing, slap, slap, crisp cross.</p>
<p><em>Bing!</em></p>
<p>Don't try that ess with me, though.</p>
<p>I'm so advanced I lock my arms out to my sides (T-pose) and just start spinning.</p>
<p>Fools be running into these fists.</p>
<p>Like a top.</p>
<p>But, as I've said many many times, I am a man of peace.</p>
<p>I just like to keep things spicy.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Mirror | rorriM</title>
        <author>
            <name>𖤂</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/mirror-mirror/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/mirror-mirror/</id>

        <updated>2026-01-12T13:11:38-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    You know what my problem is? I still walk around like&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>You know what my problem is?</p>
<p>I still walk around like I'm 230.</p>
<p>But I'm not.</p>
<p>I still think I am.</p>
<p>And sure, all things being equal, I bring equalizers with me.</p>
<p>I'm like that meme of a cub looking in the mirror and seeing a lion, except I'm an old(ish) tiger looking and seeing a svelte one in their prime.</p>
<p>But all of that to say, I think I should realize things aren't the same anymore.</p>
<p>And like everything that that implies, there is some good and some not so good.</p>
<p>I can move quicker than ever.</p>
<p>But I can tell I've lost a step.</p>
<p>Ain't that something?</p>
<p>It's something.</p>
<p>But there's one thing I forgot to tell you about that meme. The mirror reflects your soul, not your physical.</p>
<p>And all I see is a smiling (smirking?) lucky mf.</p>
<p>😼</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
