<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>Iterating</title>
    <link href="https://iterating.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://iterating.com" />
    <updated>2026-01-24T19:07:45-05:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>𖤂</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://iterating.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>iPad Handling</title>
        <author>
            <name>𖤂</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/ipad-handling/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/ipad-handling/</id>

        <updated>2026-01-24T18:55:41-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Some people can talk a good game. Talk, talk, talk. It's&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Some people can talk a good game.</p>
<p>Talk, talk, talk.</p>
<p>It's the ones that share so much about how great they are that creep me out.</p>
<p>Especially when no one else agrees.</p>
<p>But it can work the other way, too.</p>
<p>Sometimes, you learn stuff you never really wanted to know.</p>
<p>For example, I recently learned about a trend on one of them newfangled (aka quite old) social media hades holes that is just someone begging for money.</p>
<p>They livestream for cash.</p>
<p>Some of them even admonish their viewers for not giving enough.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>You can do better than that!</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Oddly, it apparently works.</p>
<p>Actually, I have no idea.</p>
<p>I don't want to dig any further into it.</p>
<p>I will say, though, part of me is impressed.</p>
<p>One of the things about growing up Korean is that you have quite a bit of shame.</p>
<p>That is, you are <em>taught</em> to have it.</p>
<p>How you can bring shame to yourself, and more importantly, shame to your family.</p>
<p>Honor.</p>
<p>And at first I thought, about these streamers, have you no shame?</p>
<p>And I think, some of them don't, but some oddly shift it some way. Not only do they have no shame, they shame their viewers. </p>
<p>They shame their donors!</p>
<p><em>How dare you not give to me. After all I've done (nothing but asking for money).</em></p>
<p>It's psychology.</p>
<p>Weeds out a lot.</p>
<p>How scams often contain typos and bad grammar intentionally. For it weeds out everyone else so only the most susceptible are left.</p>
<p>Easy pickings.</p>
<p>Anyone who gives money to someone in need is a saint.</p>
<p>But giving money to a stranger online because they demand you do so is an interesting consequence of, I think(?), loneliness.</p>
<p>People want to hear their name out loud. Want to be thanked. Want to be shamed, even.</p>
<p>Shame is many things, but it's not alone, especially amongst Koreans.</p>
<p>So all of that to say, here is my Venmo:</p>
<p>Just kidding.</p>
<p>But if you're offering...</p>
<p>Nah, what am I saying!?!</p>
<p>Listen, if you're cutting checks...</p>
<p>Is that what they still say? Cutting checks?</p>
<p>I think that's right.</p>
<p>I hope it's all some sort of artistic statement. Begging streams. Some sort of ironic tragecomedy.</p>
<p>Like those pranks they play on people just to see what they do.</p>
<p>And they film it.</p>
<p>But I know, I know, somehow, that would be worse.</p>
<p>There's a picture of near century old Billy Shatner eating a bowl of cereal from the driver's seat of his car.</p>
<p>And I've seen a lot of folks saying that is their goal.</p>
<p>To be able to live with that zero of an eff to give.</p>
<p>I just see negligence (or self-driving) at best.</p>
<p>And I love Bill Shat.</p>
<p>So he gets a pass.</p>
<p>So these digital folks with their pixeled palms out, I'm hoping its some weird ai. But I know it ain't.</p>
<p>I know it ain't.</p>
<p>It's as real as anything else these days.</p>
<p>This coming from an optimist.</p>
<p>💰</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Opus Apex</title>
        <author>
            <name>𖤂</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/opus-apex/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/opus-apex/</id>

        <updated>2026-01-23T17:08:29-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    For the first twenty or so years of your life, your&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>For the first twenty or so years of your life, your life is pretty much about you.</p>
<p>Maybe 30.</p>
<p>Sometime before 40, I hope, you start to think about other people more than you do about yourself.</p>
<p>At least, that's what happened to me.</p>
<p>My life hasn't been about me for a long time.</p>
<p>And I love it that way.</p>
<p>There was a season where everything was about me again a few years ago, but that's because I was fighting for my life.</p>
<p>That was/is a boss battle.</p>
<p>But even then, I wanted to make sure my family was taken care of.</p>
<p>Was impacted least.</p>
<p>Were finding silver linings.</p>
<p>I don't say that to brag, I just didn't want to go out without leaving instructions or on a bad note.</p>
<p>I wanted them to remember me at my best.</p>
<p>I didn't want to whither away.</p>
<p>But I almost did.</p>
<p>I mean I withered.</p>
<p>But not totally away.</p>
<p>You come to peace in such moments.</p>
<p>What a good run I had.</p>
<p>How blessed.</p>
<p>You see, the loss is all on this side of life.</p>
<p>For those that remain.</p>
<p>At least, that's how I choose to see it.</p>
<p>It's funny.</p>
<p>All this time feels extra.</p>
<p>Like a bonus.</p>
<p>Like an after-but-before-afterlife.</p>
<p>A sequel.</p>
<p>Like I got a second chance.</p>
<p>I've had a few of those, you know.</p>
<p>I wish I could tell you it will all work out. </p>
<p>But you have to figure it out on your own.</p>
<p>I will say that I always thought life was all about me.</p>
<p>How I didn't need anyone.</p>
<p>And how wrong I was.</p>
<p>How it's all about the people you love.</p>
<p>All about the people who love you.</p>
<p>Not fake you.</p>
<p>The real you.</p>
<p>The one that appears when everyone else is gone you.</p>
<p>They know <em>that</em> you. They know you by your actions, your thoughts, not just your words.</p>
<p>These are the ones that get to stay.</p>
<p>Because they loved you even at your withered.</p>
<p>And they cheer you loudest at your best.</p>
<p>I think the kids call it being a "real one."</p>
<p>So this is for the real ones.</p>
<p>Am I saying that right?</p>
<p>Oh, I'm not.</p>
<p>This is for <em>my</em> real ones.</p>
<p>Who know my real one.</p>
<p>The end and the beginning.</p>
<p>♥️</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Two Fiddy</title>
        <author>
            <name>𖤂</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/two-fiddy/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/two-fiddy/</id>

        <updated>2026-01-22T12:27:52-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    This year marks the United States' 250th anniversary. Still a young&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>This year marks the United States' 250th anniversary.</p>
<p>Still a young country by some metrics, but fully an adult.</p>
<p>And it got me to think, I probably won't see 300th. Or if I get there, I probably won't be able to do much about it.</p>
<p>So 250th we will celebrate.</p>
<p>'Merica.</p>
<p>It's weird to me to live in a time where patriotism is considered by some as bad.</p>
<p>Where waving Old Glory can get you hurt.</p>
<p>At least here. On home turf.</p>
<p>That's weird, to me.</p>
<p>I love this country.</p>
<p>My country.</p>
<p>Tis of thee.</p>
<p>I'd wear yellow and red and shake and beat up heels, but yellow and red ain't my colors.</p>
<p>I'm more rose gold.</p>
<p>I tell you what, though, things are very interesting.</p>
<p>I think there is a war going on.</p>
<p>But instead of good versus evil, it's a little more nuanced. A little easier to spot.</p>
<p>I'd say it is the beautiful versus the ugly.</p>
<p>There is a war on beautiful.</p>
<p>Usually fought by uglies.</p>
<p>And I hate to say it, but we outnumbered.</p>
<p>That's right, that was just a sneaky way to say I think I'm beautiful.</p>
<p>A beautiful patriot. I'm a Giants fan so that "p" will stay lowercase.</p>
<p>Speaking of Harbaugh, I recall a story he and his brother shared about their father. How every morning, as he dropped his two sons off at school, he would say the same thing.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>"Now, boys, I want you to attack this day with an enthusiasm previously unknown to mankind."</p>
</blockquote>
<p>I heard that decades ago and I still remember it verbatim. Because, man, if that ain't America, well I don't what is.</p>
<p>Now, I'd say that to you right now, but I'm not your daddy. </p>
<p>Unless my kids are reading this, then, of course I am your daddy.</p>
<p>I'm talking to these other people who want me to coach them.</p>
<p>Who want me to mentor them.</p>
<p>Somewhere between 250 and 300, I might be available, but not today.</p>
<p>Not this year.</p>
<p>This year, I celebrate some important birthdays.</p>
<p>To singing your anthem perfectly.</p>
<p>And motivational founding fathers.</p>
<p>Happy birthday.</p>
<p>🇺🇸</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>End Of A Lightning Bolt</title>
        <author>
            <name>𖤂</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/living-on-the-end-of-a-lightning-bolt/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/living-on-the-end-of-a-lightning-bolt/</id>

        <updated>2026-01-21T15:52:39-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    What a year it's been. And we're on Day 21. A&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>What a year it's been.</p>
<p>And we're on Day 21.</p>
<p>A lucky number for some.</p>
<p>As you get older, you realize certain things.</p>
<p>Patterns emerge.</p>
<p><em>Didn't we do this a decade ago? Two?</em></p>
<p>They say history doesn't repeat, it rhymes.</p>
<p>As you get lucky enough to be an adult with silver hairs, you start to realize something.</p>
<p>Everything is manipulated.</p>
<p>Someone is stirring the pot.</p>
<p>Who?</p>
<p>Well, you should consider such questions very dangerous.</p>
<p>And the truth is, I have no idea.</p>
<p>I do have suspects, though.</p>
<p>And I just wonder, if all the noise is meant to distract us.</p>
<p>Up, down. War, peace. Win, lose. Live, die.</p>
<p>Government doesn't always use its money honestly and fairly?</p>
<p>Politicians can be crooked?</p>
<p>The market is going down?</p>
<p>We got conflict in our streets?</p>
<p>People love to gamble?</p>
<p>There are concerns of war all over the globe?</p>
<p>Huh.</p>
<p>Who knew?</p>
<p>This is not news.</p>
<p>This is the history of our world.</p>
<p>Humans are flawed.</p>
<p>Even, especially, our best ones.</p>
<p>And good intentions can have some pretty evil consequences.</p>
<p>Look back, it will show you what's coming towards.</p>
<p>It might be different, but it's the same.</p>
<p>Lock it up, lock it in. </p>
<p>The time coming.</p>
<p>Me?</p>
<p>I'm changing the world by changing me.</p>
<p>If I can change my world, the world is changed (at least to me).</p>
<p>And shouldn't that be the first metric?</p>
<p>So I'm dancing in the stratosphere, with Dusty, and the American Dream.</p>
<p>Just thankful for my piece (peace).</p>
<p>⚡</p>
<p>🙏</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Alpha Omega</title>
        <author>
            <name>𖤂</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/alpha-omega/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/alpha-omega/</id>

        <updated>2026-01-20T13:52:54-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    I believe in every day sacralization. To make every day, every&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I believe in every day sacralization. </p>
<p>To make every day, every moment, something beyond sacred.</p>
<p>Beyond holy.</p>
<p>This is, of course, easier said than done.</p>
<p>But it's good to have nice goals.</p>
<p>Another goal I'm narrowing down on is this idea of an Apex Opus.</p>
<p>It's my play on magnum opus, but even more unique, more personal, more for you.</p>
<p>The pinnacle work.</p>
<p>Your highest success.</p>
<p>And while I see it as an integral part of raising a family and leading your tribe, I also wonder if it could be something more distilled, more concrete, even if non-analog.</p>
<p>Magnum opuses are works of art or books.</p>
<p>What about apex opuses?</p>
<p>I'm not sure yet.</p>
<p>A word (or more), a drawing, a human being (or three), a creation of some form that you made or transformed with your own bare mind and hands.</p>
<p>That sounds good.</p>
<p>As I believe that we will all be remembered most for a snapshot in time (hopefully in the Best of Times), I also believe that we will be honored for our best work.</p>
<p>At least, ideally.</p>
<p>If you're a crook, folks tend to remember you at your worst. For your worst actions. For your worst work.</p>
<p>But let's try to avoid that.</p>
<p>Let's go the other way.</p>
<p>A 180.</p>
<p>And try to be remembered at our best.</p>
<p>At our highest.</p>
<p>At our grandest.</p>
<p>At our apex.</p>
<p>Now, for most of you, I have really good news.</p>
<p>You haven't hit your peak yet.</p>
<p>But I have some less good news.</p>
<p>You have to start working on your apex opus.</p>
<p>Wait, that sounds like excellent news.</p>
<p>It doesn't have to become well-known, if the only person who benefits is you, I call that a win.</p>
<p>But start to think about it.</p>
<p>Who are you?</p>
<p>What are you about?</p>
<p>And what will you be at your highest point?</p>
<p>Show your work.</p>
<p>And what you show will be proof you were here.</p>
<p>And that you made something of yourself.</p>
<p>And if no one else will applaud, well, you can count on at least one pair of hands.</p>
<p>Not me, though. </p>
<p>Probably your umma.</p>
<p>But it should be you.</p>
<p>Sorry, I probably led you to think it'd be me clapping.</p>
<p>I'm like Tony Danza ova here.</p>
<p>Busy.</p>
<p>AO.</p>
<p>OA.</p>
<p>Al out.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Apex Opus</title>
        <author>
            <name>𖤂</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/apex-opus/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/apex-opus/</id>

        <updated>2026-01-19T16:22:32-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Today is like a second Sunday. It feels like that to&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Today is like a second Sunday.</p>
<p>It feels like that to me.</p>
<p>And so, I don't want to write too much, because I already did.</p>
<p>But here's something interesting.</p>
<p>In a good life, I think that having a <em>magnum opus</em> is essential.</p>
<p>Having a great work.</p>
<p>Having made something of tremendous value.</p>
<p>If only for yourself. And your loved ones.</p>
<p>An impact.</p>
<p>But even more important is having an <em>apex opus</em>.</p>
<p>Your highest work.</p>
<p>Your grandmasterpiece.</p>
<p>Your verse.</p>
<p>As in, what will be the headline on your obituary?</p>
<p>And I mean that in a good way.</p>
<p>In the best way.</p>
<p>I am iterating on this big idea.</p>
<p>To dreams.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Don of Kings </title>
        <author>
            <name>𖤂</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/don-of-kings/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/don-of-kings/</id>

        <updated>2026-01-18T17:50:21-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    I interrupt this musings column with the following: Why hasn't anyone&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I interrupt this musings column with the following:</p>
<p>Why hasn't anyone told me about chess boxing?</p>
<p>You know, the hybrid sport that alternates rounds of boxing and chess?</p>
<p>Aka the Sport of the Future?</p>
<p><em>60 Minutes</em> did a feature on it a couple of months ago.</p>
<p>It's huge in Russia (I think). Has been for years (I think).</p>
<p>And I'm just hearing about it now.</p>
<p>Brains and brawn.</p>
<p>Hooks and rooks (stole that from the <em>60M</em> segment, but it's pretty good!).</p>
<p>Perfect for a nerd who can fight (sorta).</p>
<p>Or a fighter who can nerd out (sorta).</p>
<p>Aka, <em>my people</em>.</p>
<p>You can have your pickles and balls.</p>
<p>Feast on 'em.</p>
<p>I found my old man sport.</p>
<p>♟🥊</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Tango and Cash</title>
        <author>
            <name>𖤂</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/tango-and-cash/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/tango-and-cash/</id>

        <updated>2026-01-18T11:32:38-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    The dance to life is a delicate one. And by that&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>The dance to life is a delicate one.</p>
<p>And by that I mean spectrums.</p>
<p>A large part of leading a family is to know the balance between protecting them and also letting them learn lessons the hard way (for themselves).</p>
<p>And the trick is, I think, to protect them from the hardest or perhaps I should say harshest lessons.</p>
<p>And what's the harshest?</p>
<p>I'm not sure.</p>
<p>Maybe it is <em>true</em> heartbreak?</p>
<p>Or worse yet, staying in love with the wrong person?</p>
<p>Is it addiction?</p>
<p>Illness?</p>
<p>I think we have all learned enough to know that precaution has its own dangers.</p>
<p>There is danger in being safe.</p>
<p>And safety in being dangerous.</p>
<p>And thus, everything is a sliding scale.</p>
<p>And I search for that perfect balance.</p>
<p>Failure isn't bad. It took me a long time to learn that.</p>
<p>Failure is necessarily implied to make accomplishment feel earned.</p>
<p>If you are guaranteed a win, you will take it for granted.</p>
<p>Who wants to hit 1.000?</p>
<p>You think you do, but you really don't.</p>
<p>But stacking failure on top of another on top of another, that's when things get rough.</p>
<p>So that's one, to protect those you lead from the spiral failures.</p>
<p>Sidenote: Work on not being right. Or at least, not feeling some sort of weird mix of vindication ("I told you so") and validation when you caution and warn and then it happens. You can almost see it coming. They can't. You cannot rewind, but memory is a great teacher, and you hope they remember how often you seem to know what you're talking about. Even and especially before it happens.</p>
<p>I don't rely on people changing. </p>
<p>I change.</p>
<p>Either my angle or my position.</p>
<p>Some mistakes are unforgivable.</p>
<p>At least by me.</p>
<p>Protect your loved ones from those.</p>
<p>And so that's the dance.</p>
<p>It seems delicate, but upon reflection there's a lot of room on the dance floor.</p>
<p>There's a lot of space to play.</p>
<p>But all the fun's at the edges.</p>
<p>And thus, we dance.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>New You. Save?</title>
        <author>
            <name>𖤂</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/new-you-save/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/new-you-save/</id>

        <updated>2026-01-17T17:12:22-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    I don't play video games anymore (my game is writing), but&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I don't play video games anymore (my game is writing), but I still love them.</p>
<p>One of my favorite parts of video games is in its character creation.</p>
<p>Whether sports or RPG, it better have create mode down and deep.</p>
<p>I'd spend hours getting the details right.</p>
<p>Starting from their name, their look, their attributes.</p>
<p>Nerds understand.</p>
<p>I had to get it <em>juuuuuuuust</em> right.</p>
<p>Goldilocks right.</p>
<p>And this was usually before you even started playing the game!</p>
<p>And it makes me wonder, why we don't do that for the video game called Life.</p>
<p>I mean, who spends hours (let alone years) on our own character creation?</p>
<p>At least with that lens?</p>
<p>I've joked before that we all need real life character sheets (not CVs or resumes), but I think I'm onto something.</p>
<p>We need to spend more time on character creation, on who we want to be, than we do.</p>
<p>So that's what I'll leave you with today.</p>
<p>Go into "new game" or "continue game" (as appropriate) and see if you can create or edit your character.</p>
<p>And while you can spend hours finding the right eyebrows, I'd encourage you to spend some time on your mental attributes and skills. </p>
<p>Want to boost wisdom? Perhaps you look into stoicism.</p>
<p>Want to save money? The world is your oyster (make more than you spend).</p>
<p>Want to boost charisma? Well, look no further, champ.</p>
<p>[Smiling. Eyes wide open. Not blinking. Direct eye contact. Blink first, dammit.]</p>
<p>I'm just saying, most of us grown-ups stop with the character creation part of our own stories. We leave it all for the digital world.</p>
<p>And that's just silly.</p>
<p>I'm beginning to understand now that the old grandmasters didn't start out as young grandmasters. </p>
<p>They grew into it.</p>
<p>And that's sort of what I would like to do.</p>
<p>Grow into an old grandmaster character.</p>
<p>Although there is not much use for old grandmasters, as I knew it, so I think I'll edit it to being a more kinder, gentler, more useful old grand<em>mentor</em>.</p>
<p>A mentor of mentors.</p>
<p>Now, I just need to find the right shade of shimmery silver hair to compliment my glowing golden skin. </p>
<p>Be back in a few hours.</p>
<p>Create your character.</p>
<p>Create your life.</p>
<p>Create a new game.</p>
<p>Save.</p>
<p>[Returns a few hours later, full of shimmer and glow. Surprised to see you still sitting there. Doesn't sell it. Pretends to not see you. Gathers a few things. Leaves room. Turns off light. <em>I...I should probably head</em>, you say to yourself, as you sit blissfully in the dark, thinking about the right elbow accessory to equip that screams YOU when you get home.]</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>The Donger Need Food</title>
        <author>
            <name>𖤂</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/the-donger-need-food/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/the-donger-need-food/</id>

        <updated>2026-01-16T11:46:25-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Is it better to write with an empty stomach or a&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Is it better to write with an empty stomach or a full one?</p>
<p>I am wrestling with this right now.</p>
<p>The topic: Optimal belly input for optimal writing output.</p>
<p>It's probably like most things, the answer is probably somewhere in between.</p>
<p>After a light meal. As you nibble on a nice snack.</p>
<p>Or a few hours digesting a feast.</p>
<p>Right now, I got a meatloaf meal in my belly.</p>
<p>Meat.</p>
<p>Loaf.</p>
<p>Poetic.</p>
<p>A rare non-kimchi meal.</p>
<p>But it's been known to happen.</p>
<p>And boy, am I full, but I'm not sure I can write to my best ability.</p>
<p>The Donger need nap.</p>
<p>The Donger need write.</p>
<p>Of course, there is no perfect time to write or anything else.</p>
<p>Only windows of opportunity.</p>
<p>So this is mine.</p>
<p>I sits.</p>
<p>I writes.</p>
<p>I do not consider this a chore.</p>
<p>Which surprises me.</p>
<p>Having to do this thing every day.</p>
<p>But I am increasingly treating this as almost like another meal.</p>
<p>I have to eat.</p>
<p>I have to write.</p>
<p>Or, better put:</p>
<p>I get to eat.</p>
<p>I get to write.</p>
<p>A privilege.</p>
<p>Because that is what it is.</p>
<p>Now, I'm not always bringing the heat.</p>
<p>Somedays, I'm throwing change-ups and sliders.</p>
<p>This is probably my eephus.</p>
<p>But I'm smiling. </p>
<p>Belly full.</p>
<p>Floating a few inches off the ground.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Strike Three!</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Got 'em.</p>
<p>PS: If you ever call me "The Donger" that's a nut punch right there. Maybe two.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
