<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>Iterating</title>
    <link href="https://iterating.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://iterating.com" />
    <updated>2025-10-12T20:21:15-04:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Alex Chung</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://iterating.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>I Been Here For Years</title>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Chung</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/i-been-here-for-years/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/i-been-here-for-years/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-12T20:21:15-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Ever heard of Kintsugi? It's popping up more and more lately.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Ever heard of Kintsugi?</p>
<p>It's popping up more and more lately. It's a Japanese thing. Where they take broken pottery and repair it using precious metals, like gold.</p>
<p>The idea is that rather than fixing it and hiding the repairs and making it look new again, you highlight the flaws and turn them into the focal point. Beauty in the once broken.</p>
<p>You treat the damage and its solution as part of the pottery's story. Hurt and heal.</p>
<p>As you might expect, this has become a popular idea for life and business.</p>
<p>Taking your scars and showing them off. Letting it shine as part of your story. Everyone breaks. Some of us build back stronger than ever.</p>
<p>Nobody likes a story where a guy starts out perfect and stays perfect.</p>
<p>Everybody loves comebacks, kid.</p>
<p>But don't call it that.</p>
<p>You been here for years.</p>
<p>To the beautifully broken.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Marriage (In A Nutshell)</title>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Chung</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/marriage-in-a-nutshell/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/marriage-in-a-nutshell/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-12T17:10:10-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Watching a show the other day. See the lady from Who's&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Watching a show the other day. See the lady from <em>Who's The Boss?</em> in it.</p>
<p>Me: "See that lady? That's the lady from <em>Who's the Boss?</em> Remember that show?</p>
<p>Wife: "Yes. Judith Light?"</p>
<p>Me: "Yeah. That's her!"</p>
<p>Wife (looking at screen): "No, it's not."</p>
<p>Me: "Yeah, it is."</p>
<p>Wife: "No, it's not her."</p>
<p>Me: "Yeah, it is."</p>
<p>Wife: "No, it's not."</p>
<p>Me: "Mmhmm, it's her."</p>
<p>Wife (seeing a close-up): "It is!"</p>
<p>Another day in paradise.</p>
<p>And I mean it.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Grandmentor</title>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Chung</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/grandmentor/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/grandmentor/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-11T17:25:21-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Remember in those Saturday morning Kung Fu movies, the old guy?&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Remember in those Saturday morning Kung Fu movies, the old guy?</p>
<p>Long, silvery hair, fu manchu, could float on clouds and ride lightning bolts.</p>
<p>Never the main character, just the Grandmaster the star needs to meet to beat the bad guys and get the girl.</p>
<p>A little mean. A little eccentric. A little ethereal.</p>
<p>There's marketing that says everyone wants to be the hero, but you get paid the most for being the mentor. The guide. Ain't that grand?</p>
<p>If you're into that.</p>
<p>Me?</p>
<p>I like riding lightning bolts.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Chopping Down Mountains with the Edge of My Hand</title>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Chung</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/chopping-down-mountains-with-the-edge-of-my-hand/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/chopping-down-mountains-with-the-edge-of-my-hand/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-11T16:29:51-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    You know, professional fighters and wrestlers are lucky. They get entrance&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>You know, professional fighters and wrestlers are lucky.</p>
<p>They get entrance songs. </p>
<p>I suppose baseball players get walk-up music. And relief pitchers get a song.</p>
<p>But Bill in accounting doesn't. </p>
<p>Or Fred in legal.</p>
<p>And you know what?</p>
<p>Maybe they should.</p>
<p>All of that to say, what's your entrance song?</p>
<p>What you rocking to the ring or cage?</p>
<p>I've always been partial to Monster Magnet's "Space Lord" -- but then there's Hendrix.</p>
<p>High quality problem, picking out your entrance song.</p>
<p>Too many to choose from.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>I Got This Theory</title>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Chung</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/i-got-this-theory/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/i-got-this-theory/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-10T18:44:28-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    So people remember people by a singular image. Like for the&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>So people remember people by a singular image.</p>
<p>Like for the current president of the United States. He will be remembered for this current phase. </p>
<p>It won't be real estate mogul. It won't be reality TV star.</p>
<p>It'll be him old. Mr. President. That's his singular photo op.</p>
<p>It's like Yoda. Or Mr. Miyagi.</p>
<p>We don't remember them young, however accomplished they were then. They're forever the older versions. Their singular image.</p>
<p>Of course it works for younger people, too. Some we remember for their youth.</p>
<p>Often those taken too soon.</p>
<p>And so what I'm getting at is, I'm working on my singular image thing.</p>
<p>And I want it to be a long ways away.</p>
<p>I don't want it to be 20 year old me. Or 40. Or 50. Maybe 60. Maybe 70.</p>
<p>God willing.</p>
<p>Anyways, that's my theory.</p>
<p>What's the picture people will remember you by? You then? You now? Or you later?</p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Dragon, Fly</title>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Chung</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/dragon-fly/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/dragon-fly/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-09T18:59:40-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Did you know that dragonflies spend most of their lives swimming?&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Did you know that dragonflies spend most of their lives swimming?</p>
<p>Years. </p>
<p>They only live a few weeks above water and flying around. As the dragonflies we know and love.</p>
<p>Imagine that. You spend your whole life underwater.</p>
<p>Thinking that is the whole world.</p>
<p>Then, in your golden years, you emerge. In a whole new world.</p>
<p>As a whole new creation.</p>
<p>Fly, dragon, fly.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Iterate You Say</title>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Chung</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/iterate-you-say/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/iterate-you-say/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-08T20:27:17-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Been thinking a lot about time. Time as currency. Time as&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Been thinking a lot about time.</p>
<p>Time as currency.</p>
<p>Time as wealth.</p>
<p>And how the richest of us have decades, even a century, ahead of us.</p>
<p>And how we punish people with prison terms measured in time. How we punish by taking their time away. It's the ultimate penalty. Taking away time.</p>
<p>And how so many of us waste our time.</p>
<p>Like self-imposed prison sentences.</p>
<p>And I wrestle with this, as a man who believes in playing the long game.</p>
<p>Patience while enjoying the moment. Delaying gratification but finding it gratifying to do so. Tapping infinity in a second. Over and over.</p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>The Good</title>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Chung</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/the-good/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/the-good/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-08T20:01:27-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    When I was a kid, we rooted for the good guys.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>When I was a kid, we rooted for the good guys.</p>
<p>The heroes.</p>
<p>The ones who saved people. Beat up villains.</p>
<p>And it was clear. It was clear who the heroes were. And who the villains were.</p>
<p>And today, to me, it's not as clear.</p>
<p>You live long enough, stuff turns upside down.</p>
<p>Who are your heroes?</p>
<p>Who are your villains?</p>
<p>Who is the best person you know? Not talking fame, wealth, or power.</p>
<p>Who has the best heart? Who is bravest? Who do you love the most?</p>
<p>Is it still cool to be good?</p>
<p>And would anyone, anyone in the world, say the best person they know is you?</p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>It&#x27;s Not Business, It&#x27;s Personal</title>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Chung</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/its-not-business-its-personal/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/its-not-business-its-personal/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-07T23:18:44-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    So this is going to be a personal thing. And as&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>So this is going to be a personal thing. And as a private person, the question then becomes: How personal do I want to get?</p>
<p>Where am I right now?</p>
<p>I'm good. I'm really good. Lucky. Blessed.</p>
<p>It wasn't always this way. Or maybe it was, but I didn't see it.</p>
<p>I see now.</p>
<p>They say youth is wasted on the young. But maybe it really is wisdom wasted on the old.</p>
<p>I sure am wiser than I used to be. But maybe I'm just getting old.</p>
<p>In the 80s, there was this curmudgeon of a wrestler named Terry Funk, a Texas cowboy heel who they would call "Middle-Aged and Crazy!" He used to brand our heroes with an iron from his ranch and swing his fists at ghosts. I used to love to hate him.</p>
<p>But he makes more sense to me, now.</p>
<p>I'm not saying I'm crazy (I'll leave the middle-aged part alone), but the things I've done in my life probably only would make sense to few.</p>
<p>I'm being vague purposefully. I don't know how much I want to share. But it's always been personal, never business.</p>
<p>At least with me. Always personal.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Two-A-Days</title>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Chung</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/two-a-days/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/two-a-days/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-07T22:56:14-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Yeah, yeah. I'm excited. Want to create as many entries as&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Yeah, yeah. I'm excited. Want to create as many entries as I can to see how they stack.</p>
<p>Nothing to see here. No one's looking anyway.</p>
<p>I hope. You looking? Blog looker.</p>
<p>These are the ramblings of a guy who has nothing really to say.</p>
<p>Other than: Thank You.</p>
<p>Can I still write? </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
