<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>Iterating</title>
    <link href="https://iterating.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://iterating.com" />
    <updated>2026-03-03T11:18:00-05:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>杻백</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://iterating.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Late Again</title>
        <author>
            <name>杻백</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/late-again/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/late-again/</id>

        <updated>2026-03-03T11:18:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    A great actor playing a terrible role once told another actor&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>A great actor playing a terrible role once told another actor on screen to "never go full absurd."</p>
<p>He said another word, but that's how I took it.</p>
<p>Never go full absurd.</p>
<p>That's the mistake.</p>
<p>Going maximal absurdity.</p>
<p>Leave a little room for normalcy.</p>
<p>Full absurd makes people squirmy.</p>
<p>Now, I typically enjoy that, but only in degrees.</p>
<p>And thus, believe it or not, I have to dial it down at times.</p>
<p>For the public.</p>
<p>For the column.</p>
<p>In pro wrestling, they say "just be yourself, dialed up to 11."</p>
<p>And in the modern day circus, this advice works.</p>
<p>But I'm just a dude in a spaceship, rocketing around the multiverse.</p>
<p>If I dialed it up to 11, I'd be<span style="text-decoration: line-through;">in</span> onUranus.</p>
<p>游</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Grand</title>
        <author>
            <name>杻백</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/grand/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/grand/</id>

        <updated>2026-03-02T20:06:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Workshop with me. Say I get to 60. What will I&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Workshop with me.</p>
<p>Say I get to 60.</p>
<p>What will I be?</p>
<p>Will I be grand?</p>
<p>I hope to be grand.</p>
<p>But not in the way you might think (too soon!).</p>
<p>A mentor.</p>
<p>A founder.</p>
<p>Alive.</p>
<p>The last part is somewhat out of my control.</p>
<p>But I think I can do something about the other two.</p>
<p>I can mentor.</p>
<p>I can found.</p>
<p>I've done both.</p>
<p>I do both.</p>
<p>What does it mean to be a grandmentor?</p>
<p>What does it mean to be a grandfounder?</p>
<p>Mentor of mentors?</p>
<p>Founder of founders?</p>
<p>The cool thing about coining a term is you get to define what it means.</p>
<p>These are the types of things I enjoy doing.</p>
<p>Evoking with words.</p>
<p>Dreaming big.</p>
<p>Playing the long game.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Asymmetric Bettor</title>
        <author>
            <name>杻백</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/asymmetric-bettor/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/asymmetric-bettor/</id>

        <updated>2026-03-01T12:42:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    I don't gamble. At least, not like most. I like little&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I don't gamble.</p>
<p>At least, not like most.</p>
<p>I like little ventures, large outputs.</p>
<p>Now, you're thinking monetarily.</p>
<p>And that's where most people want to take it.</p>
<p>But if you think about it, little ins and big outs are what life is about.</p>
<p>Like a prism.</p>
<p>Light in, rainbow out.</p>
<p>This musings column, I'd like to think, is an asymmetric bet of sorts.</p>
<p>I just sit here and type.</p>
<p>A few minutes a day.</p>
<p>And let me tell you, it has been a huge win.</p>
<p>The trick then is to find your own arenas where a little goes a long way.</p>
<p>Writing.</p>
<p>Coding.</p>
<p>Hustling.</p>
<p>Love.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>"You know, sometimes all you need is twenty seconds of insane courage, just literally, twenty seconds of just embarrassing bravery. And I promise you, something great will come of it."</p>
</blockquote>
<p>To underdogs.</p>
<p>And underdawgs.</p>
<p>Betting on you.</p>
<p>游</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Vidi, Vici, Veni</title>
        <author>
            <name>杻백</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/vidi-vici-veni/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/vidi-vici-veni/</id>

        <updated>2026-02-28T11:33:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    You know, I hear they cancelled Latin. I do like a&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>You know, I hear they cancelled Latin.</p>
<p>I do like a lot of Latin, though.</p>
<p>It's an interesting language with lots of interesting words and phrases.</p>
<p>But we're not a language class.</p>
<p>We're here to...</p>
<p>[Covers mic.]</p>
<p>What are we here to do, again?</p>
<p>People just come here to read the musings?</p>
<p>No, no, that can't be right.</p>
<p>[Uncovers mic.]</p>
<p>We are here to talk about grace.</p>
<p>About giving it, receiving it, and how it took me ages to understand its power.</p>
<p>For many decades, I never gave it.</p>
<p>I was cold.</p>
<p>Unforgiving.</p>
<p>Ungraceful.</p>
<p>And it worked both ways.</p>
<p>I never gave myself any grace.</p>
<p>Nor did I give it to others.</p>
<p>Unless I didn't care about you. Then you're just invisible.</p>
<p>Ain't that something?</p>
<p>Not giving you grace meant I cared.</p>
<p>Back then.</p>
<p>I'm changed now, right?</p>
<p>Right??</p>
<p>Bah.</p>
<p>Now, respect I did give.</p>
<p>I was raised to respect.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>"You're supposed to be my lab partner."</p>
<p>"I am!"</p>
<p>"No, you're not. You're disloyal."</p>
</blockquote>
<p>And it's something I did give and did expect.</p>
<p>And if I didn't receive it, well, then there might be a problem.</p>
<p>But I've learned, as I approach these golden years, to extend grace in the face of disrespect.</p>
<p>At least, I know it on paper.</p>
<p>I'm not batting 1.000 here on the extend grace in the face of disrespect stat line.</p>
<p>But we all gotta start somewhere.</p>
<p>Grace falls from the sky like manna from Heaven.</p>
<p>I've lived many ways.</p>
<p>No grace.</p>
<p>Grace.</p>
<p>Everything in between.</p>
<p>Living on grace is a good way to be.</p>
<p>Respectfully,</p>
<h1>杻백</h1>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Moose Out Front Should Have Told You</title>
        <author>
            <name>杻백</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/moose-out-front-should-have-told-you/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/moose-out-front-should-have-told-you/</id>

        <updated>2026-02-27T13:06:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Today, I want to talk about love. And how, if you&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Today, I want to talk about love.</p>
<p>And how, if you have it, if you are it, how very little else matters.</p>
<p>Now, I don't want to say that I didn't have it growing up.</p>
<p>I did.</p>
<p>It's just I didn't have it <em>present</em>.</p>
<p>My folks worked so hard.</p>
<p>Every day.</p>
<p>They showed love through their sacrifice.</p>
<p>Toiling so that I might some day reap.</p>
<p>All of that to say, I went searching for love, adventure, and trouble alone.</p>
<p>I suppose we all do.</p>
<p>And I'm blessed to say I found it.</p>
<p>So blessed.</p>
<p>It staggers me.</p>
<p>And while I joke about thinking I'd be a monk alone on some mountain top, a part of me is so shocked it went this way.</p>
<p>A family man?</p>
<p>Beloved?</p>
<p>Daddy?</p>
<p>How about that?</p>
<p>I still worry about a lot of things.</p>
<p>But being loved isn't one of them.</p>
<p>I am loved.</p>
<p>And I know it.</p>
<p>I can see it.</p>
<p>I can feel it.</p>
<p>It's such a unique feeling.</p>
<p>Too powerful to even want to write about.</p>
<p>One I didn't expect I wanted or needed.</p>
<p>But I do.</p>
<p>I need something to fight for.</p>
<p>Someone to fight for.</p>
<p>Always have.</p>
<p>But I never thought I needed love.</p>
<p>It was just something you had.</p>
<p>That is until I met my wife.</p>
<p>Until we made our kids.</p>
<p>Their unconditional love feels to me very conditional.</p>
<p>In that, I have to earn it.</p>
<p>Be worthy of it.</p>
<p>Every single day.</p>
<p>Ahh, probably getting a little sentimental in my old(ish) age.</p>
<p>There's a scene in <em>Pulp Fiction</em>, where Travolta and Jackson are sitting in the diner, discussing what their future holds.</p>
<p>And Sam says he is going to walk the earth.</p>
<p>What you mean walk the earth?</p>
<p>You know, like Caine in Kung Fu.</p>
<p>Travel from town to town.</p>
<p>Meet people.</p>
<p>Get in adventures.</p>
<p>And so that's what I did.</p>
<p>But it was a pretty lonely time.</p>
<p>And now, I suppose I still do it.</p>
<p>But I'm never alone.</p>
<p>I got my pride with me.</p>
<p>游부游냞游떂游떁</p>
<p>We roll deep.</p>
<p>All of a sudden I'm Chevy Chase.</p>
<p>On perpetual vacation.</p>
<p>Didn't see that coming.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>I See, I See</title>
        <author>
            <name>杻백</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/i-see-i-see/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/i-see-i-see/</id>

        <updated>2026-02-26T11:49:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Gather round class. Let's all form a circle. And let's sit&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Gather round class.</p>
<p>Let's all form a circle.</p>
<p>And let's sit down on the floor pillows provided to you.</p>
<p>Today, we discuss a topic near and dear to my heart.</p>
<p>We discuss...</p>
<p>Oh, let me open up some windows, get some fresh air.</p>
<p><em>He's stalling again. He's out of ideas.</em></p>
<p>There, let's all take a deep inhale of this wonderful invisible gas.</p>
<p>High quality O2, baby.</p>
<p>Hear those wind chimes?</p>
<p>Got those last week.</p>
<p><em>Yep, definitely stalling. He's so weird.</em></p>
<p>Where was I?</p>
<p>Oh yes, the topic.</p>
<p>Today's topic is on haters.</p>
<p><em>Eeek. Does he know?</em></p>
<p>Now, I've tried, relatively speaking, to keep my chin down and keep to myself.</p>
<p>Still got haters.</p>
<p>I was shy.</p>
<p>Still got haters.</p>
<p>I was aloof.</p>
<p>Still got haters.</p>
<p>I tried new armors.</p>
<p>Tried being overly me (cranked up to 11) and just tried to be a shouty salesy guy.</p>
<p>Still got haters.</p>
<p>Tried to do right.</p>
<p>Tried to do good.</p>
<p>Tried to be just.</p>
<p>Still got haters.</p>
<p>Now, I'm just me.</p>
<p>And so class, what I will offer you today, is that likely in this circle right now is a hater.</p>
<p>Take a look around.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Brothers and sisters, and friends, and I see some enemies...</p>
</blockquote>
<p>And to them, I say, welcome.</p>
<p>I used to think an enemy to my face is more valuable that a false friend behind me.</p>
<p>I suppose I still believe that.</p>
<p>And I still believe what a good friend told me, decades ago, that if the holes of arse are mad at you, you must be doing something right!</p>
<p>Now I confess some good people have rightfully been upset with me, are upset with me, and I regret those tremendously.</p>
<p>Such as I can.</p>
<p>Such is life.</p>
<p>I could have been kinder.</p>
<p>But to the arses, who I have made upset, well it's time to do a little dance.</p>
<p>In your honor.</p>
<p>...[Five minutes later.]...</p>
<p>Good job, everyone.</p>
<p>Deep breaths.</p>
<p>Hear the chimes.</p>
<p>Now, let's all sit down again.</p>
<p>Take a long drink of water.</p>
<p>Appreciate how good that tastes.</p>
<p>Yum.</p>
<p>Hydration.</p>
<p>Hear your heart thumping.</p>
<p>Like a bass drum.</p>
<p>Now look down.</p>
<p>In front of you all are little hand mirrors.</p>
<p>Pick those up.</p>
<p>And tell me what you see.</p>
<p>Friend?</p>
<p>Or enemy?</p>
<p>游녜游녜</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>No Problemo</title>
        <author>
            <name>杻백</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/no-problemo/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/no-problemo/</id>

        <updated>2026-02-25T13:43:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    High quality problems are the best problems. These are the type&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>High quality problems are the best problems.</p>
<p>These are the type of problems one only has when they have a good life. It presumes a good life.</p>
<p>For example, if you spend time thinking about how human beings could ever become starfaring, it presumes you are likely living a life of abundance. Or at least, you have the ability to live in denial.</p>
<p>Lots of good people are struggling with real problems, I won't call them low-quality, but these stink. How will I pay the bills? How will I get my next meal? Where will I lay my head?</p>
<p>These are heartbreakers.</p>
<p>Soulcrushers.</p>
<p>True problems.</p>
<p>Sometimes, you can catch yourself struggling with a high-quality problem.</p>
<p>It can consume you.</p>
<p>And it's important to realize that these are the problems we <em>strive</em> to have.</p>
<p>Where should we put our money? What shall next week's meals be? Should we move?</p>
<p>How do we interstellar travel?</p>
<p>All high-quality problems.</p>
<p>Ones to seek.</p>
<p>May all your problems be high af.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Army Of One</title>
        <author>
            <name>杻백</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/army-of-one/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/army-of-one/</id>

        <updated>2026-02-24T12:16:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    I know what you're thinking. You expect us to come here&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I know what you're thinking.</p>
<p><em>You expect us to come here everyday and read something that only takes you five minutes to write?</em></p>
<p>And to that I retort, "How dare you?"</p>
<p>First of all, I expect no one to read this.</p>
<p>Isn't that obvious?</p>
<p>This is [waves hands all around musings column] for me.</p>
<p>And second of all, I'll have you know it takes six minutes sometimes.</p>
<p>Maybe even seven.</p>
<p>Eight.</p>
<p>You might think I feign outrage when I have nothing to say.</p>
<p>You might think that.</p>
<p>And it might look like that right now.</p>
<p>You dirty son of a...</p>
<p>But you'd be wrong.</p>
<p>I just think in this day and age of everyone trying to sell you something, usually themselves, that me coming here and just writing about farts and love is awesome.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Starfaring</title>
        <author>
            <name>杻백</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/starfaring/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/starfaring/</id>

        <updated>2026-02-23T12:30:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Did you know, you can pay to have someone rocket you&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Did you know, you can pay to have someone rocket you into space after you pass?</p>
<p>I like to think I can dream big.</p>
<p>I like to think that I can picture infinity.</p>
<p>And God, the ultimate big and infinite, is foundational in my brain.</p>
<p>But when I think about interstellar travel, I wrestle with it.</p>
<p>A lot of folks who have the luxury of thinking about such things, think that a human being visiting another planet is one of the integral steps of our continuous survival.</p>
<p>Not just you and me, kid.</p>
<p>The earth and everyone on it.</p>
<p>So the end game (such as it is because it never ends) is to venture towards all the stars in the night's sky.</p>
<p>And go beyond them.</p>
<p>To see what we can't see.</p>
<p>To become a starfaring civilization.</p>
<p>It's the scale of this that's so staggering.</p>
<p>200 billion trillion (sextillion) stars. Of course, there's countless more planets.</p>
<p>But we are talking 2 x 10 to the 23rd power suns.</p>
<p>200,000,000,000,000,000,000,000.</p>
<p>That's a lot of suns.</p>
<p>That's a lot of zeroes.</p>
<p>23 of 'em.</p>
<p>MJ of 'em.</p>
<p>An astronomical amount of stars.</p>
<p>I don't care what you say, though.</p>
<p>Because at that scale, you're just guessing.</p>
<p>I'm just guessing.</p>
<p>The thing that astounds me about space is the vastness.</p>
<p>And this idea that it's empty.</p>
<p>Lifeless.</p>
<p>Mostly.</p>
<p>And I wonder, how can space be so expansive, but so vacant?</p>
<p>Am I missing something?</p>
<p>We are a long way from jet-setting between planets, a longer way from hopping galaxies and universes, and about forever away from taming it all.</p>
<p>Such as it ever could be.</p>
<p>But words are powerful.</p>
<p>Most powerful.</p>
<p><em>Quill over sword.</em></p>
<p>And one of my favorites is <em>starfaring</em>.</p>
<p><em>Traveling among the stars.</em></p>
<p>I just love it.</p>
<p>Oh, and if you're looking for me, you'll know where I will be.</p>
<p>Just tilt your chin up.</p>
<p>Forever,</p>
<p>游눪</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Liner Notes</title>
        <author>
            <name>杻백</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/liner-notes/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/liner-notes/</id>

        <updated>2026-02-22T12:03:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    One of my favorite parts of a good live album or&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>One of my favorite parts of a good live album or concert is the intro, the monologue, the banter.</p>
<p>Sometimes the band's playing a little something in the background, while the singer talks about the song coming up.</p>
<p>When I was young, I didn't like live versions.</p>
<p>I wanted the album version.</p>
<p>And most of the time, the live versions weren't as good.</p>
<p>Poorer sounding.</p>
<p>Vocally or otherwise.</p>
<p>Sometimes, these folks dared changing the lyrics!</p>
<p>Or turned it acoustic!</p>
<p>As I grew up, I learned I was wrong.</p>
<p>I realized how change could be so very magical.</p>
<p>How much play there was in doing it live.</p>
<p>How you can go acoustic, ballad, or electric.</p>
<p>How the same song can feel so different, can play so different, just by changing how you sing it.</p>
<p>And so, I learned that the true measure of a band was not in the safe studio, it was how they did it live.</p>
<p>Did they have a story to tell before certain songs.</p>
<p>Did they evolve it in the time since it's release.</p>
<p>You hear some artists say they hate to sing their hits because it's just the same crap over and over.</p>
<p>It becomes something of a catch phrase.</p>
<p>And I get that, maybe that's why songs do evolve.</p>
<p>To keep it interesting.</p>
<p>The best songs change over time. But they stay the same in spirit.</p>
<p>The best remakes are those that change fast to slow, electric to acoustic. But they stay the same in significance.</p>
<p>And versa vice.</p>
<p>I wish sometimes, that there was a piano playing behind me, while I stand on this stage.</p>
<p>Musing about music.</p>
<p>Sure, I hit some keys of my own, but they aren't the Mariah Carey or Bruce Hornsby kind, more the clicky-clacky.</p>
<p>And I just got to tell you, poetry comes in all forms.</p>
<p>You can read it, you can listen to it, you can see it in motion.</p>
<p>Live and in living color.</p>
<p>But most importantly, you can <em>feel</em> it.</p>
<p>To the bone.</p>
<p>In your heart.</p>
<p>For our souls.</p>
<p>This is for you.</p>
<p>[Cues up the band.]</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
