<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>Iterating</title>
    <link href="https://iterating.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://iterating.com" />
    <updated>2026-01-02T23:05:07-05:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>𖤂</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://iterating.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>High Low There</title>
        <author>
            <name>𖤂</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/high-low-there/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/high-low-there/</id>

        <updated>2026-01-02T17:04:51-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    I had to write again. Can't start 2026 like an absurd&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I had to write again.</p>
<p>Can't start 2026 like an absurd person would.</p>
<p>That was <em>so</em> 2025.</p>
<p>Listen, I got a question:</p>
<p>Do you have to get really low to get really high?</p>
<p>I mean to know what high truly means.</p>
<p>Do you have to be poor to appreciate being wealthy?</p>
<p>Do you have to have your heart broken to treasure and enjoy real love?</p>
<p>I mean, to value it as you should:</p>
<p>Priceless. </p>
<p>If you were born rich, you tend to stay it, and take it for granted.</p>
<p>You wouldn't fully understand its literal value unless you lost it.</p>
<p>Same with love, I think, an always in love, never broken, heart. Seems like that kind of heart would break others' hearts.</p>
<p>You don't appreciate the unlimited power of love until it breaks you or someone close to you.</p>
<p>The more I wrestle with it, the more I am learning that our point of view, our perspective, might be one of the only truly unique things we have.</p>
<p>We all own a unique, one of one, perspective. A set of lenses through which we live.</p>
<p>And as similar as some things may be, you'll find stark differences the further you zoom in.</p>
<p>So the challenge, then, should you choose to accept it is:</p>
<p>Learn from your singular perspective and the infinite of others.</p>
<p>Why do you (and they) see the world the way you (and they [<em>this is the last time I will do the "and they" thing so just put it after every "you" following</em>]) do?</p>
<p>How do you define wealth? Is it good or evil? And why?</p>
<p>How do you define love? Is it good or evil? Do you still believe in it? And why?</p>
<p>How do you define yourself? Are you good or evil? Do you still believe in you? And why?</p>
<p>And, perhaps most importantly, how do you define God? Is God benevolent or malevolent? Did you ever, or do you still, believe? And why?</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>MMXXVI</title>
        <author>
            <name>𖤂</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/mmxxvi/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/mmxxvi/</id>

        <updated>2026-01-02T14:51:19-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Two Ms. Two Xs. A V and an I. That spells&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Two Ms. Two Xs. A V and an I.</p>
<p>That spells Ememexexveeeeye.</p>
<p>Or something.</p>
<p>Rolls off the tongue, don't it?</p>
<p>Apparently, these are numerals but they look like capital letters if you ask me.</p>
<p>I am partial to LX, though.</p>
<p>60. And kinda, sorta, my name.</p>
<p>LX is the new XXIX (was going to say 30, but yeah), so I hear.</p>
<p>When in Rome...</p>
<p>Get ready, people.</p>
<p>Things will start out fast and hot.</p>
<p>I can feel it in my vibes.</p>
<p>May your Ememexexveeeeye be better than your Ememexexveee.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Party Horn</title>
        <author>
            <name>𖤂</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/party-horn/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/party-horn/</id>

        <updated>2026-01-01T11:24:05-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Well, hey. Long time. What's it been, a year? Guffaw. I&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Well, hey.</p>
<p>Long time.</p>
<p>What's it been, a year?</p>
<p><em>Guffaw.</em></p>
<p>I so funny.</p>
<p><em>Guffaws again.</em></p>
<p>Give me a second here.</p>
<p>Ok.</p>
<p>Man, I'm good.</p>
<p>So witty.</p>
<p>So this is my way of starting the new year on this here daily journal thing.</p>
<p>If you're new here, I ramble. Rant. Reason. Revere.</p>
<p>Mostly, this is my mental playground. </p>
<p>Where I get to flip around and jump and flow my brain and finger muscles.</p>
<p>I'd love for you to join me.</p>
<p>Actually, I couldn't care less if you did, it just seems like people say that.</p>
<p>Ooooooooh, honorable reader, will you join my journey, please?</p>
<p>[Farts slowly, loudly, still going...you wonder "How does he do that?" The author, staring at you the whole time, never breaks eye contact. It is almost melodic. And ends on a high note, which, strangely, delights you. You got a few seconds before the smell hits. I would leave.]</p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Ramble, Old Man, Ramble</title>
        <author>
            <name>𖤂</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/ramble-old-man-ramble/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/ramble-old-man-ramble/</id>

        <updated>2025-12-31T11:29:20-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Only been writing again for the last couple of months, but&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Only been writing again for the last couple of months, but it feels like a longer time.</p>
<p>I've been blessed (cursed?) with the ability to stop things I loved doing without missing it much.</p>
<p>I used to define myself by how much I could lift off my chest or over my head.</p>
<p>Always a spiritual sort, I prayed to heavy metal listening to heavy metal.</p>
<p>Found God there (and in a Muay Thai gym).</p>
<p>But I don't do it anymore.</p>
<p>Or at least for now I don't.</p>
<p>And I don't miss it (much).</p>
<p>You'd think I would, because it was a really big part of me, a big part of how I defined myself.</p>
<p>And that's how I kind of feel about writing.</p>
<p>I have written my entire life.</p>
<p>Have always loved the written word.</p>
<p>For a long time, I couldn't read or write anymore.</p>
<p>And that sucked. More than the not lifting thing. Which shocks me, writing that truth.</p>
<p>I started listening to stories and watching them.</p>
<p>And that helped, a lot, but it did not replace writing.</p>
<p>And so, all of that to just say, I'm very thankful to be able to type away again. To meander in my brain and pluck what I find and place it down on digital paper.</p>
<p>To ramble again, if no longer to rumble.</p>
<p>Rumbling is a young man's game.</p>
<p>Writing can be an old man's.</p>
<p>Something to look forward to (no old man here).</p>
<p>This might come across as sort of a down thing, but it's not. </p>
<p>It's the exact opposite.</p>
<p>An up thing.</p>
<p>I'm writing again.</p>
<p>Wrote everyday here since early October.</p>
<p>I'm back, baby!</p>
<p>Or, at least, I am <em>here</em>.</p>
<p>I still get things off my chest, just now in a different form.</p>
<p><em>Lightweight, easy, easy</em>.</p>
<p>What an interesting timeline.</p>
<p>To the last day of a good year.</p>
<p>Happy.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Seconds To Last</title>
        <author>
            <name>𖤂</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/seconds-to-last/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/seconds-to-last/</id>

        <updated>2025-12-30T12:45:26-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    I have always liked that word, "penultimate." Last but one. Second&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I have always liked that word, "penultimate."</p>
<p>Last but one.</p>
<p>Second to last.</p>
<p>The one right before the one before.</p>
<p>Pen...ultimate!</p>
<p>What a cool way to say almost last.</p>
<p>So here we are writing about penultimates.</p>
<p>How goes things?</p>
<p>You good?</p>
<p>You might think my asking about you is just a delay tactic.</p>
<p>A way to avoid writing anything of substance.</p>
<p>And to that I say, "How dare you!?"</p>
<p>You're right of course, but feigned outrage is my way to counter most things.</p>
<p>I got nothing to say, man. I'm still here.</p>
<p>I still believe in magic.</p>
<p>I know how the trick is done.</p>
<p>I know it by heart.</p>
<p>But I still believe in magic.</p>
<p>Watch this day vanish.</p>
<p>Poof!</p>
<p><em>How'd he do that?</em></p>
<p>And then the next one!</p>
<p>Poof!</p>
<p><em>Woah!</em></p>
<p>The whole year gone!</p>
<p>The trick is making the seconds last, even on the second to last.</p>
<p><em>POOF!</em></p>
<p>[The author vanishes in a puff of smoke, caused by a smoke machine which incidentally pumps out dance music from the 90s. Resulting in a dramatic, but not in the way he envisioned, end scene.]</p>
<blockquote>
<p>♫ Is this some Reebok or some Nike? ♫</p>
</blockquote>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Slingshots Slingshots Slingshots</title>
        <author>
            <name>𖤂</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/slingshots-slingshots-slingshots/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/slingshots-slingshots-slingshots/</id>

        <updated>2025-12-29T14:25:20-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    One of the reasons I like to try new things is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>One of the reasons I like to try new things is because after a while, things can start sounding like an echo chamber.</p>
<p>You hear the same things over and over.</p>
<p>The same stuff said in a different way.</p>
<p>Groups agreeing with one another on everything and everyone.</p>
<p>And any ideas to the contrary are disregarded at best.</p>
<p>For me, I could agree with you vehemently on something, but if you keep pounding the idea home, I start to see the contrary views. </p>
<p>Your certainty makes me doubt.</p>
<p>So I stay away from fanatics. </p>
<p>On all sides.</p>
<p>Or, perhaps better said, keep them at a distance.</p>
<p>Some of my favorite ideas are led by people who basically say:</p>
<p>If you don't get it, you're just a moron.</p>
<p>Which, you should know by now, I understand.</p>
<p>Maybe it's the smugness.</p>
<p>Maybe that's why my brain goes, "Well, maybe there is another view here."</p>
<p>I always liked a well-written dissent over the more popular majority opinion.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>"How are you liking the company?"</p>
<p>"Well, this company feels like a Goliath. And I have always been a David guy."</p>
</blockquote>
<p>And maybe that's it.</p>
<p>Maybe if a room feels like it's full of drooling, nodding, giants, I instinctively grab my rounds.</p>
<p>Has the art of cordial disagreement faded away?</p>
<p>Agree to disagree?</p>
<p>Do professors still give out their best grades to students who disagree with their point of view, but do so so articulately and well-reasoned that it deserves a top grade?</p>
<p>My concern is it seems the world is flocking more and more into these silos of safety.</p>
<p>Where everyone in this silo has to think a certain way.</p>
<p>They all say the same things, believe the same things, and if you do not, well then, please see yourself out.</p>
<p>I am proud to say I have very few people I would call true friends. And believe it or not, some of them disagree with me. I know, I know, impossible, you say.</p>
<p>But it's true. They have their own ideas. Their own guidelines. And when I need to hear another side to an angle I am considering, I go there first.</p>
<p>Break this argument.</p>
<p>Shatter it.</p>
<p>What am I missing?</p>
<p>Don't echo.</p>
<p>Counter.</p>
<p>Left jab?</p>
<p>Right straight.</p>
<p>Left headkick?</p>
<p>Right legkick.</p>
<p>Get out of them chambers that have endless mirrors.</p>
<p>Who wants a million versions of themselves looking back at them?</p>
<p><em>Woah, cool.</em></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Fetch</title>
        <author>
            <name>𖤂</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/fetch/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/fetch/</id>

        <updated>2025-12-28T12:52:35-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    One of the things I have always tried to distill is&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>One of the things I have always tried to distill is this idea of success.</p>
<p>What is it?</p>
<p>How do you measure it?</p>
<p>How will you know when you are "successful?"</p>
<p>I mean, does a bell chime or does some little guy dressed as an elf dance at your side when it happens?</p>
<p>I think too many of us measure success by net worth.</p>
<p>And I suppose that's one way to do it.</p>
<p>I grew up with a terrible sense of money.</p>
<p>Didn't have much, didn't need much.</p>
<p>Maybe that's not so terrible.</p>
<p>But what I'm getting at is can you be a great family man <em>and</em> succeed in business?</p>
<p>Who's done that?</p>
<p>And who gets to measure whether you are successful or not?</p>
<p>You, your portfolio, or your family?</p>
<p>And what about your soul, your fortitude, your honor? </p>
<p>Does that matter in the "success" formula?</p>
<p>I mean, ain't that the most important stick?</p>
<p>What I'm getting at is:</p>
<p>Did you have a good year?</p>
<p>And no matter your answer, how are you defining it?</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Everyday We Shuffling</title>
        <author>
            <name>𖤂</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/everyday-we-shuffling/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/everyday-we-shuffling/</id>

        <updated>2025-12-27T13:34:45-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Again, I sit down to write without an idea about what&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Again, I sit down to write without an idea about what to say.</p>
<p>I mean, I got a lot of ideas, but I am holding back on most things.</p>
<p>Some things do not belong on a blog.</p>
<p>But here I am.</p>
<p>So let's get to writing.</p>
<p>First of all, the word "blog" is terrible.</p>
<p>It stinks.</p>
<p>It's like the word, "brand." </p>
<p>Yuck.</p>
<p>But yeah, I do both.</p>
<p>I suppose.</p>
<p>In my own anti-way.</p>
<p>Do it by not doing it right.</p>
<p>Or [waves hands] doing it different.</p>
<p>I'm yelling at people who cut in lines again.</p>
<p>I suppose that's something.</p>
<p>"Line starts back here, boys!"</p>
<p>That is kind of funny to me.</p>
<p>And then no-selling the "Oh, sorry" response.</p>
<p>Like I've moved on entirely.</p>
<p>Which I have.</p>
<p><em>Who is apologizing to me? And for what?</em></p>
<p>Next!</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Get To</title>
        <author>
            <name>𖤂</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/get-to/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/get-to/</id>

        <updated>2025-12-26T13:20:40-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    I sit alone in a four cornered room staring at candles.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <blockquote>
<p>I sit alone in a four cornered room staring at candles.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Oh, is this thing on?</p>
<p>Listen, I hope you had yourself a Merry little Christmas.</p>
<p>And now, you find yourself getting ready to celebrate the end of the old year and to welcome the new.</p>
<p>I should wax on and wax off about ends and beginnings.</p>
<p>But that seems a little too cliche.</p>
<p>Why on earth would I do that?</p>
<p>Everyone does that.</p>
<p>And if you know a little something about me, I don't do what everyone does.</p>
<p>So here's what I will say.</p>
<p>Most of them out there are going to be lazy these last few days.</p>
<p>So there's opportunity in being especially active now.</p>
<p>While the others are celebrating, it is a great time to put in the work.</p>
<p>Sure, it's only a couple of days, but maybe you strike gold, while everyone else is drinking it.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Just remember, they can buy anything. But they can't buy backbone. Don't let them forget that.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>And I know, I know, this is for like one person out of the millions (thousands, hundreds, dozens, handful) who read this nonsense.</p>
<p>But yes, this is for <em>you</em>, friend.</p>
<p>My words have never been for the crowd.</p>
<p>Just for the ones who can keep their heads.</p>
<p>I see you, back row, left side. On your feet. Clapping. Hollering. Underlining.</p>
<p>This is for you.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Ho Ho Hoes</title>
        <author>
            <name>𖤂</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/ho-ho-hoes/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/ho-ho-hoes/</id>

        <updated>2025-12-25T15:28:43-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Merry Christmas. That was going to be it. But let's keep&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Merry Christmas.</p>
<p>That was going to be it.</p>
<p>But let's keep it going.</p>
<p>To those hurting in these times, I want to send a special message.</p>
<p>And to those in a great place, I also want to share the same message.</p>
<p><em>This, too, shall pass.</em></p>
<p>To those low, just <em>survive</em>.</p>
<p>And to those high, just <em>bless</em>.</p>
<p>Or maybe it's the reverse.</p>
<p>I forget.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
