<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>Iterating</title>
    <link href="https://iterating.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://iterating.com" />
    <updated>2025-12-04T16:26:13-05:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>AL8X</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://iterating.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Iterating...</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/iterating/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/iterating/</id>

        <updated>2025-12-04T16:21:08-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    I'm writing again today. Just to see if I can do&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I'm writing again today. Just to see if I can do it.</p>
<p>I wonder how sustainable it is to just type by feel. </p>
<p>Don't get me wrong, I can still see. I'm fine.</p>
<p>It's just typing on my computer has suddenly turned... off.</p>
<p>I think I have sensitivity to certain screens. Too much flashing/refreshing/wa wah.</p>
<p>As someone who loves tech, this is a bit of a bummer. But I'm going to roll with it. I'm in no shape to complain. I just will figure a work around.</p>
<p>Closing my eyes to type is the first workaround.</p>
<p>Writing by feel.</p>
<p>I've been a bit under the weather so that's probably the reason.</p>
<p>Who knows.</p>
<p>What I know is that this writing thing is wired into my OS and I'm not going to stop over some vision thing.</p>
<p>I wish I had something more to say it's just not going to happen until I get into a groove with this eyes closed typing thing.</p>
<p>Living up to this site's domain name.</p>
<p>Test. Feedback. Update. Test.</p>
<p>I used to only want to be perfect. Never fail. This made me not try the harder things. Or prepare for them.</p>
<p>This was the weakness of my youth. </p>
<p>I can write blind.</p>
<p>I will write blind.</p>
<p>But I can see.</p>
<p>See?</p>
<p>The only way to get to perfect is to fail. Over and over.</p>
<p>You can't stop this ess. This thing overflowing.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>By Feels</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/by-feels/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/by-feels/</id>

        <updated>2025-12-04T11:34:53-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Perhaps, I have figured out a way to keep writing. I&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Perhaps, I have figured out a way to keep writing.</p>
<p>I took a typing class in eight grade that changed my life.</p>
<p>We all worked on big mechanical metal typewriters and we learned by starting with the individual keys covered with little white stickers.</p>
<p>We learned to type by feel. Not sight. Well, I think we had an overhead projector that showed where the keys were, but we couldn't look down at the keys for help.</p>
<p>We had to train our fingers to know which letters they were responsible for.</p>
<p>The pinkies had the least responsibility, whereas the index and middle got the brunt.</p>
<p>Anyways, my point being, perhaps I can type with my eyes closed.</p>
<p>I can peek at the keys but I know when my fingers strike true.</p>
<p>This is not an ideal way to write, but I somehow feel more attuned to writing this way.</p>
<p>My eyes aren't fighting the screen, I'm keeping them mostly closed, just my fingers hunting the board. I know this seems like a cruel twist of fate, but I have learned we just never know what's going to happen and that there is no sustained new normals.</p>
<p>Only seasons. Windows of time.</p>
<p>Take nothing for granted.</p>
<p>I can type this way. Not sure how great I'll write. But I suppose you could have asked that all along.</p>
<p>I can write with my eyes closed. What a blessing that is. I hope to share more substantive stuff in the near future. But forgive me any typos. </p>
<p>The key to typing by feel is knowing where you are. I touch my index fingers together to make sure they are aligned and in the right position. Otherwise, it's anarchy.</p>
<p>What I am learning is that I must write. If only for myself. And some times, many times, all the time, when you must have something, you are tested.</p>
<p>So, I suppose, this is some sort of test.</p>
<p>That's ok. </p>
<p>And, as I have learned to say, even in nonoptimal conditions, what does this make possible?</p>
<p>I just realized, for the first time ever, that the "j" and "f" keys (where your index fingers rest), have a little notch at the bottom. None of the other keys do. I think this is so you know where to orient them. Where to rest them.</p>
<p>I remember doing that now. When learning to type. I would peel a corner of a sticker for each hand, so I could feel a certain letter. I'd peel the corner up on "a" and "l" keys so I knew where they were by feel, fi not by sight.</p>
<p>Have "f" and "j" always been so distinguished? Weird, I never noticed.</p>
<p>I will now. </p>
<p>All because I starting writing by feel.</p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Fun While It Lasted</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/fun-while-it-lasted/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/fun-while-it-lasted/</id>

        <updated>2025-12-03T15:09:12-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    My vision is different. I wish I could say this was&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>My vision is different.</p>
<p>I wish I could say this was me being deep and mystical.</p>
<p>But all this writing has made my vision sharper but different.</p>
<p>This started two days ago.</p>
<p>I can still write, and I still plan to, but it's a bit more difficult now.</p>
<p>Strange, right?</p>
<p>Ah well, it's this new avatar.</p>
<p>Things don't work like they used to or work differently.</p>
<p>Good and bad. Like all things.</p>
<p>For a while, then, the writing may slow or stop.</p>
<p>Until I can heal.</p>
<p>Or find a new way to write.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Long Decembers</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/long-decembers/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/long-decembers/</id>

        <updated>2025-12-02T12:15:18-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Would we love December if it didn't have Christmas and New&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Would we love December if it didn't have Christmas and New Year's Eve in it?</p>
<p>I don't know.</p>
<p>The last month of the year.</p>
<p>The unofficial (early) and official start of winter.</p>
<p>It can be a busy time and a chill time.</p>
<p>It is time to put a bow on it and other objects.</p>
<p>To wrap up the year and presents in celebration.</p>
<p>This was a good year.</p>
<p>Maybe next year will be better than the last.</p>
<p>To holding on to moments.</p>
<p>And letting them go.</p>
<p>To long Decembers.</p>
<p>And new years.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Peaks and Plateaus</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/peaks-and-plateaus/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/peaks-and-plateaus/</id>

        <updated>2025-12-01T13:59:50-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Most of us, especially our young ones, seek the peak experience.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Most of us, especially our young ones, seek the <em>peak</em> experience.</p>
<p>The high spots.</p>
<p>The highlights.</p>
<p>The explosive.</p>
<p>Anyone can see glimmers of this with their own two eyes, their heart, their soul. The select few have tasted it, breathed it, and lived it.</p>
<p>And almost like a drug, you can spend an eternity trying to recapture that initial experience. Chasing fleeting moments like ghost hares. Trying to snatch that rabbit's foot one more time.</p>
<p>More rare, and more rewarding, I have learned, is the <em>plateau</em> experience (a terrible name, btw - we will rename it) signifying a prolonged experience of elevated and profound joy.</p>
<p>An ability like this is earned over a lifetime. Meaning, with few exceptions in an already exceptional few, this is a superpower reserved for those who have accumulated a good amount of yesterdays.</p>
<p>As we grow older, the wise say, we should stop chasing Alpha Centauri, and just learn to appreciate how beautiful the full moon is.</p>
<p>Still celestial, still infinite, still divine, just with a more sustainable point of view.</p>
<p>Peaks are awesome. But plateaus can be forever.</p>
<p>And if I have to choose, I choose forever.</p>
<p>But I'm just getting old.</p>
<p>Hit a lot of peaks. Fell in more valleys.</p>
<p>Right now, I'll just enjoy the view.</p>
<p>...</p>
<p>They say you have to die a little to be truly reborn.</p>
<p>I feel that ess, to the bone.</p>
<p>I died a little.</p>
<p>And I am new.</p>
<p>I hear the moon will be beautiful tonight.</p>
<p>But Alpha Centauri calls.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Todays</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/todays/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/todays/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-30T00:42:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    This show I was watching, a documentary of sorts, showed a&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>This show I was watching, a documentary of sorts, showed a dad talking about his daughter.</p>
<p>You could tell this man loved his daughter. You could see it in his eyes.</p>
<p>And he sweetly recalled telling her over the years, time and time again, that he's got a lot more yesterdays than she does. But, and more importantly, she has a lot more tomorrows.</p>
<p>This wasn't a happy show, because he shares this knowing his daughter has passed on, and he says he's now living with only yesterdays. No more tomorrows for him.</p>
<p>And I feel his pain.</p>
<p>I found his story profoundly touching.</p>
<p>How we have a (predetermined?) allotment of yesterdays and tomorrows.</p>
<p>I have a lot of yesterdays in my life. I'd like to think I have a bunch of tomorrows coming. Same for my loved ones. Especially those with not a lot of yesterdays racked up. A whole mountain of tomorrows. A starfaring stack of 'em.</p>
<p>But we simply do not know.</p>
<p>I don't know.</p>
<p>I only hope.</p>
<p>I wish.</p>
<p>I pray.</p>
<p>And I know there is so much truth in a life <em>well</em> lived being worth far more than a life <em>long</em> lived. </p>
<p>But I wish more than anything, as a father, for far more tomorrows for my children than I have had yesterdays. And that someday, they remember their yesterdays as being as sweet as my todays.</p>
<p>They say only the good die young, and I believe that (to some degree), but that doesn't mean the good can't die old.</p>
<p><em>Only</em> the good die young.</p>
<p>Not <em>all</em> of the good.</p>
<p><em>Some</em> good die old.</p>
<p>This, like many things, makes me so grateful for the right nows.</p>
<p>To the well lived, long life.</p>
<p>And to yesterdays, tomorrows, and everything in between.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>What, You My Master Now?</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/what-you-my-master-now/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/what-you-my-master-now/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-29T14:05:05-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    I used to really get a kick out of commencement speeches.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I used to really get a kick out of commencement speeches.</p>
<p>The whole idea fascinated me.</p>
<p>Distilling your life's lessons into one speech in front of bored students.</p>
<p>To provide the future of the world with our best, carefully curated, nuggets of accumulated wisdom.</p>
<p>So I would watch them.</p>
<p>And try to be an eternal student.</p>
<p>I suppose I should again.</p>
<p>Haven't watched one in years.</p>
<p>I heard a line the other day that I really enjoyed.</p>
<p>That old line about when the student is ready, the master appears.</p>
<p>But they added a line.</p>
<p>When the student is <em>truly</em> ready, the master disappears.</p>
<p>I dig it.</p>
<p>When the student is ready, the master appears.</p>
<p>When the student is <em>truly</em> ready...</p>
<p>Poof.</p>
<p>...</p>
<p>Just kidding, still here!</p>
<p>We got work to do, kids.</p>
<p>COMMENCE!</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Curations</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/curations/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/curations/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-28T00:57:35-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    I'm no history buff, but I can lift the past once&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I'm no history buff, but I can lift the past once in a while.</p>
<p>In 1776, the newly formed US of A was fighting for its life.</p>
<p>And like many startups, it was badly in need of funding.</p>
<p>So what did they do?</p>
<p>Well, what they do now.</p>
<p>They started to print money.</p>
<p>One of the first coins they made was the continental dollar.</p>
<p>It wasn't officially a dollar but that's what we call it today.</p>
<p>The reason I ramble about this coin is that it had a typo on the front.</p>
<p>It read in part "Continental Curency" with only one "r" in currency.</p>
<p>The coin now, should you find a real one, is worth a small fortune.</p>
<p>But there's wisdom in this "typo."</p>
<p>Curency.</p>
<p><em>CURE</em>ncy.</p>
<p>It almost looks more correct, doesn't it?</p>
<p>We need one of those today.</p>
<p>A solution to the money problem. </p>
<p>Although the accepted reason was that the designer simply ran out of space, I'd like to think they designed the 1776 continental dollar in the way it should have been.</p>
<p>In the year the US declared its independence, it decided to start a curency.</p>
<p>The study of money is a fascinating one. And anyone who does can see where we're headed. And for all that future, and from all that's passed, we certainly require a cure.</p>
<p>And see.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Given Thanks</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/given-thanks/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/given-thanks/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-27T20:18:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    On a day of thanks, thanks should be given. So here,&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>On a day of thanks, thanks should be given.</p>
<p>So here, take my thanks.</p>
<p>I bequeath it to you.</p>
<p>...</p>
<p>I don't have much to say today. </p>
<p>Just impossibly thankful.</p>
<p>For a good second.</p>
<p>For a good minute.</p>
<p>For a good hour.</p>
<p>For a good day.</p>
<p>For a good week.</p>
<p>For a good month.</p>
<p>For a good year.</p>
<p>For the best life.</p>
<p>Stay spicy, my friends.</p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Jive Turkeys</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/jive-turkeys/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/jive-turkeys/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-26T13:50:04-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Someone once said to me: "You're so different!" Or something to&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Someone once said to me: "You're so different!" Or something to that effect.</p>
<p>They didn't mean it as an insult, quite the opposite. But it's happened. A lot. And I would always have some derivative of the same response, "What are you? <em>Normal?!?</em>"</p>
<p>And I'd scoff and sneer at the "Normal" part. Almost like it felt disdainful to even say the word.</p>
<p><em>Normal</em>.</p>
<p>Eww.</p>
<p>Who wants to be that?</p>
<p>I sure didn't.</p>
<p>Although I will admit, normal is getting pretty weird these days, it's still not what I want to be.</p>
<p>It's not who I am.</p>
<p>I figure the people who find this silly place will only understand me if they understand this post. If they <em>get</em> it.</p>
<p>Normal sucks.</p>
<p>There I said it.</p>
<p>Happy Thanksgiving Eve!</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
