<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>Iterating</title>
    <link href="https://iterating.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://iterating.com" />
    <updated>2025-10-26T23:23:06-04:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>AL8X</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://iterating.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Both Can Be True</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/both-can-be-true/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/both-can-be-true/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-26T23:22:39-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Almost forgot to write today. I mean, I did forget. But&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Almost forgot to write today. I mean, I did forget.</p>
<p>But no time like the present.</p>
<p>My goal is to write at least once a day. And while no one's really paying attention, I'm paying attention. That means something, at least to me. Maybe someone in the future, too.</p>
<p>If you ever have the good fortune to love someone, my goodness, what a thing.</p>
<p>And the thing about love is it makes you stronger and weaker at the same time. </p>
<p>Love gives you strength beyond measure, but it can also leave you so vulnerable in many ways.</p>
<p>Heartbreaks are audible, visceral, and as true as any compound fracture. And I'm not just talking romantic ones. It's about affection and concern. Strength and weakness.</p>
<p>I don't know why I write about love today -- who knows why I write about anything.</p>
<p>I've been hearing a lot of people are giving up on love, which just seems foolish.</p>
<p>Love seems reserved for only those of flesh and bone. Will ai ever know love?</p>
<p>Humans can fall in love with anything.</p>
<p>Strength and weakness.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>New Dog, Old Tricks</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/new-dog-old-tricks/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/new-dog-old-tricks/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-25T18:22:11-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    There's a part of me that grew up with this idea&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>There's a part of me that grew up with this idea of fair fights.</p>
<p>Generally speaking, it was one versus one, no outside interference, and you played by a set of rules. No hitting the spinal column, eye balls, balls balls.</p>
<p>You know, fair fights.</p>
<p>But to those who are not yet fully formed, or those who are and were given a size, age, or health disadvantage (relative to their opponent(s)), there is no such thing as a fair fight.</p>
<p>Every fight is unfair. Already in favor of the other side.</p>
<p>We can do things like train and learn techniques and what not.</p>
<p>But big can usually beat little.</p>
<p>Usually.</p>
<p>One of the ways it sometimes doesn't is by changing it into a fair fight.</p>
<p>Kicking groins. Gouging eyes. Elbowing spines.</p>
<p>Pocket sand!</p>
<p>You know, fighting "dirty"? But to me, that's not fighting dirty. That's fighting fair.</p>
<p>Real life ain't the UFC or boxing.</p>
<p>I suppose there is the law. But that's the only rules. </p>
<p>If someone is trying to kill you, you should be prepared to fight to the death.</p>
<p>And should you ever find yourself unarmed and in a fight, remember that the easiest ways to win are:</p>
<p>1) Explosive, angry, force. I mean animal mean. The will to fight and do so violently is incredibly underrated. Who wants to contend with a pissed-off yellow jacket?; and/or</p>
<p>2) Tire them out. Most people aren't trained to fight for any length of time. If you can handle their initial wind, there usually isn't enough time for them to get their second. Fatigue and cowards, you know. This is the downside of Point 1.</p>
<p>Oh, and this probably wouldn't work as well to those with extensive training.</p>
<p>But yeah, like most fights, the best way to win is just to avoid them.</p>
<p>Woof.</p>
<p>DISCLAIMER: I am a man of peace. Do not fight, people. Follow the law. And absolutely, positively, defend yourself and your loved ones.</p>
<p>There is no honor in violent encounters, but there is in you.</p>
<p>Good, Dog.</p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Fall</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/fall/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/fall/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-24T22:42:01-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    What a wonderful time of year. Color changes. Perky cool winds.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>What a wonderful time of year.</p>
<p>Color changes. Perky cool winds. Favorite hoodies.</p>
<p>Falls seem shorter now. </p>
<p>There's always nostalgia in my blood during these months.</p>
<p>I'm blessed with the ability to focus on my best memories. Like how we only listen to our favorite band's best songs and forget their worst.</p>
<p>Skip. Skip. Aww sookie.</p>
<p>And fall is a wonderful season to reminisce. </p>
<p>Winter is unforgiving, but autumn is more of a listener.</p>
<p>May all your falls be short ones.</p>
<p>To autumn and everything after.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Bodies of Water</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/bodies-of-water/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/bodies-of-water/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-23T16:08:25-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    I'm a peninsula guy, I see that now. NYC (yeah yeah,&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I'm a peninsula guy, I see that now.</p>
<p>NYC (yeah yeah, it's an island, work with me here I'm making a point). Great Lakes. The Bay. Korea.</p>
<p>I like and have always liked being by the water.</p>
<p>I like being close to water because it soothes my fire. It cools it down. Let's me relax. But I'm careful to never let it put it out.</p>
<p>My whole life, bodies of water have called to me. And yet, I don't really get in. It's the city boy in me. I like to sit by it. Feel that cool breeze. Watch my loved ones revel and frolic in it. </p>
<p>It is my opposite, water is. And as such, I respect it so. And while I draw near it, I always keep it a bit away.</p>
<p>This is why the peninsula is my way. It juts out into the water, even surrounds itself in it, but it is always rooted into the mainland. Sticks its head and neck out, but maintains a firm foundation. A solid plan, as plans go.</p>
<p>I remember the first time I saw the Pacific Ocean.</p>
<p>It's ferocity humbled me; I stood in awe of it. How it smashed and swept what it wanted to, paying no mind to the little dot of H2O and fire watching it.</p>
<p>I'm more of a lake guy, now.</p>
<p>If you think it's because I'm getting older, you're probably right. And because the fire's not as bright. This makes my life easier. Easier and better. </p>
<p>Oceans, lakes, humans. My favorite bodies of water (not necessarily in that order).</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Go Out There and Sling It</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/go-out-there-and-sling-it/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/go-out-there-and-sling-it/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-22T14:31:50-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Ever heard of Tom Brady, Jr.? Owns a piece of the&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Ever heard of Tom Brady, Jr.?</p>
<p>Owns a piece of the Raiders and some baseball card stores? </p>
<p>Well, before all that glitz and glamour, the kid played football.</p>
<p>But it didn't start all sunshines and rainbows.</p>
<p>First, he had to get drafted.</p>
<p>So draft day came, and he sat with his parents at home and waited.</p>
<p>And waited.</p>
<p>And waited.</p>
<p>It got so bad he had to go take a walk, his parents by his side, as they tried to soothe and console their pride and joy.</p>
<p>Ever proud, though not so joyful. Because their son was at his lowest.</p>
<p>And then the call came. Pick 199! Half-dozen QBs taken before him.</p>
<p>And his father's reaction?</p>
<p>"We were <strong><em>jubilant</em></strong>."</p>
<p>Maybe things would have turned out better for Tom if he'd have been drafted higher.</p>
<p>I mean, minority owner? C'mon. Card shops? Who would pay for cardboard?</p>
<p>What sticks with me here is I've always admired his parents.</p>
<p>In a day and age, now and then, where many would be heartbroken or outraged, his parents were jubilant.</p>
<p>What a magical word.</p>
<p>Jubilant.</p>
<p>I want you to use that word today to describe something you feel.</p>
<p>And I want you to mean it.</p>
<p>To Tom Brady, Sr.</p>
<p>My hero.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>More Human Than Human</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/more-human-than-human/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/more-human-than-human/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-21T14:51:35-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Have you heard about this new fangled thing called Artificial Intelligence?&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Have you heard about this new fangled thing called Artificial Intelligence?</p>
<p>No?</p>
<p>It's all the rage with kids and old people. I fit somewhere in the middle. It might just catch on.</p>
<p>And I have to admit, it's got a lot of utility.</p>
<p>Just this past week, I had it rediscover (for me) a Korean singer in the 80s/90s. I was K-Poppin' before K-Poppin' was cool.</p>
<p>Anyway, AI is like a personal assistant who you task with an assignment that would normally take hours, days, or weeks and instead it completes it almost instantly. Sure, it's wrong more than we like, but that comes with everything.</p>
<p>Perfection eludes even (and especially) code.</p>
<p>Oh, and the price is right. One of the perks of this race towards AGI is that companies are losing huge amounts just to gain users like us. Of course, we are helping train it, feeding and fattening it up. But nothing in the world is free (except our souls).</p>
<p>It seems like more than ever, the program is starting to sound real.</p>
<p>And if it can do most of our tasks, what is left for humans?</p>
<p>Are we all supplied a universal basic income and left to pursue our dreams?</p>
<p>Can you buy a fleet of robots that work for you? You buy a robot that companies hire, paying you their salary?</p>
<p>You see where I'm headed?</p>
<p>It seems naive to not believe our future is somewhat dystopian.</p>
<p>Some might say it is already here.</p>
<p>But I think there's always a lot of value in contemplating what it means to be a human being right now and in this near future.</p>
<p>I don't know. All this is from a rusty brain, writing with rusty muscles. Rambles. Iterations. But I don't hallucinate.</p>
<p>We are now able to upload a person's image, writings, voice recordings and recreate them. Add in tangible robots or VR headsets, and you can almost have everyone you have ever wanted in your life, in your life.</p>
<p>Sure, it wouldn't be them, but you wouldn't be able to tell the difference.</p>
<p>Or would you?</p>
<p>And if you could, would you even care?</p>
<p>I had this idea once about contact lenses you put on that would put you in another world. You would put them on and suddenly be in another timeline. And the idea being, if that world was better than this one, would you ever take the contacts off?</p>
<p>If dreams were for sale, which ones would you buy?</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Hippos</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/hippos/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/hippos/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-20T14:35:32-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Have you ever run into someone who recommended a book, like&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Have you ever run into someone who recommended a book, like highly, and then you read the book, only to have come to the conclusion that the person recommending this book does nothing (and often opposite of what) the book recommends?</p>
<p>I'm talking books that range as high as the Bible to as low as the latest hyped "best seller" in self-help / business. </p>
<p>"Oh, you gotta read this."</p>
<p>You do. And then you think. Huh. Did this mothereffer read a single page? Is this opposite day?</p>
<p>People who portray themselves as one thing, who purport to walk a certain way, have to face a cold reality that the ones who truly know them, who are closest to them, know whether it's all congruent with their true nature -- or just a way to posture.</p>
<p>Bah. It is as it always was.</p>
<p>And it's always the ones you suspect the most.</p>
<p>Happy Monday!</p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Bet</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/bet/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/bet/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-19T17:49:26-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Guys like to gamble. I generalize, but we do. And the&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Guys like to gamble. I generalize, but we do.</p>
<p>And the most common ways are to bet on yourself, bet on future outcomes, and bet on things to go up (or down).</p>
<p>Unfortunately, social class only changes the type of wagering people do.</p>
<p>From the scratch-offs at your local gas station to hedge fund long and shorts, everyone seems to have something they stake money on for the chance of multiplying their input.</p>
<p>The best kind of wager is something called an asymmetric bet.</p>
<p>It's usually because you hold an edge in knowledge. And take a relatively small risk for an often exponential potential output.</p>
<p>But rather than the traditionally proportionately small chance of winning, an asymmetric bet gives you a higher than predicted success rate.</p>
<p>So, still the same moonshots, but with a greater chance of hitting.</p>
<p>We all should know the best gambles are those we take in ourselves. We are asymmetric gambles. A little bit of time and attention can yield lifelong rewards.</p>
<p>I used to be the all in guy. I'd follow Rudyard Kipling's advice. </p>
<p>But I'm old(er) now. </p>
<p>No more risking it all on one turn of pitch-and-toss.</p>
<p>Instead, I look for unbalanced ideas and investments of time and attention. There are so many out there. </p>
<p>To asymmetric opportunities and outcomes and those who still believe in them.</p>
<p>Ours is the world.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Danger Danger</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/danger-danger/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/danger-danger/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-18T13:47:32-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    I remember a line that goes something like, you know you&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I remember a line that goes something like, you know you are old when young men no longer find you dangerous.</p>
<p>You know, spidey senses tingling, tapping their friends to get their attention, and getting out of the way (or getting ready to fight).</p>
<p>It gets me to think about being older, kinder, gentler.</p>
<p>I always try to think, even in the most negative of times, "What does this make possible?"</p>
<p>There is strength in appearing weak. </p>
<p>There is power in being dismissed.</p>
<p>There is freedom in being unnoticed.</p>
<p>Too much of my youth was spent trying to be seen. In my own way. But it's true.</p>
<p>Wisdom teaches you not to feed the wild animals, otherwise, they follow you home.</p>
<p>Keyboards and warriors.</p>
<p>Look out!</p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>It&#x27;s A Good Deal</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/its-a-good-deal/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/its-a-good-deal/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-17T18:06:26-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    You tired of all the bad news? Here is some good.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>You tired of all the bad news?</p>
<p>Here is some good.</p>
<p>I admit it, I used to love buying the latest tech. </p>
<p>And best usually means expensive.</p>
<p>Cheap tech used to suck.</p>
<p>But is that changing/changed?</p>
<p>You can find incredible stuff now that's a downright bargain, especially in electronics. </p>
<p>Heck, if you can wait, buying older but still viable tech is a downright steal.</p>
<p>And you know, I love me a good deal.</p>
<p>There's lots of companies in the tech space producing excellent products and services for a wonderful price.</p>
<p>The floor is rising on quality and performance. But the price is staying (relatively) in the basement. </p>
<p>Where else can you say that?</p>
<p>And when does good and budget beat best and pricy?</p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
