<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>Iterating</title>
    <link href="https://iterating.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://iterating.com" />
    <updated>2025-11-06T00:50:17-05:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>AL8X</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://iterating.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Advice</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/advice/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/advice/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-06T00:50:17-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Drake Maye is the quarterback for the New England Patriots. He&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Drake Maye is the quarterback for the New England Patriots.</p>
<p>He said something the other day that I thought relevant.</p>
<p>He said "All the praise when you're successful and all the hatred when things go bad...Don't take criticism from someone you wouldn't take advice from."</p>
<p>It reminds me of a quote from an old friend.</p>
<p>"If the A-holes are mad at you, you're doing something right."</p>
<p>Today's world gives microphones and megaphones to voices of varying value and values.</p>
<p>Pick your mentors.</p>
<p>Pick your enemies.</p>
<p>May they never cross.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Find Me Later</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/find-me-later/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/find-me-later/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-05T19:07:22-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Say what you want about Google, but they are a verb.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Say what you want about Google, but they are a verb.</p>
<p>And the thing that struck me about their founders was what they said early on. Back before they dominated. When they were just search. And wondering how to monetize it.</p>
<p>As they were just beginning, as they were just gaining traction, they said something really interesting.</p>
<p>They said: The later you discover us, the better.</p>
<p>Meaning, they wanted people to find out about Google later. </p>
<p>Why?</p>
<p>Because the team believed the later you found them, the better they would be. Their first impression would be more impressive.</p>
<p>In a world where most people want it and they want it now, there are still some of us who are like yeah, I got work to do, find me later.</p>
<p>Find me later.</p>
<p>I'm not saying I'd be better, but the later you find me, the better.</p>
<p>I got so much work to do.</p>
<p>But I'm trying. I'm trying real hard, Ringo.</p>
<p>To be the shepherd.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Testing</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/testing-3/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/testing-3/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-05T19:05:35-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    123. Type check. Will this update? I continue to tinker on&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>123.</p>
<p>Type check.</p>
<p>Will this update?</p>
<p>I continue to tinker on this thing. </p>
<p>Trying to learn every day.</p>
<p>Will this work? </p>
<p>Let's find out!</p>
<p>Remember those days when we'd have to knock the side of the television to get it to work?</p>
<p>Technology is always improving, but you can't thump it anymore.</p>
<p>It's unthumpable.</p>
<p>And there are times when it just don't make sense. When the urge to thump rises.</p>
<p>And you got to adjust, you gotta tinker. I would say iterate, but yeah, that's not the right word.</p>
<p>Clouds and locals. </p>
<p>Syncs and backups.</p>
<p>Fixed this issue, it seems, but it really wasn't an issue.</p>
<p>Just redundancy.</p>
<p>A Plan B.</p>
<p>Two is one, you know.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Sniff</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/sniff/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/sniff/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-04T18:50:59-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    You smell that? Something in the air. Something big is coming.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>You smell that?</p>
<p>Something in the air.</p>
<p>Something big is coming.</p>
<p>Oh, and I farted.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Sheet</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/sheet/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/sheet/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-03T14:37:11-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    I think people should have character sheets. Resumes suck. Character sheets&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I think people should have character sheets.</p>
<p>Resumes suck.</p>
<p>Character sheets are cool.</p>
<p>Ability scores. Hit points. Levels. Classes. Alignment. Weapons. Armor. Magic items.</p>
<p>Why save that sweet nectar for the fictional?</p>
<p>So that's what I would encourage you to do today.</p>
<p>Create your own character sheet. For you.</p>
<p>And keep updating it, iterating(!) it, as you go through this campaign called life.</p>
<p>To leveling up, forever.</p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Nails and Unicorns</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/nails-and-unicorns/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/nails-and-unicorns/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-02T12:17:48-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Every decision you have ever made, good or bad, has put&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Every decision you have ever made, good or bad, has put you right here. </p>
<p>To where you are right now.</p>
<p>If you're happy with where you are right now, it's hard to have regrets.</p>
<p>Every downturn led to an up, every up to a down. Sometimes they stack.</p>
<p>It's the downturn stacks you must avoid. Loss on loss on loss.</p>
<p>Upturn stacks are sacred. Gain on gain on gain.</p>
<p>Exponential works both ways.</p>
<p>But they happen. For want of nails or unicorns.</p>
<p>We've all been through it. If you haven't yet, you will.</p>
<p>And if you really think about it, every gain and every loss has also provided an accompanying loss and gain as well.</p>
<p>Yin and yang. Bad in good. Good in bad.</p>
<p>The real questions are:</p>
<p>What do we lose in gain?</p>
<p>And what do we gain in loss?</p>
<p>Hope you find your nail, even if you have to step on it.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>V5.0</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/v50/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/v50/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-01T15:25:48-04:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    One thing they don't tell you about life is that if&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>One thing they don't tell you about life is that if you live long enough you go through different versions of yourself.</p>
<p>The first version is your childhood. Large and small iterations as you turn older. Teen. Young adult. Professional. Parent. Grandparent. Retired. Professional amateur. Etc.</p>
<p>The way I figure it, I'm at version 5.0.</p>
<p>I'm not saying it's better than previous versions (yes, I am), but there's things that have been refined, things removed, and things added.</p>
<p>Like all major updates.</p>
<p>There's been a lot of hours upping my wisdom score and a lot less time in the weight room (not many centenarians walking around at 220 pounds). More long walks (for me).</p>
<p>Oh, and there's the fact that version 4.something almost died.</p>
<p>There's that, too.</p>
<p>Anyways, that's what I'll leave you with.</p>
<p>This idea that we're always changing.</p>
<p>I don't think people tell people this enough.</p>
<p>You don't stay the exact same your whole life. </p>
<p>There are different phases. Seasons. Versions.</p>
<p>You just keep iterating.</p>
<p>Iterating.</p>
<p>That's kind of the whole thing we're doing, right?</p>
<p>Huh.</p>
<p>Mental note.</p>
<p>To versions past, present and future.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Au Contraire</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/au-contraire/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/au-contraire/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-31T13:18:50-04:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    I am sort of a contrarian. In some things. There's headlines&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I am sort of a contrarian. In some things.</p>
<p>There's headlines all over the place of heinous crimes done and thwarted.</p>
<p>This is the history of our world, but it sure seems like a lot of them lately. A literal doom scroll.</p>
<p>And one of the things you see all the time is, such and such happened.</p>
<p>Tragedy happened.</p>
<p>Or, better, tragedy narrowly averted.</p>
<p>We got 'em.</p>
<p>There is no danger to the public.</p>
<p>Go about your day.</p>
<p>Nothing to see here, people.</p>
<p>It's the "no danger" part that makes me chuckle.</p>
<p>This illusion that hey, yeah a group of bad people were going to do a lot of not good, but we caught them all (we think, we're still looking into it), so go on about your business.</p>
<p>It's the oxygen mask falling down in a doomed air flight.</p>
<p>This reassurance of safety that to me is not so reassuring.</p>
<p>Of course, this is done for many reasons, some of them strategic.</p>
<p>Mostly, I think it's done to keep us in our little bubbles of same.</p>
<p>So what do I do?</p>
<p>I know that's what you're wondering.</p>
<p>Well, I'll tell you what I do.</p>
<p>You wanna know?</p>
<p>Really?</p>
<p>I suppose that's why you're here.</p>
<p>Okay, I tell my family, when the going gets tough, when the ess is hitting the proverbs, whatever you do, whatever happens: Panic!*</p>
<p>That's what I tell them.</p>
<p>"Whatever you do: Panic!"</p>
<p>We laugh and laugh.</p>
<p>It always brings light to a dark hypothetical.</p>
<p>I think these "no danger to the public" lines bring hypothetical lights to dark truths.</p>
<p>And you can't see in the dark, mon frere.</p>
<p>Especially with hypothetical lights.</p>
<p>...</p>
<p>PANIC!!!</p>
<p><em>*What? Did you think I was going to say I fight crime? Who am I, Aqua Man?</em></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>How to Keep Score</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/how-to-keep-score/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/how-to-keep-score/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-30T00:43:11-04:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    How do you measure how well you're doing in your life?&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>How do you measure how well you're doing in your life?</p>
<p>Money? Cars? Homes? Careers? Accolades and awards?</p>
<p>Exits?</p>
<p>Moonshots?</p>
<p>Followers?</p>
<p>PRs?</p>
<p>Net worth?</p>
<p>I think these are all fine and dandy metrics, but really, I think these are all wrong.</p>
<p>I think things like:</p>
<p>Do I have and live by my values?</p>
<p>Am I happy and content?</p>
<p>Do I love well?</p>
<p>Am I blessed?</p>
<p>These feel more right.</p>
<p>Warren Buffett (of all people -- you'll soon see why I note this) once said something along the lines of "Would you rather be known as the world's greatest lover but in fact be the world's worst? Or would you rather be known as the world's worst lover but in fact be the world's best?"</p>
<p>The idea being only you should define how well you're doing in life. If you rely on the opinion of others, you will often find that path lacking. I know I did.</p>
<p>Too many people sell their sacred integrity for more reputation.</p>
<p>Soul for show.</p>
<p>It's time for a new measuring stick.</p>
<p>Determining our own truths and sticking to our first principles is a huge and hard win. To <em>be</em> worthy. To believe we are and have enough. To seek more not for external praise but internal reward. Because you resonate most when you chase what is in harmony with your innerkeeper.</p>
<p>Too many people want to go viral. </p>
<p>Just be your cure.</p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Revenge of the Nerds</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/revenge-of-the-nerds/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/revenge-of-the-nerds/</id>

        <updated>2025-10-29T11:50:24-04:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Life is oversimplification. Here is another example. People who excel early&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Life is oversimplification.</p>
<p>Here is another example.</p>
<p>People who excel early in life in athletics use their bodies to fund their lives. Often sacrificing their health in their later years to do so.</p>
<p>People who excel early in life in business use their brains to fund their lives. Often sacrificing their health in their early years to do so.</p>
<p>But what I realized about nerds (especially those who do really well for themselves), they start becoming health nuts.</p>
<p>Instead of peaking physically at an early age, they peak later. Much later.</p>
<p>Making up for lost time.</p>
<p>It results in this strange thing of seeing old legends in terrible shape and old nerds looking jacked.</p>
<p>I use these terms affectionately.</p>
<p>Who am I to say which way is best?</p>
<p>I skipped class in law school to go lift.</p>
<p>Look how great I turned out.</p>
<p>You know where the weight room is?</p>
<p>I'll check it out.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
