<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>Iterating</title>
    <link href="https://iterating.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://iterating.com" />
    <updated>2025-11-29T14:05:05-05:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>AL8X</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://iterating.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Paper Credentials</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/paper-credentials/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/paper-credentials/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-29T14:05:05-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    I used to really get a kick out of commencement speeches.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I used to really get a kick out of commencement speeches.</p>
<p>The whole idea fascinated me.</p>
<p>Distilling your life's lessons into one speech in front of bored students.</p>
<p>To provide the future of the world with our best, carefully curated, nuggets of accumulated wisdom.</p>
<p>So I would watch them.</p>
<p>And try to be an eternal student.</p>
<p>I suppose I should again.</p>
<p>Haven't watched one in years.</p>
<p>I heard a line the other day that I really enjoyed.</p>
<p>That old line about when the student is ready, the master appears.</p>
<p>But they added a line.</p>
<p>When the student is <em>truly</em> ready, the master disappears.</p>
<p>When the student is ready, the master appears.</p>
<p>When the student is truly ready...</p>
<p>Poof.</p>
<p>Just kidding, still here!</p>
<p>We got work to do, kids.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Curations</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/curations/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/curations/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-28T00:57:35-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    I'm no history buff, but I can lift the past once&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I'm no history buff, but I can lift the past once in a while.</p>
<p>In 1776, the newly formed US of A was fighting for its life.</p>
<p>And like many startups, it was badly in need of funding.</p>
<p>So what did they do?</p>
<p>Well, what they do now.</p>
<p>They started to print money.</p>
<p>One of the first coins they made was the continental dollar.</p>
<p>It wasn't officially a dollar but that's what we call it today.</p>
<p>The reason I ramble about this coin is that it had a typo on the front.</p>
<p>It read in part "Continental Curency" with only one "r" in currency.</p>
<p>The coin now, should you find a real one, is worth a small fortune.</p>
<p>But there's wisdom in this "typo."</p>
<p>Curency.</p>
<p><em>CURE</em>ncy.</p>
<p>It almost looks more correct, doesn't it?</p>
<p>We need one of those today.</p>
<p>A solution to the money problem. </p>
<p>Although the accepted reason was that the designer simply ran out of space, I'd like to think they designed the 1776 continental dollar in the way it should have been.</p>
<p>In the year the US declared its independence, it decided to start a curency.</p>
<p>The study of money is a fascinating one. And anyone who does can see where we're headed. And for all that future, and from all that's passed, we certainly require a cure.</p>
<p>And see.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Given Thanks</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/given-thanks/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/given-thanks/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-27T20:18:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    On a day of thanks, thanks should be given. So here,&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>On a day of thanks, thanks should be given.</p>
<p>So here, take my thanks.</p>
<p>I bequeath it to you.</p>
<p>...</p>
<p>I don't have much to say today. </p>
<p>Just impossibly thankful.</p>
<p>For a good second.</p>
<p>For a good minute.</p>
<p>For a good hour.</p>
<p>For a good day.</p>
<p>For a good week.</p>
<p>For a good month.</p>
<p>For a good year.</p>
<p>For the best life.</p>
<p>Stay spicy, my friends.</p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Jive Turkeys</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/jive-turkeys/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/jive-turkeys/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-26T13:50:04-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Someone once said to me: "You're so different!" Or something to&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Someone once said to me: "You're so different!" Or something to that effect.</p>
<p>They didn't mean it as an insult, quite the opposite. But it's happened. A lot. And I would always have some derivative of the same response, "What are you? <em>Normal?!?</em>"</p>
<p>And I'd scoff and sneer at the "Normal" part. Almost like it felt disdainful to even say the word.</p>
<p><em>Normal</em>.</p>
<p>Eww.</p>
<p>Who wants to be that?</p>
<p>I sure didn't.</p>
<p>Although I will admit, normal is getting pretty weird these days, it's still not what I want to be.</p>
<p>It's not who I am.</p>
<p>I figure the people who find this silly place will only understand me if they understand this post. If they <em>get</em> it.</p>
<p>Normal sucks.</p>
<p>There I said it.</p>
<p>Happy Thanksgiving Eve!</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Goldilocks Mean</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/goldilocks-mean/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/goldilocks-mean/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-25T15:56:23-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    It occurs to me that is sort of my journal. I&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>It occurs to me that is sort of my journal.</p>
<p>I would say private journal but it's on the friggin' internet.</p>
<p>So I won't.</p>
<p>It's my journal.</p>
<p>I've written a lot in my life. Always filtered, though.</p>
<p>This is as close as I have gotten to being "me" but it's still heavily colandered.</p>
<p>I don't want to share everything.</p>
<p>I think that's the art, right?</p>
<p>What to share, what not to.</p>
<p>People seem to trend two ways: They either create a highlight reel or throw a pity party.</p>
<p>But as a stoic of sorts, I believe in golden means.</p>
<p>Goldilocks means.</p>
<p>Not too hot, not too cold. </p>
<p><em>Juuuuuuust</em> right.</p>
<p>It's truly the way to go through our life campaign.</p>
<p>And what is the optimal sliding scale setting?</p>
<p>70% highlights, 30% rants?</p>
<p>50/50?</p>
<p>90/10?</p>
<p>Bah, who knows. You figure it out, numbers cruncher.</p>
<p>I'm more of a vibe guy.</p>
<p>Stay gold.</p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>(in)Tangible</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/intangible/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/intangible/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-24T01:41:53-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    I have always lived on the corner of digital and analog.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I have always lived on the corner of digital and analog.</p>
<p>I mean, I love the internet. Always have.</p>
<p>I love what I can touch, too. Always will.</p>
<p>It seems we're all that way, now.</p>
<p>Growing up with BBSes and dial-up modems, the digital realms were left to nerds. And I was one, being Co-SysOp of a local board. It was a niche of a niche, and that made it even better.</p>
<p>But today, everyone wants to be online. Kids strive to be YouTubers. And you can make a living doing tangible things in an intangible world.</p>
<p>It's almost fading the other way. The tangible stuff is becoming the niche of a niche.</p>
<p>"What's wrong with him?" Was asked about those who lived on the computer and drove their family nuts by tying up the home line with a modem that screeched violently if they picked the phone up to make a call.</p>
<p>Now, "What's wrong with him?" is asked about a person who wants to stay off social media and keep a low profile online. Suspect by not wanting to connect.</p>
<p>The intangible has become too trusted. People used to be so suspicious of whoever they met online. Now, we're butchered like pigs because everyone trusts their little always-online pocket computer and the things it alerts them to.</p>
<p>Maybe it's the city boy in me, but I don't trust anybody.</p>
<p>DTA.</p>
<p>I was writing this to celebrate the mixture of the tangible and intangible.</p>
<p>I didn't mean to go so gloomy. </p>
<p>It's interesting because the intangible is now a very, very real part of the world.</p>
<p>You can get thrown in prison for actions done only in an imaginary world. </p>
<p>Very tangible consequences from intangible actions.</p>
<p>All of this to say:</p>
<p>It's <em>weird</em>, right?</p>
<p>I can't put my finger on it, but it's just really weird.</p>
<p>There's no difference now, between digital and analog.</p>
<p>It's just one big thing.</p>
<p>And it's only getting bigger.</p>
<p>This is weird, right?</p>
<p>I live on the corner of digital and analog, but I repeat myself.</p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Thanks Given</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/thanks-given/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/thanks-given/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-23T20:01:28-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    I suppose this is as good a week as any to&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I suppose this is as good a week as any to start feeling thankful.</p>
<p>In the recent past, someone has (over)thanked me for holding the door for them and a grocery store employee went out of their way to thank me for returning a shopping cart.</p>
<p>Such things are always appreciated, but it makes me wonder, do folks not do this normally?</p>
<p>We know the answer.</p>
<p>Bunch of savages in this town.</p>
<p>I'm no hero, though. No, seriously, sit down. Ok, ok, I'll wait.</p>
<p>...</p>
<p>I'm tryptophaning this week.</p>
<p>Sounds like a Vietnamese influencer.</p>
<p>Trypto Phan.</p>
<p>I gotta say, I'm more a fried chicken fellow than a deep-fried turkey man, but this week is an exception.</p>
<p>Gobble gobble, ya'll.</p>
<p>For gullets reborn, thanks are given.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Play Date</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/play-date/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/play-date/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-22T13:34:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    I'm going to try and put some forethought (aforethought?) into these&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I'm going to try and put some forethought (aforethought?) into these musings.</p>
<p>Instead of just turning the faucet on and seeing what color flows out.</p>
<p>I suppose that'd be a good way to do it.</p>
<p>To prepare.</p>
<p>But not today, today is Saturday. I'm chilling.</p>
<p>So this is what you get.</p>
<p>How are you?</p>
<p>How are you doing?</p>
<p>What's new?</p>
<p>Zzzzzzz.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Rank</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/rank/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/rank/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-21T14:35:28-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Did you know that we used to score people's intelligence? I&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Did you know that we used to score people's intelligence?</p>
<p>I mean, we still do for "geniuses" and what not. But I'm talking about going the other way. The low way.</p>
<p>And these ranks had titles like moron, imbecile, and idiot.</p>
<p>Guess which one was dumbest?</p>
<p>Idiot.</p>
<p>An imbecile is a little smarter than an idiot.</p>
<p>And a moron is King of the Stupid.</p>
<p>So, calling someone a moron isn't as bad as it sounds.</p>
<p>You're actually paying them a compliment.</p>
<p>If they're an imbecile or an idiot.</p>
<p>Class dismissed.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Sip the Juice</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/sip-the-juice/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/sip-the-juice/</id>

        <updated>2025-11-20T17:38:06-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    My brain is starting to unfog. This writing every day thing&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>My brain is starting to unfog.</p>
<p>This writing every day thing is helping me rewire.</p>
<p>Unclogging the conduction wire.</p>
<p>Letting more juice flow.</p>
<p>Not to say that I wasn't flowing before, but I wasn't flowing before.</p>
<p>Time is so interesting. </p>
<p>Living in a bad way felt numb. Like I wasn't in my skin. Just an observer.</p>
<p>My eyes didn't feel like my own.</p>
<p>It felt like forever. </p>
<p>But it's slowly and largely faded.</p>
<p>So staggeringly thankful.</p>
<p>I don't know if I'm just used to a new normal, a new avatar, but I am starting to understand.</p>
<p>I am just happy to be here.</p>
<p>An honor to be nominated.</p>
<p>Writing to myself.</p>
<p>To my loved ones.</p>
<p>And to strangers (how'd you get in here?).</p>
<p>The thing I'm focusing on now is energy. </p>
<p>The inner fuel tank.</p>
<p>I get about as terrible a gas mileage as my body-on-frame SUVs.</p>
<p>But I love 'em.</p>
<p>I'm not saying I want to be a Tesla or some hybrid, just want some more juice when I stomp.</p>
<p>Here's the thing I'm learning, though:</p>
<p>There was a time when I had to use my juice on just keeping myself above ground.</p>
<p>So I conserved it. Hoarded it. Let it stock up, even as it diminished.</p>
<p>But it is only by using it that the capacity regrows.</p>
<p>Muscle memory applying to all sorts of circuitry.</p>
<p>How much fuel do I got left?</p>
<p>I got enough to go around.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
