<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>Iterating</title>
    <link href="https://iterating.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://iterating.com" />
    <updated>2025-12-14T18:12:31-05:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>AL8X</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://iterating.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Tush Push</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/tush-push/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/tush-push/</id>

        <updated>2025-12-14T18:12:31-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    I got this theory. About pro football. I call it "The&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I got this theory.</p>
<p>About pro football.</p>
<p>I call it "The curse of the decent quarterback."</p>
<p>And it goes a little something like this:</p>
<p>Teams that find a decent quarterback are cursed to play them for a decade, to middling success at best.</p>
<p>A good enough quarterback, I argue, only gives good enough results, not a ring. But they're too good to let go. So you keep them. And you never win it all.</p>
<p>That's my theory.</p>
<p>So what would I do if I were running a pro team?</p>
<p>Glad you asked.</p>
<p>I'd do weird ess like draft a QB every year, even if I think we've got a winner already.</p>
<p>Just stack 'em.</p>
<p>Have the best backup in the league. And the best 3rd string. Always.</p>
<p>Even draft 1st round QBs in consecutive years. Maybe three in a row. Get them rookie contracts on the cheap.</p>
<p>Why not?</p>
<p>Then I'd focus on the offensive line. Then all defense. And lastly, the skill players.</p>
<p>I won't insult any QB by naming them, I think you know what I mean if you watched for any length of time. It's such an important position in today's game that you must get the decision right. And then when you do, protect it at all costs. Even if you have to keep competition flowing by bringing in their heir apparents yearly.</p>
<p>Have the QB feel like he's got to earn the starting role every game, because he does.</p>
<p>Of course, this idea is just from the mind of a old(ish) flag football cornerback.</p>
<p>But from my armchair, it's as clear as day.</p>
<p>Now, where's Jon Gruden when I need him?</p>
<blockquote>
<p>"Coach, I got this theory..."</p>
</blockquote>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Wont</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/wont/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/wont/</id>

        <updated>2025-12-13T00:26:27-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Writing while tired is a silly, dangerous, thing. So I won't.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Writing while tired is a silly, dangerous, thing.</p>
<p>So I won't.</p>
<p>But let me just say, it's pretty cool to write tired.</p>
<p>You just ramble and ramble and hope maybe something worth something will tumble out.</p>
<p>Of course, that's how I write every day.</p>
<p>I don't like hosting, but we're hosting this weekend. So I'm writing early.</p>
<p>Just in case.</p>
<p>This writing every day thing has become important to me. </p>
<p>Even though this is my second writing, it counts as the next day, technically.</p>
<p>So the streak continues.</p>
<p>Hermit don't like hosting. Hermit only like to do what he like to do. Hermit curmudgeon. Hermit need sleep.</p>
<p>Goodnight.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Raining &#x27;Bows</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/raining-bows/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/raining-bows/</id>

        <updated>2025-12-12T15:57:54-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    I'm still working through this idea that the secret to life&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I'm still working through this idea that the secret to life is noticing, feeling, living the magic of everyday moments.</p>
<p>Of making the routine feel elevated.</p>
<p>Of seeing heaven in a favorite song.</p>
<p>I think that's the whole point of this [<em>waves hands around chaotically</em>] thing.</p>
<p>You know?</p>
<p>We get 30,000 sunsets (give or take). </p>
<p>30,000 golden hours right before.</p>
<p>Each one magical.</p>
<p>Each one sacred.</p>
<p>If you want them to be.</p>
<p>I took for granted growing up in the city.</p>
<p>I never looked <em>up</em>.</p>
<p>And now, when I see skyscrapers, I stare in awe like a tourist.</p>
<p>How they block out the skyline because they <em>are</em> the skyline.</p>
<p>How creatures just like us made them.</p>
<p>From the ground up.</p>
<p>I'll leave it to you whether skyscrapers are a good thing or a bad thing.</p>
<p>But they are a pretty amazing display of what humans can do.</p>
<p>I feel that way about redwood trees, too. Except we didn't make those.</p>
<p>I heard a long time ago that we lose just as much as we gain by learning how a rainbow is made.</p>
<p>And I suppose most think it's easier to be awed when you're young, naive, or just foolish.</p>
<p>But it's true (about the rainbow).</p>
<p>Sometimes boiling it down to textbook "science" takes a bit of the beauty away. Takes away the "that which cannot be said." Takes away the magic. Because you know how the trick is done.</p>
<p>Rainbows are magnificent.</p>
<p>So are small humans that have half your genes (Lord help us) and half your love's (thank God).</p>
<p>And Robin Williams (especially in his dramatic roles).</p>
<p>And countless other things we experience routinely.</p>
<p>We just get used to it all.</p>
<p>So here's to never getting used to it.</p>
<p>To keeping it forever fresh.</p>
<p>Groundhog day is life for most. </p>
<p>Over and over.</p>
<p>Same same same.</p>
<p>Is that a blessing or a curse?</p>
<p>Is nothing sacred?</p>
<p>Or is everything?</p>
<p>I made my choice.</p>
<p>What you doing?</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Double rainbow!!!</p>
</blockquote>
<p>These are what we stay alive for.</p>
<p>Aye aye, Captain.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Space Lord Mother Mother</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/space-lord-mother-mother/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/space-lord-mother-mother/</id>

        <updated>2025-12-11T11:35:23-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Psst. Hey you. Yeah, I'm talking to you. Get over here.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Psst.</p>
<p>Hey you.</p>
<p>Yeah, I'm talking to you.</p>
<p>Get over here.</p>
<p>Listen.</p>
<p>Listen.</p>
<p>There's some stuff that happened this year that has probably blown your mind.</p>
<p>But guess what?</p>
<p>Next year will be just as weird.</p>
<p>Maybe weirder.</p>
<p>Just like every year coming and every year since.</p>
<p>Sure, maybe its got on a new outfit or shade of makeup.</p>
<p>But it's all the same.</p>
<p>Unless aliens come from a rock rocket.</p>
<p>That would be different.</p>
<p>I joked with my wife: "What if they (the aliens) put in their starfaring flight to Earth, their dumbest, most disposable representative(s) they could find?" </p>
<p>Their planet's idiot(s).</p>
<p>Just because they didn't want to lose anyone important.</p>
<p>Not for something as trivial as a flight to our solar system.</p>
<p>And these fools from the sky come down to say hello.</p>
<p>And we humans and our world leaders race to greet them. With records of gold detailing our efforts. Maybe some even on the ground. On their knees.</p>
<p>And these aliens are like, "Woah. Cool."</p>
<p>While we deify them.</p>
<p>Or kill them.</p>
<p>50/50.</p>
<p>Same same.</p>
<p>What would be better: Aliens sending their very best or their very worst?</p>
<p>In my tale, they send their dumbest.</p>
<p>And hilarity ensues.</p>
<p>Or tragedy.</p>
<p>Which will get funnier over time.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Imp Patient</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/imp-patient/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/imp-patient/</id>

        <updated>2025-12-10T11:48:54-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    For a guy who almost died who still plays the long&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>For a guy who almost died who still plays the long game (I think), I'm understandably sort of impatient.</p>
<p>I mean, I can delay gratification, delegate, lead, and all that bull mess, but what I mean is that window of time after the deal is done where you are waiting for everything to wrap up and close.</p>
<p>The shipping time.</p>
<p>The transfer time.</p>
<p>The results of your efforts time.</p>
<p>The when you can call it complete time.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Put a bow on it!</p>
</blockquote>
<p>But it's always been that way. </p>
<p>Studying for the bar exam sooooked. Taking the bar sucked. </p>
<p>But waiting six months(!) for the results?</p>
<p>Worst of all <em>by far</em>.</p>
<p>Why? I think it's the <em>out of my control </em>part. The <em>what if</em> part. The <strong><em>not knowing</em></strong> part.</p>
<p>Give me a bunch of things I can do to prepare and get it done, a mountain of them (please don't), and it'll get done. But once it's fate is in someone else's hands, I suppose that drives me a <em>little</em> crazy.</p>
<p>What's taking so long?</p>
<p>Do they need something else?</p>
<p>Was I unclear?</p>
<p>There's a snow storm in the rust belt. Is that why its delayed?</p>
<p>This is a part of young me (Yung Mi?) that I carry today in my back pocket.</p>
<p>And while I've done enough to discipline that boy over the years, he still shows his face every once in awhile.</p>
<p>And the holidays with all its over-promising and under-delivering, well it's enough to make an old man shake his fist in the sky and throw punches at the sun.</p>
<p>No old men here, though.</p>
<p>Just hurry up already.</p>
<p>[Shakes fist at screen.]</p>
<p>Yung Mi yaaa, what are you going to do when you grow up?</p>
<p>Coffee's for closers, you know.</p>
<p>Just crank up <em>Enter Sandman</em> and brew me a cup.</p>
<p>I'm just getting warmed up.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Wholly</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/wholly/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/wholly/</id>

        <updated>2025-12-09T12:35:14-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Someday, I'm going to write about sacralizing everything. It won't be&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Someday, I'm going to write about sacralizing everything.</p>
<p>It won't be today, but I'm building up to it.</p>
<p>In a world where nothing is sacred, we really have it backwards.</p>
<p>Everything is.</p>
<p>If we want it to be.</p>
<p>I'm learning that to see the <em>forever</em> in the <em>fleeting</em> is the key to this whole life thing.</p>
<p>When you can see God in a sun ray during golden hour.</p>
<p>When you feel it in your tummy when you see your wife's genuine smile. Her smize.</p>
<p>When you hear your children belly laugh at silly jokes.</p>
<p>These are just lights, grins, and giggles, you say.</p>
<p>And you'd be right. They are just that.</p>
<p>But you're also so very, very wrong.</p>
<p>Both can be true.</p>
<p>I hope you see that.</p>
<p>Infinity fits in the palm of your hand.</p>
<p>Eternity is an hour.</p>
<p>Everything and nothing.</p>
<p><em>C'est la vie</em>.</p>
<p>∞ and 0.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Ain&#x27;t It Fun</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/aint-it-fun/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/aint-it-fun/</id>

        <updated>2025-12-08T11:59:15-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Are you having fun yet? I sure am. I remember someone&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Are you having fun yet?</p>
<p>I sure am.</p>
<p>I remember someone saying if you're bored, you're boring.</p>
<p>And I take that to heart.</p>
<p>Bored people are snoozers.</p>
<p>Peripheral people.</p>
<p>Background noise.</p>
<p>I'd make an L with my hand and put it to my forehead but I think that will get me cancelled (much like many of the things we grew up with).</p>
<p>That's just going too far.</p>
<p>I think the secret to non-boredom is finding excitement in the mundane.</p>
<p>Joy in the routine.</p>
<p>Infinity in the stillness.</p>
<p>If there's an area that you love that most people would think crazy, I think that's your sweet spot.</p>
<p>If you hold a view that is 180 degrees opposite of most, you should cultivate that.</p>
<p>I mean, obey the law, be morally correct, but other than that? </p>
<p>All bets are off.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>"Don't be boredom, be boresmart!"</p>
</blockquote>
<p>One of these days, one of my sayings will hit.</p>
<p>It probably won't be that one, but c'mon, <em>c'mon</em>, this is good stuff here.</p>
<p>[<em>Puts three fingers up and places hand over forehead...holds it there and pauses for a uncomfortably long time. Puts hand down. The author is strangely satisfied and pleased with himself. Grinning (smirking?), he then leaves the room.</em>]</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Pickles</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/pickles/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/pickles/</id>

        <updated>2025-12-07T12:58:46-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    "So you're a dilettante?" "I'm a what?" "A dabbler, someone who&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <blockquote>
<p>"So you're a dilettante?"</p>
<p>"I'm a what?"</p>
<p>"A dabbler, someone who pretends to be an expert but really just knows a little about a lot."</p>
<p>"Oh. I am not."</p>
</blockquote>
<p>So, it turns out, I'm a dilettante.</p>
<p>In a lot of ways.</p>
<p>I didn't always know what that meant, and I suppose I still really don't.</p>
<p>I mean, I love a lot of things.</p>
<p>Interested in a lot of things.</p>
<p>Some things I dig deeper.</p>
<p>Most things I dig for a while.</p>
<p>Some things stay.</p>
<p>Most things have to go.</p>
<p>I always respect and admire those who can center and hone in on their one thing.</p>
<p>Like my buddy who loves to weld. Mothereffer a welder, to the bone.</p>
<p>But reality is, I like to dabble.</p>
<p>Call it whatever you want, but I just enjoy learning a little something new.</p>
<p>And even after all these years, after all I think I know, I continue to find "new" areas.</p>
<p>Now most of these have been around forever, but I never saw them. Even if they highly overlapped the areas I have been interested in for decades.</p>
<p>To me, that's so neat.</p>
<p>Bruce Lee said something like how he doesn't fear the man who has practiced 10,000 different techniques once. But rather fears the man who has practiced one kick 10,000 times.</p>
<p>And that's right. You would fear a dude with one massively overbuilt leg. That ess would be scary.</p>
<p>But hear me out.</p>
<p>How would you fare against the man who practiced 10,000 different techniques ten times? A hundred?</p>
<p>I'm just saying.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Venn</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/venn/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/venn/</id>

        <updated>2025-12-06T17:28:56-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    I've always been careful to keep my circles separate. Family friends.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I've always been careful to keep my circles separate.</p>
<p>Family friends. Work friends. School friends. Old school friends. Digital friends.</p>
<p>Each in their own category. </p>
<p>Never the two shall mix.</p>
<p>I don't know why I'd do that.</p>
<p>In the few times they did actually interact, it felt like some wacky crossover episode had taken place, and I didn't quite know how to act.</p>
<p>For you see, in each circle, I was a different version of "me."</p>
<p>I see that now.</p>
<p>I didn't see it then.</p>
<p>The reason I didn't overlap the circles was because I didn't know how to be <em>me</em> when they mixed.</p>
<p>Was I school Alex? Work Alex? OG Alex? Digital Alex?</p>
<p>Very few have seen me with my hair down, so to speak, and that's probably for the best.</p>
<p>The point of all this is how so many haven't changed. And how so many have.</p>
<p>And I don't know which one is better: Those who haven't changed and those who have.</p>
<p>I know I've changed.</p>
<p>I still don't venn diagram my life. But there are no separate circles, now. Just one special one.</p>
<p>I sit in it and pilot it around this vast program called reality. My copilots actively keeping everything running, while I try to keep us on course.</p>
<p>Every now and again, another circle, past or future, approaches.</p>
<p>I let them bounce, though.</p>
<p>They don't get in.</p>
<p>This is the hermit in me, I know.</p>
<p>But the fella they're looking for is long gone.</p>
<p>Went to never never land and never came home.</p>
<p>...Did they leave yet?</p>
<p>Ok, good.</p>
<p>I know who I am now.</p>
<p>I know how to play it.</p>
<p>I am bubbles clustered together. So many.</p>
<p>That one day popped into one big bubble.</p>
<p>I believe in the sanctity of this bubble. </p>
<p>I <em>sacralize</em> it.</p>
<p>There is no place in the world I would rather be, than where I am right now. With who I am with right now.</p>
<p>Floating through the cosmos.</p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Better Than Nothing</title>
        <author>
            <name>AL8X</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/better-than-nothing/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/better-than-nothing/</id>

        <updated>2025-12-05T15:53:42-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    They say kids are made out of rubber. Not literally of&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>They say kids are made out of rubber. </p>
<p>Not literally of course.</p>
<p>More in the way they can bounce back from injury.</p>
<p>And I see it.</p>
<p>How fast my kids can heal from a bump or owwie.</p>
<p>I don't know what adults are made out of, but I marvel at how my body fixes itself.</p>
<p>It is very cyclical.</p>
<p>Up days. Down days.</p>
<p>Flushing out. Feeding in.</p>
<p>Give. </p>
<p>Take.</p>
<p>I want to make something clear.</p>
<p>I'm thankful for every setback.</p>
<p>Because it comes with a hidden perk.</p>
<p>I just have to figure it out.</p>
<p>The body is a universe onto itself.</p>
<p>I don't think we think about this enough.</p>
<p>Sure, bodies are temples, but they're way more than that.</p>
<p>They're vast. Infinite when you zoom in.</p>
<p>Full of life, giving you life. The total system working together (sometimes against each other) to keep you running.</p>
<p>This is not appreciated enough.</p>
<p>At least by me.</p>
<p>I'm working on it though.</p>
<p>You know what's weird?</p>
<p>Supposedly, we are made up of more nothing than something.</p>
<p>We are. The world is. Everything in the universe.</p>
<p>We are more space than substance.</p>
<p>That ess crazy.</p>
<p>Don't believe it.</p>
<p>You're more something than nothing.</p>
<p>You're all something.</p>
<p>We just haven't figured out the right way to name the nothing.</p>
<p>There's probably a centillion nothings that are somethings. </p>
<p>We just don't know how to delineate between them.</p>
<p>Or how to see them.</p>
<p>This is not a very good post. </p>
<p>Better than nothing.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
