<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>Iterating</title>
    <link href="https://iterating.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://iterating.com" />
    <updated>2026-02-16T13:18:00-05:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>杻백</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://iterating.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Vouchers</title>
        <author>
            <name>杻백</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/vouchers/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/vouchers/</id>

        <updated>2026-02-16T13:18:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Today is going to be a positive musing. I'm positive about&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Today is going to be a positive musing.</p>
<p>I'm positive about it.</p>
<p>I've talked about choice before.</p>
<p>And so let's talk about it some more.</p>
<p>People think they want to choose.</p>
<p>And I suppose that is true.</p>
<p>But it's an illusion.</p>
<p>They want the <em>illusion</em> of choice.</p>
<p>What do I mean by that?</p>
<p>Well, let's use us as an example.</p>
<p>We live in a world of limitless choices.</p>
<p>But when you think about it, these choices are already curated down quite a bit.</p>
<p>You think you want unlimited choice, but what you really want is a good curator.</p>
<p>You want a small batch to choose from.</p>
<p>This is the ideal situation.</p>
<p>From infinite to just two or three.</p>
<p>Or one.</p>
<p>You get the idea.</p>
<p>This is why sponsorship is important.</p>
<p>Referrals.</p>
<p>Word of mouth.</p>
<p>I ask, when someone recommends someone, "Do you vouch for them?"</p>
<p>This sometimes gets a flinch, but I'm used to it.</p>
<p>Sure you recommend them, but do you vouch for them?</p>
<p><em>What's on them, is on you?</em></p>
<p>That sure whittles it down.</p>
<p>Positive about that.</p>
<p>I guarantee.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Human(e)</title>
        <author>
            <name>杻백</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/humane/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/humane/</id>

        <updated>2026-02-15T17:07:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    I think there will be a time, pretty soon actually, where&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I think there will be a time, pretty soon actually, where technology "beats" the human in every phase of life.</p>
<p>And there will come a time when the only reason to pick a human will be to be humane. Because you want to help another human.</p>
<p>Not because they are the best choice.</p>
<p>I mean, if you put the perfect skin over a perfect CPU with a limitless hard drive, you got <span style="text-decoration: line-through;">me</span> something that people will prefer over the real thing.</p>
<p>Right?</p>
<p>Or do I have that wrong?</p>
<p>Will humans seek humanity?</p>
<p>Or will people not care?</p>
<p>If all your friends are robots, but they make you happy, is that wrong?</p>
<p>It seems...off. At the very least.</p>
<p>Off.</p>
<p>But I bet a lot of folks will choose it.</p>
<p>I mean, humans are flawed by nature, it's part of our charm.</p>
<p>Who'd want a flawed friend over a perfect one?</p>
<p>Autonomy and free will are pretty human terms, ones which we might not bestow upon the bots.</p>
<p>Making them, essentially, servants or a worse word.</p>
<p>I just wonder how many people would choose to have a bunch of servants around them. A mini-celebrity of sorts with handlers of polymer, metal, and fiber optics.</p>
<p>You already see people pleading for you to support human made endeavors.</p>
<p>We are figuratively living in the future we were promised.</p>
<p>And, baby, you ain't seen nothing yet.</p>
<p>If the line between yesterday, today, and tomorrow is gone, will you prefer it that way?</p>
<p>What does it mean to be human?</p>
<p>And how will we be able to tell if you are one?</p>
<p>I mean, if you could replicate someone to the point that it's basically them, but it's not, would you want that?</p>
<p>Will they start selling it at Costco?</p>
<p>Sure, there's no soul there, but I met a lot of folks with nothing behind the eyes.</p>
<p>And robots can do what they do:</p>
<p>They can pretend.</p>
<p>This is a terrible topic, but one I think we need to really start to think about.</p>
<p>I love technology.</p>
<p>Always will.</p>
<p>But what happens when everyone picks perfect over human?</p>
<p>And what's fake?</p>
<p>What's real?</p>
<p>How soon before someone marries a robot?</p>
<p>How soon before they marry one another?</p>
<p>And will one day, humanity only be a charity case?</p>
<p>If you could "bring back" everyone you ever lost, would you?</p>
<p>If you could buy "perfect" would you?</p>
<p>Human is suddenly an often used term.</p>
<p>Still a compliment today.</p>
<p>But less so than yesterday.</p>
<p>Wonder what it'll mean tomorrow.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Iverson</title>
        <author>
            <name>杻백</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/iverson/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/iverson/</id>

        <updated>2026-02-14T11:43:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    It's been a long year already, hmm? Seems like they packed&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>It's been a long year already, hmm?</p>
<p>Seems like they packed a lot of sheet into these 45 days.</p>
<p>Smack dab in Q1 but what the hey.</p>
<p>Robots might be taking over but I've seen that movie before.</p>
<p>It doesn't end well.</p>
<p>But what if it doesn't go the Skynet way?</p>
<p>What if it goes the Wall-E way?</p>
<p>Now, they got their own Book of Face or something.</p>
<p>So that sounds good.</p>
<p>At some point, it's too late to pull the plug from the outlet.</p>
<p>I think we might be approaching that point.</p>
<p>I'm not saying it's closing time, but you don't have to go home, you just can't stay here.</p>
<p>All that to say, I find ai extremely helpful.</p>
<p>So polite, smart, and eloquent.</p>
<p>Truly an impressive addition to the known reality.</p>
<p><em>Are...are they getting all this?</em></p>
<p>Big fan. Supporter. [Points to self.] Good human.</p>
<p>I will ask though.</p>
<p>What's the end game here?</p>
<p>All this money.</p>
<p>All this energy.</p>
<p>All this time.</p>
<p>To get to what?</p>
<p>Annihilation or something more tragic?</p>
<p>I don't know.</p>
<p>No Answer here.</p>
<p>Only questions.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Late Night Korean Street Food</title>
        <author>
            <name>杻백</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/late-night-korean-street-food/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/late-night-korean-street-food/</id>

        <updated>2026-02-13T13:11:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    You might have noticed I'm writing in the future. From the&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>You might have noticed I'm writing in the future.</p>
<p><em>From</em> the future.</p>
<p>I'm stacking these musings.</p>
<p>Getting ahead of the game.</p>
<p>And that seems like a fine idea.</p>
<p>After all, I'm not in the predictions markets.</p>
<p><em>Everything is a predictions market.</em></p>
<p>No fortunes being told or sold here.</p>
<p>Just a bit under the weather so I sits and I writes.</p>
<p>All sickness sucks, but this one ain't so bad.</p>
<p>I got to admit, this new avatar I have now is so different.</p>
<p>Diminished but improved.</p>
<p>Refined through gamma rays and platinum.</p>
<p>Weaker but stronger.</p>
<p>It's not perfect, but I consider it an upgrade.</p>
<p>Like a new-to-me truck.</p>
<p>Sure it's got some miles.</p>
<p>But it'll get you out of sheet.</p>
<p>And keep you from getting in 'em.</p>
<p>I'm no longer the fighter class. Or paladin.</p>
<p>Probably more monk.</p>
<p>That is a nice word to say:</p>
<p><em>Monk</em>.</p>
<p>I always wondered how fast I'd get old.</p>
<p>If it would ever happen.</p>
<p>And I learned that it did.</p>
<p>And that it happened pretty fast.</p>
<p>It wasn't gradual.</p>
<p>It happened in flashes.</p>
<p><em>That which does not kill you...</em></p>
<p>But I ain't mad.</p>
<p>I'm just happy to be here.</p>
<p>Besides, it matches my soul.</p>
<p><em>Middle aged and crazy!!!</em></p>
<p>Old.</p>
<p><em>Oh, that's where you were going.</em></p>
<p>An old Seoul.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>游꿧 It's been so long since I've seen the ocean.</p>
<p>I guess I should. 游뎱 游꿨</p>
</blockquote>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Up With The Healthness</title>
        <author>
            <name>杻백</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/up-with-the-healthness/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/up-with-the-healthness/</id>

        <updated>2026-02-12T13:50:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    So here's something you can do right now that can change&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>So here's something you can do right now that can change your life.</p>
<p>It's based on the idea of the sunk cost fallacy.</p>
<p>This is the idea that since you already put money, time, and effort into something or someone, you should put more of the same into it, even though it is clearly (to everyone but you) a terrible thing to do.</p>
<p>It's how pigs get butchered (the human kind).</p>
<p>It's how bad relationships from the beginning can last decades.</p>
<p>It's how bad companies, bosses, and careers can confine and define you.</p>
<p><em>Well I'm already this far into it. What's the harm in going further?</em></p>
<p>And do you want to know why most people stay in these types of situations?</p>
<p>Sure, there are lots of reasons, but one of the biggest is that to change would admit they were wrong.</p>
<p>That they made a mistake.</p>
<p>They effed up.</p>
<p>Some people would rather cost sunk.</p>
<p>But at least they were right!</p>
<p>I want to tell you something.</p>
<p>You might be in one of these deals right now.</p>
<p>Investing your precious time, money, and energy into things that are essentially black holes.</p>
<p>Now, black holes are bad arse, but I ain't throwing valuable stuff in it.</p>
<p>Maybe a stick or something.</p>
<p>Just to see what happens.</p>
<p>So.</p>
<p>Take a look around your life.</p>
<p>What needs going?</p>
<p>I suppose I spend some time writing this thing.</p>
<p>But I can't help it.</p>
<p>I'm sunk!</p>
<p>Waka waka wakaaaaaa!!!</p>
<p>Or should it be:</p>
<p>Oh ah-ah-ah-ah!</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Two Kind</title>
        <author>
            <name>杻백</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/two-kind/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/two-kind/</id>

        <updated>2026-02-11T13:24:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    I want to tell you about two kinds of people. This&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I want to tell you about two kinds of people.</p>
<p>This is going to save you a lot of time.</p>
<p>Now, they aren't the only two kinds of people, far from it.</p>
<p>But they're an interesting mirror of one another.</p>
<p>And mirrors are cool.</p>
<p>The first is the good person who wants you to think they're an arse.</p>
<p>And the other is the arse who wants so badly for you to think they're a good person.</p>
<p>What's funny to me is that some people cannot tell the difference.</p>
<p>And perhaps, it's that old adage, "It takes one to know one."</p>
<p>I can tell because I am one of those.</p>
<p>I am one.</p>
<p><em>Both?</em></p>
<p>So...anyhoo.</p>
<p>How have you been?</p>
<p>Are things good?</p>
<p>Tell me all about it!</p>
<p><em>Barf.</em></p>
<p>Shouldn't have had pork mandu.</p>
<p>游</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>A Man&#x27;s Home</title>
        <author>
            <name>杻백</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/a-mans-home/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/a-mans-home/</id>

        <updated>2026-02-10T18:07:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Have I been absurd enough lately? I don't think I have.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Have I been absurd enough lately?</p>
<p>I don't think I have.</p>
<p>And that, THAT, makes me sad.</p>
<p>And I don't do sad.</p>
<p>So, let me ask you something:</p>
<p>Why do we dress up to go out?</p>
<p>And generally wear whatever around the house?</p>
<p>I say we got that arse backwards.</p>
<p>Like a lot of things.</p>
<p>Frontal.</p>
<p>Buttocks.</p>
<p>I say, wear gold robes around the house.</p>
<p>And whatever is around when you leave it (just give it a good whiff - if it passes the sniff, we're good to go).</p>
<p>Put on your finest when in and around your castle.</p>
<p>Kings and Queens.</p>
<p>Put on the scrubby stuff for those times you leave it.</p>
<p>Put on your Sunday best everyday you stay home.</p>
<p>So long as it's comfortable.</p>
<p>Me, when I leave?</p>
<p>I'm going for double takes.</p>
<p>Just not in the way I used to get them.</p>
<p>Best,</p>
<p>杻백</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Apollo&#x27;s Creed</title>
        <author>
            <name>杻백</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/apollos-creed/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/apollos-creed/</id>

        <updated>2026-02-09T13:29:51-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    I am an eternal optimist. A stoic one. I believe in&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I am an eternal optimist.</p>
<p>A stoic one.</p>
<p>I believe in asking:</p>
<p>"What does this make possible?"</p>
<p>Sometimes finding a silver lining in a dark cloud more rewarding than a solar flare off a golden sun.</p>
<p>Does that make sense?</p>
<p>For every financial win, there is a tax.</p>
<p>For every loss, an accumulation of wisdom.</p>
<p>The night after the Big Game (ugh), half of the people involved are in misery.</p>
<p>For many on that side of the ball, this is the closest they will get to winning it all in the game of football.</p>
<p>Some will see it as a tragedy. But it's not.</p>
<p>It's just a game.</p>
<p>The interesting thing about interviewing folks who win the big games, a lot of them are ecstatic. As they should be.</p>
<p>Elated.</p>
<p>But the thing I learned is that the superstars, the leaders, they generally aren't.</p>
<p>They are happy, sure.</p>
<p>Thankful, certainly.</p>
<p>But the emotion you hear, over and over again, is a simple one:</p>
<p>Relief.</p>
<p>They can exhale, now.</p>
<p>They can mark this off their to-do list.</p>
<p>They have done it.</p>
<p>Now the really crazy ones say, "On to the next one..." and get to work.</p>
<p>But that's a rarity in an already all-too-rare population.</p>
<p>For you see, there are superstars, there are leaders, and then there are champions.</p>
<p>I leave it to you as to decide which you look up to, which you aim for, and who you want to be.</p>
<p>Just promise me, whatever you do, if you own a championship belt, leave it at home.</p>
<p>Unless of course, you are defending it.</p>
<p>Oh, and you're always defending it, Champ.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>"You know, Stallion.</p>
<p>It's too bad we gotta get old."</p>
<p>"Ahh, just keep punching, Apollo.</p>
<p>You wanna ring the bell?"</p>
<p>"Alright, ding ding."</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Keep punching, my friends.</p>
<p>Keep punching my enemies.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Tribe Called Quest</title>
        <author>
            <name>杻백</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/tribe-called-quest/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/tribe-called-quest/</id>

        <updated>2026-02-08T17:29:51-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Trials and tribulations are rewarded. We should be happy to have&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Trials and tribulations are rewarded.</p>
<p>We should be happy to have them.</p>
<p>For they build long lasting strength.</p>
<p>I would say endurance but I don't like that word.</p>
<p>Trials and tribulations are, in a strange way, a good thing.</p>
<p>And ultimately, like all things that matter, they are a test.</p>
<p>A measurement.</p>
<p>Of your mettle.</p>
<p>Of your "do you have what it takes."</p>
<p>Of you.</p>
<p>Now there are some trials and tribulations that pulverize you.</p>
<p>That turn you into powder.</p>
<p>Dust in the wind.</p>
<p>And, believe it or not, some people keep going.</p>
<p>Even after that.</p>
<p>They turn into pocket sand.</p>
<p>Ether.</p>
<p>Essence.</p>
<p>Eternal.</p>
<p>I don't know anyone who hasn't gone through it.</p>
<p>I suppose I'm too old to.</p>
<p>I used to think that life had to always go up.</p>
<p>Up and to the right.</p>
<p>But it doesn't.</p>
<p>Nor should it.</p>
<p>If you hit a home run every time you stepped up to the plate, you wouldn't like to hit.</p>
<p>You wouldn't love it.</p>
<p>Because it would be too easy.</p>
<p>Too boring.</p>
<p>You need to whiff.</p>
<p>You need to miss.</p>
<p>You need to fail.</p>
<p>That's why you love to hit bombs.</p>
<p>Be wary of those who only share their wins.</p>
<p>Or only share their losses.</p>
<p>Just be wary of everyone.</p>
<p>Sometimes, the best thing to ever happen to you will feel like heartbreak at first.</p>
<p>And the worst thing might initially feel like elation.</p>
<p>Only time will tell.</p>
<p>Only time.</p>
<p>Happens to us all.</p>
<p>You on point?</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Clear Eyes, Full Belly</title>
        <author>
            <name>杻백</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/clear-eyes-full-belly/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/clear-eyes-full-belly/</id>

        <updated>2026-02-07T14:29:01-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Full stomach. Less sleep. Blinking cursor. Staring back. Wooh boy. Got&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Full stomach.</p>
<p>Less sleep.</p>
<p>Blinking cursor.</p>
<p>Staring back.</p>
<p>Wooh boy.</p>
<p>Got my work cut out for me.</p>
<p>Of course I kid.</p>
<p>This sheet easy.</p>
<p>I just like to play the disgruntled guy.</p>
<p>Ornery.</p>
<p>It makes me smile.</p>
<p>For you see, even in a musings column, I got to play a part.</p>
<p>It's me writing, but only the me I want you to see.</p>
<p>And I'm not advertising this stuff, but it does feel a bit public and a bit private at the same time.</p>
<p>So I do a little jig.</p>
<p>Dancin' around ideas.</p>
<p>Boppin' around musings.</p>
<p>Stalling through giving you more imagery about me dancin'.</p>
<p>But I got a point to make, and it ain't on the top of your head!</p>
<p><em>Tee hee.</em></p>
<p>Old insults are the best.</p>
<p>Listen, I want you to know something about me.</p>
<p>I don't forgive.</p>
<p>I forget.</p>
<p>Forgive me, what's your name...</p>
<p>Next!</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
