<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>Iterating</title>
    <link href="https://iterating.com/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://iterating.com" />
    <updated>2026-02-26T11:49:00-05:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>杻백</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://iterating.com</id>

    <entry>
        <title>I See, I See</title>
        <author>
            <name>杻백</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/i-see-i-see/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/i-see-i-see/</id>

        <updated>2026-02-26T11:49:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Gather round class. Let's all form a circle. And let's sit&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Gather round class.</p>
<p>Let's all form a circle.</p>
<p>And let's sit down on the floor pillows provided to you.</p>
<p>Today, we discuss a topic near and dear to my heart.</p>
<p>We discuss...</p>
<p>Oh, let me open up some windows, get some fresh air.</p>
<p><em>He's stalling again. He's out of ideas.</em></p>
<p>There, let's all take a deep inhale of this wonderful invisible gas.</p>
<p>High quality O2, baby.</p>
<p>Hear those wind chimes?</p>
<p>Got those last week.</p>
<p><em>Yep, definitely stalling. He's so weird.</em></p>
<p>Where was I?</p>
<p>Oh yes, the topic.</p>
<p>Today's topic is on haters.</p>
<p><em>Eeek. Does he know?</em></p>
<p>Now, I've tried, relatively speaking, to keep my chin down and keep to myself.</p>
<p>Still got haters.</p>
<p>I was shy.</p>
<p>Still got haters.</p>
<p>I was aloof.</p>
<p>Still got haters.</p>
<p>I tried new armors.</p>
<p>Tried being overly me (cranked up to 11) and just tried to be a shouty salesy guy.</p>
<p>Still got haters.</p>
<p>Tried to do right.</p>
<p>Tried to do good.</p>
<p>Tried to be just.</p>
<p>Still got haters.</p>
<p>And so class, what I will offer you today, is that likely in this circle today is a hater.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Brothers and sisters, and friends, and I see some enemies...</p>
</blockquote>
<p>And to that, I say, welcome.</p>
<p>I used to say an enemy to my face is more valuable that a false friend.</p>
<p>I still believe that.</p>
<p>And I still believe what a good friend told me, decades ago, that if the holes of arse are mad at you, you're doing something right!</p>
<p>Now I confess some good people have rightfully been upset with me, and I regret those tremendously.</p>
<p>Such as I can.</p>
<p>But to the arses, who I have made upset, well it's time to do a little dance.</p>
<p>In your honor.</p>
<p>...[Five minutes later.]...</p>
<p>Good job, everyone.</p>
<p>Now, let's all sit down again.</p>
<p>Take a long drink of water.</p>
<p>And pick up the item in front of you.</p>
<p>In front of you all are little hand mirrors.</p>
<p>Pick those up.</p>
<p>And tell me what you see.</p>
<p>Friend?</p>
<p>Or enemy?</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>No Problemo</title>
        <author>
            <name>杻백</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/no-problemo/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/no-problemo/</id>

        <updated>2026-02-25T13:43:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    High quality problems are the best problems. These are the type&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>High quality problems are the best problems.</p>
<p>These are the type of problems one only has when they have a good life. It presumes a good life.</p>
<p>For example, if you spend time thinking about how human beings could ever become starfaring, it presumes you are likely living a life of abundance. Or at least, you have the ability to live in denial.</p>
<p>Lots of good people are struggling with real problems, I won't call them low-quality, but these stink. How will I pay the bills? How will I get my next meal? Where will I lay my head?</p>
<p>These are heartbreakers.</p>
<p>Soulcrushers.</p>
<p>True problems.</p>
<p>Sometimes, you can catch yourself struggling with a high-quality problem.</p>
<p>It can consume you.</p>
<p>And it's important to realize that these are the problems we <em>strive</em> to have.</p>
<p>Where should we put our money? What shall next week's meals be? Should we move?</p>
<p>How do we interstellar travel?</p>
<p>All high-quality problems.</p>
<p>Ones to seek.</p>
<p>May all your problems be high af.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Army Of One</title>
        <author>
            <name>杻백</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/army-of-one/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/army-of-one/</id>

        <updated>2026-02-24T12:16:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    I know what you're thinking. You expect us to come here&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I know what you're thinking.</p>
<p><em>You expect us to come here everyday and read something that only takes you five minutes to write?</em></p>
<p>And to that I retort, "How dare you?"</p>
<p>First of all, I expect no one to read this.</p>
<p>Isn't that obvious?</p>
<p>This is [waves hands all around musings column] for me.</p>
<p>And second of all, I'll have you know it takes six minutes sometimes.</p>
<p>Maybe even seven.</p>
<p>Eight.</p>
<p>You might think I feign outrage when I have nothing to say.</p>
<p>You might think that.</p>
<p>And it might look like that right now.</p>
<p>You dirty son of a...</p>
<p>But you'd be wrong.</p>
<p>I just think in this day and age of everyone trying to sell you something, usually themselves, that me coming here and just writing about farts and love is awesome.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Starfaring</title>
        <author>
            <name>杻백</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/starfaring/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/starfaring/</id>

        <updated>2026-02-23T12:30:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Did you know, you can pay to have someone rocket you&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Did you know, you can pay to have someone rocket you into space after you pass?</p>
<p>I like to think I can dream big.</p>
<p>I like to think that I can picture infinity.</p>
<p>And God, the ultimate big and infinite, is foundational in my brain.</p>
<p>But when I think about interstellar travel, I wrestle with it.</p>
<p>A lot of folks who have the luxury of thinking about such things, think that a human being visiting another planet is one of the integral steps of our continuous survival.</p>
<p>Not just you and me, kid.</p>
<p>The earth and everyone on it.</p>
<p>So the end game (such as it is because it never ends) is to venture towards all the stars in the night's sky.</p>
<p>And go beyond them.</p>
<p>To see what we can't see.</p>
<p>To become a starfaring civilization.</p>
<p>It's the scale of this that's so staggering.</p>
<p>200 billion trillion (sextillion) stars. Of course, there's countless more planets.</p>
<p>But we are talking 2 x 10 to the 23rd power suns.</p>
<p>200,000,000,000,000,000,000,000.</p>
<p>That's a lot of suns.</p>
<p>That's a lot of zeroes.</p>
<p>23 of 'em.</p>
<p>MJ of 'em.</p>
<p>An astronomical amount of stars.</p>
<p>I don't care what you say, though.</p>
<p>Because at that scale, you're just guessing.</p>
<p>I'm just guessing.</p>
<p>The thing that astounds me about space is the vastness.</p>
<p>And this idea that it's empty.</p>
<p>Lifeless.</p>
<p>Mostly.</p>
<p>And I wonder, how can space be so expansive, but so vacant?</p>
<p>Am I missing something?</p>
<p>We are a long way from jet-setting between planets, a longer way from hopping galaxies and universes, and about forever away from taming it all.</p>
<p>Such as it ever could be.</p>
<p>But words are powerful.</p>
<p>Most powerful.</p>
<p><em>Quill over sword.</em></p>
<p>And one of my favorites is <em>starfaring</em>.</p>
<p><em>Traveling among the stars.</em></p>
<p>I just love it.</p>
<p>Oh, and if you're looking for me, you'll know where I will be.</p>
<p>Just tilt your chin up.</p>
<p>Forever,</p>
<p>游눪</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Liner Notes</title>
        <author>
            <name>杻백</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/liner-notes/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/liner-notes/</id>

        <updated>2026-02-22T12:03:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    One of my favorite parts of a good live album or&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>One of my favorite parts of a good live album or concert is the intro, the monologue, the banter.</p>
<p>Sometimes the band's playing a little something in the background, while the singer talks about the song coming up.</p>
<p>When I was young, I didn't like live versions.</p>
<p>I wanted the album version.</p>
<p>And most of the time, the live versions weren't as good.</p>
<p>Poorer sounding.</p>
<p>Vocally or otherwise.</p>
<p>Sometimes, these folks dared changing the lyrics!</p>
<p>Or turned it acoustic!</p>
<p>As I grew up, I learned I was wrong.</p>
<p>I realized how change could be so very magical.</p>
<p>How much play there was in doing it live.</p>
<p>How you can go acoustic, ballad, or electric.</p>
<p>How the same song can feel so different, can play so different, just by changing how you sing it.</p>
<p>And so, I learned that the true measure of a band was not in the safe studio, it was how they did it live.</p>
<p>Did they have a story to tell before certain songs.</p>
<p>Did they evolve it in the time since it's release.</p>
<p>You hear some artists say they hate to sing their hits because it's just the same crap over and over.</p>
<p>It becomes something of a catch phrase.</p>
<p>And I get that, maybe that's why songs do evolve.</p>
<p>To keep it interesting.</p>
<p>The best songs change over time. But they stay the same in spirit.</p>
<p>The best remakes are those that change fast to slow, electric to acoustic. But they stay the same in significance.</p>
<p>And versa vice.</p>
<p>I wish sometimes, that there was a piano playing behind me, while I stand on this stage.</p>
<p>Musing about music.</p>
<p>Sure, I hit some keys of my own, but they aren't the Mariah Carey or Bruce Hornsby kind, more the clicky-clacky.</p>
<p>And I just got to tell you, poetry comes in all forms.</p>
<p>You can read it, you can listen to it, you can see it in motion.</p>
<p>Live and in living color.</p>
<p>But most importantly, you can <em>feel</em> it.</p>
<p>To the bone.</p>
<p>In your heart.</p>
<p>For our souls.</p>
<p>This is for you.</p>
<p>[Cues up the band.]</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Karate Man Bruise On The Inside</title>
        <author>
            <name>杻백</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/karate-man-bruise-on-the-inside/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/karate-man-bruise-on-the-inside/</id>

        <updated>2026-02-21T13:14:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    We've all heard of eternal optimists. I'm an internal optimist. Sure,&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>We've all heard of eternal optimists.</p>
<p>I'm an <em>internal</em> optimist.</p>
<p>Sure, the exterior is crusty.</p>
<p>Rough.</p>
<p>Cantankerous.</p>
<p>But it's part of my charm.</p>
<p>I'm going for old(ish) curmudgeon.</p>
<p>And let me tell you something, I'm hitting it out of the stadium.</p>
<p>Boom!!!</p>
<p>But on the inside, and I think that's the side that matters, I'm hopeful.</p>
<p>I'm thankful.</p>
<p>I'm joyous.</p>
<p>If I went around looking like I feel, well I'd just have this goofy grin on my face.</p>
<p>And no one needs to see that.</p>
<p>So I furrow.</p>
<p>I scrunch.</p>
<p>Like the sun's in my eyes.</p>
<p>Pursed lips.</p>
<p>Like I'm scrutinizing something on the horizon.</p>
<p><em>Blue steel.</em></p>
<p>We have all known people so happy on the outside, and quite the reverse on the in.</p>
<p>So maybe all these sour patch adults are really just elated on the inside.</p>
<p>I'd like to believe that that's true.</p>
<p>At least it is for me.</p>
<p>Internal optimism.</p>
<p>Input output.</p>
<p>IO.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Venture</title>
        <author>
            <name>杻백</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/venture/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/venture/</id>

        <updated>2026-02-20T16:49:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    Credentials are an interesting thing. I used to be impressed with&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Credentials are an interesting thing.</p>
<p>I used to be impressed with them.</p>
<p>Used to impress myself with them.</p>
<p>Framed certificates signifying intellect.</p>
<p>Business cards and titles therewith.</p>
<p>Term sheets.</p>
<p>Firm handshakes (still important).</p>
<p>These things used to matter to me.</p>
<p>Now, I'm borderline feral.</p>
<p>Barely civilized, if I ever was.</p>
<p>Respectful, but wild.</p>
<p>I'm happy to say I have a lot of credentials.</p>
<p>Even happier to say I don't need 'em.</p>
<p>They got me here, in a roundabout way, and that's worth it in and of itself.</p>
<p>Couldn't be where I am without them.</p>
<p>Ties with collared shirts would break me out.</p>
<p>Felt like a costume.</p>
<p>A collar.</p>
<p>A leash.</p>
<p>I don't wear them anymore.</p>
<p>My old boss at the Menlo Park venture capital law firm said, "Alex, you need to be on the other side of the table."</p>
<p>I think he was trying to get rid of me, but he's right.</p>
<p>That's where I belong.</p>
<p>Been trying to fit square pegs in round holes my whole life.</p>
<p>Then I figured out something:</p>
<p>Credentials don't make you happy.</p>
<p>They make your parents happy.</p>
<p>Because it makes them feel better around other old Koreans.</p>
<p>I love my folks, but I wish they didn't care about what other old Koreans thought.</p>
<p>Everything, though, puts me right here.</p>
<p>Writing on this ridiculously good domain name just for my own personal joy.</p>
<p>Haha.</p>
<p>Weird.</p>
<p>游돜</p>
<p></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>There</title>
        <author>
            <name>杻백</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/there/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/there/</id>

        <updated>2026-02-19T13:55:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    I'm fighting something. I suppose we all are. It's creating a&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I'm fighting something.</p>
<p>I suppose we all are.</p>
<p>It's creating a bit of of a fog in my brain.</p>
<p>So this musing might be a bit off.</p>
<p>Or, maybe, better than all the rest.</p>
<p>I know what you're thinking.</p>
<p>He's just stalling again.</p>
<p>Trying to find the right words to say.</p>
<p>Because he's got no idea.</p>
<p>Wrong.</p>
<p>I know exactly what I want to say.</p>
<p>It just hasn't yet been conveyed to my fingertips.</p>
<p>But it's coming.</p>
<p>...</p>
<p>I will share a joke my daughter told me.</p>
<p>Reader, will you remember me?</p>
<p><em>Yes.</em></p>
<p>Reader, will you always remember me?</p>
<p><em>Of course. Why are you asking this?</em></p>
<p>Oh, you'll see. Knock knock.</p>
<p><em>[Sigh.] Who's there?</em></p>
<p>Reader...Did you already forget!?</p>
<p>游땎</p>
<p>It's much better when she tells it.</p>
<p>Because instead of Reader she says Daddy, but in a way that stretches out the word.</p>
<p>Remember the Alamo.</p>
<p>And the Al ya know.</p>
<p><em>Daaaaaaaadeeeeeeeeeee</em>.</p>
<p>游눙</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Laugh Art</title>
        <author>
            <name>杻백</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/laugh-art/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/laugh-art/</id>

        <updated>2026-02-18T12:34:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    You know what's a sweet sound? The sound of your own&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>You know what's a sweet sound?</p>
<p>The sound of your own belly laugh.</p>
<p>Sure, hearing the laughter of others is wonderful, but when you catch yourself doing it, it's pretty sweet.</p>
<p>I don't belly laugh much, but I did yesterday.</p>
<p>My son made an observation that just tickled me to the core.</p>
<p>He's a funny son of a good woman.</p>
<p>Sometimes, a deep belly laugh is greeted simultaneously with a lil toot.</p>
<p>Laughing out both ends.</p>
<p>That's when you know you're living right.</p>
<p>游뱎游눧</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Against The Machine</title>
        <author>
            <name>杻백</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://iterating.com/against-the-machine/"/>
        <id>https://iterating.com/against-the-machine/</id>

        <updated>2026-02-17T14:54:00-05:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                    As a man of peace, I tell you what, I'm angry.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>As a man of peace, I tell you what, I'm angry.</p>
<p>Seems like the thing to be these days.</p>
<p>Pissed.</p>
<p>Is that right?</p>
<p>You know what I love?</p>
<p>When some public official is behind a podium yelling at us.</p>
<p>Admonishing us.</p>
<p>The general public.</p>
<p>Why?</p>
<p>Because they are blaming us for the actions of some fool.</p>
<p>We gotta keep our kids safe!</p>
<p>We must end senseless violence!</p>
<p>Meanwhile, I'm here drinking a nice beverage wondering why some idiot is yelling at me (it happens, but not for long).</p>
<p>I understand why it happens. I just don't get why it works.</p>
<p>Or rather, why people accept it.</p>
<p>Shouldn't it be the other way?</p>
<p>Shouldn't it be us yelling at them?</p>
<p>Oh wait, they're using my technique.</p>
<p>Be more outraged than the outraged.</p>
<p>Proactively outraged.</p>
<p>Cobra Kai sheet.</p>
<p>Strike first. Strike hard!</p>
<p>No.</p>
<p>Mercy.</p>
<p>It's clever.</p>
<p>Seems to work.</p>
<p>Has for me.</p>
<p>Ah well.</p>
<p>Back to my beverage.</p>
<p>Oh boy, "rage" is in beve<em>rage</em>.</p>
<p>Where's that podium...it's around here somewhere.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>游꿧 Microphone check! 游꿧</p>
</blockquote>
<p>游꿗</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
